{
  "ticker": "AAPL",
  "entities": [
    {
      "text": "Apple Inc.",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 0,
      "end": 10,
      "sentence": "Apple Inc. (AAPL) shares are moving on a mix of strategic supply-chain partnerships, ecosystem expansions and back-to-school incentives, while sell-side rotation calls and legal overhang temper investor enthusiasm.",
      "context": "Apple Inc. (AAPL) shares are moving on a mix of strategic su",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "AAPL",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 12,
      "end": 16,
      "sentence": "Apple Inc. (AAPL) shares are moving on a mix of strategic supply-chain partnerships, ecosystem expansions and back-to-school incentives, while sell-side rotation calls and legal overhang temper investor enthusiasm.",
      "context": "Apple Inc. (AAPL) shares are moving on a mix of strategic supply-c",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Apple",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 235,
      "end": 240,
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nApple commits $500 million to MP Materials for U.S.-based rare earth magnets, reducing reliance on China and strengthening its supply chain.",
      "context": "g temper investor enthusiasm.\nPositive Sentiment:\nApple commits $500 million to MP Materials for U.S.-bas",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "$500 million",
      "label": "MONEY",
      "start": 249,
      "end": 261,
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nApple commits $500 million to MP Materials for U.S.-based rare earth magnets, reducing reliance on China and strengthening its supply chain.",
      "context": "tor enthusiasm.\nPositive Sentiment:\nApple commits $500 million to MP Materials for U.S.-based rare earth magnets",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": true
    },
    {
      "text": "MP Materials",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 265,
      "end": 277,
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nApple commits $500 million to MP Materials for U.S.-based rare earth magnets, reducing reliance on China and strengthening its supply chain.",
      "context": "Positive Sentiment:\nApple commits $500 million to MP Materials for U.S.-based rare earth magnets, reducing relia",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "U.S.-based",
      "label": "GPE",
      "start": 282,
      "end": 292,
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nApple commits $500 million to MP Materials for U.S.-based rare earth magnets, reducing reliance on China and strengthening its supply chain.",
      "context": "t:\nApple commits $500 million to MP Materials for U.S.-based rare earth magnets, reducing reliance on China an",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": true,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "China",
      "label": "GPE",
      "start": 334,
      "end": 339,
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nApple commits $500 million to MP Materials for U.S.-based rare earth magnets, reducing reliance on China and strengthening its supply chain.",
      "context": "S.-based rare earth magnets, reducing reliance on China and strengthening its supply chain.\nReuters: Appl",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": true,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Reuters",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 376,
      "end": 383,
      "sentence": "Reuters:",
      "context": "ance on China and strengthening its supply chain.\nReuters: Apple invests $500 million in rare earths mine o",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Apple",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 385,
      "end": 390,
      "sentence": "Apple invests $500 million in rare earths mine operator MP Materials\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "context": "hina and strengthening its supply chain.\nReuters: Apple invests $500 million in rare earths mine operator",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "$500 million",
      "label": "MONEY",
      "start": 399,
      "end": 411,
      "sentence": "Apple invests $500 million in rare earths mine operator MP Materials\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "context": "gthening its supply chain.\nReuters: Apple invests $500 million in rare earths mine operator MP Materials\nPositiv",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": true
    },
    {
      "text": "MP Materials",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 441,
      "end": 453,
      "sentence": "Apple invests $500 million in rare earths mine operator MP Materials\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "context": "invests $500 million in rare earths mine operator MP Materials\nPositive Sentiment:\nBloFin integrates Apple Pay,",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "BloFin",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 474,
      "end": 480,
      "sentence": "BloFin integrates Apple Pay, expanding Apple’s payment ecosystem and driving service adoption on its platform.",
      "context": "hs mine operator MP Materials\nPositive Sentiment:\nBloFin integrates Apple Pay, expanding Apple’s payment e",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Apple Pay",
      "label": "PRODUCT",
      "start": 492,
      "end": 501,
      "sentence": "BloFin integrates Apple Pay, expanding Apple’s payment ecosystem and driving service adoption on its platform.",
      "context": "P Materials\nPositive Sentiment:\nBloFin integrates Apple Pay, expanding Apple’s payment ecosystem and driving",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Apple",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 513,
      "end": 518,
      "sentence": "BloFin integrates Apple Pay, expanding Apple’s payment ecosystem and driving service adoption on its platform.",
      "context": "Sentiment:\nBloFin integrates Apple Pay, expanding Apple’s payment ecosystem and driving service adoption",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "BloFin",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 599,
      "end": 605,
      "sentence": "BloFin Adds Apple Pay Support",
      "context": "g service adoption on its platform.\nBusinessWire: BloFin Adds Apple Pay Support\nPositive Sentiment:\nNine s",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Apple Pay",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 611,
      "end": 620,
      "sentence": "BloFin Adds Apple Pay Support",
      "context": "option on its platform.\nBusinessWire: BloFin Adds Apple Pay Support\nPositive Sentiment:\nNine states announce",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Nine",
      "label": "CARDINAL",
      "start": 649,
      "end": 653,
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nNine states announce back-to-school sales tax holidays on Apple products, likely boosting consumer demand ahead of the fall season.\nBenzinga:",
      "context": "BloFin Adds Apple Pay Support\nPositive Sentiment:\nNine states announce back-to-school sales tax holidays",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Apple",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 707,
      "end": 712,
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nNine states announce back-to-school sales tax holidays on Apple products, likely boosting consumer demand ahead of the fall season.\nBenzinga:",
      "context": "tes announce back-to-school sales tax holidays on Apple products, likely boosting consumer demand ahead o",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "the fall season",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 764,
      "end": 779,
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nNine states announce back-to-school sales tax holidays on Apple products, likely boosting consumer demand ahead of the fall season.\nBenzinga:",
      "context": "roducts, likely boosting consumer demand ahead of the fall season.\nBenzinga: Apple Stock A Back-To-School Winner?\nP",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Apple",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 791,
      "end": 796,
      "sentence": "Apple Stock A Back-To-School Winner?",
      "context": "nsumer demand ahead of the fall season.\nBenzinga: Apple Stock A Back-To-School Winner?\nPositive Sentiment",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Cyberpunk 2077",
      "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
      "start": 848,
      "end": 862,
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCyberpunk 2077 arrives on Mac, showcasing strengthened support for Apple Silicon and broadening the Mac’s appeal to gamers.",
      "context": "tock A Back-To-School Winner?\nPositive Sentiment:\nCyberpunk 2077 arrives on Mac, showcasing strengthened support f",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Mac",
      "label": "PRODUCT",
      "start": 874,
      "end": 877,
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCyberpunk 2077 arrives on Mac, showcasing strengthened support for Apple Silicon and broadening the Mac’s appeal to gamers.",
      "context": "er?\nPositive Sentiment:\nCyberpunk 2077 arrives on Mac, showcasing strengthened support for Apple Silico",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Apple",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 915,
      "end": 920,
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCyberpunk 2077 arrives on Mac, showcasing strengthened support for Apple Silicon and broadening the Mac’s appeal to gamers.",
      "context": "rives on Mac, showcasing strengthened support for Apple Silicon and broadening the Mac’s appeal to gamers",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Mac",
      "label": "PRODUCT",
      "start": 948,
      "end": 951,
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCyberpunk 2077 arrives on Mac, showcasing strengthened support for Apple Silicon and broadening the Mac’s appeal to gamers.",
      "context": "ened support for Apple Silicon and broadening the Mac’s appeal to gamers.\nThe Verge: Cyberpunk 2077 is",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "The Verge:",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 972,
      "end": 982,
      "sentence": "The Verge: Cyberpunk 2077 is launching for Mac on July 17th\nNeutral Sentiment:\nApple appears in MarketBeat’s fitness and music stock watchlists, reflecting broad sector interest but offering limited immediate catalyst.",
      "context": "ilicon and broadening the Mac’s appeal to gamers.\nThe Verge: Cyberpunk 2077 is launching for Mac on July 17th",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Cyberpunk 2077",
      "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
      "start": 983,
      "end": 997,
      "sentence": "The Verge: Cyberpunk 2077 is launching for Mac on July 17th\nNeutral Sentiment:\nApple appears in MarketBeat’s fitness and music stock watchlists, reflecting broad sector interest but offering limited immediate catalyst.",
      "context": "broadening the Mac’s appeal to gamers.\nThe Verge: Cyberpunk 2077 is launching for Mac on July 17th\nNeutral Sentime",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "July 17th",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 1022,
      "end": 1031,
      "sentence": "The Verge: Cyberpunk 2077 is launching for Mac on July 17th\nNeutral Sentiment:\nApple appears in MarketBeat’s fitness and music stock watchlists, reflecting broad sector interest but offering limited immediate catalyst.",
      "context": "The Verge: Cyberpunk 2077 is launching for Mac on July 17th\nNeutral Sentiment:\nApple appears in MarketBeat’s",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Apple",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1051,
      "end": 1056,
      "sentence": "The Verge: Cyberpunk 2077 is launching for Mac on July 17th\nNeutral Sentiment:\nApple appears in MarketBeat’s fitness and music stock watchlists, reflecting broad sector interest but offering limited immediate catalyst.",
      "context": "launching for Mac on July 17th\nNeutral Sentiment:\nApple appears in MarketBeat’s fitness and music stock w",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "MarketBeat",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1068,
      "end": 1078,
      "sentence": "The Verge: Cyberpunk 2077 is launching for Mac on July 17th\nNeutral Sentiment:\nApple appears in MarketBeat’s fitness and music stock watchlists, reflecting broad sector interest but offering limited immediate catalyst.",
      "context": "on July 17th\nNeutral Sentiment:\nApple appears in MarketBeat’s fitness and music stock watchlists, reflecting",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Apple",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1349,
      "end": 1354,
      "sentence": "Fund manager calls to rotate out of Apple, citing stagnant iPhone demand, sketchy AI strategy and tariff-related supply risks.",
      "context": "ve Sentiment:\nFund manager calls to rotate out of Apple, citing stagnant iPhone demand, sketchy AI strate",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "iPhone",
      "label": "PRODUCT",
      "start": 1372,
      "end": 1378,
      "sentence": "Fund manager calls to rotate out of Apple, citing stagnant iPhone demand, sketchy AI strategy and tariff-related supply risks.",
      "context": "ger calls to rotate out of Apple, citing stagnant iPhone demand, sketchy AI strategy and tariff-related su",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Tesla",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1497,
      "end": 1502,
      "sentence": "MarketBeat: This Fund Manager Says You Should Get Out of Tesla and Apple—",
      "context": "eat: This Fund Manager Says You Should Get Out of Tesla and Apple—Now\nNegative Sentiment:\nAnalyst warns A",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Apple",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1507,
      "end": 1512,
      "sentence": "MarketBeat: This Fund Manager Says You Should Get Out of Tesla and Apple—",
      "context": "Fund Manager Says You Should Get Out of Tesla and Apple—Now\nNegative Sentiment:\nAnalyst warns Apple is “u",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Apple",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1551,
      "end": 1556,
      "sentence": "Analyst warns Apple is “unprepared for something transformational”, questioning its innovation roadmap.",
      "context": "a and Apple—Now\nNegative Sentiment:\nAnalyst warns Apple is “unprepared for something transformational”, q",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "AAPL",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1679,
      "end": 1683,
      "sentence": "Benzinga: Analyst With Sell Rating On AAPL Stock Warns...\nNegative Sentiment:\nJim Cramer urges Apple to curb buybacks and invest in AI, criticizing its capital allocation priorities.",
      "context": "on roadmap.\nBenzinga: Analyst With Sell Rating On AAPL Stock Warns...\nNegative Sentiment:\nJim Cramer urg",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Jim Cramer",
      "label": "PERSON",
      "start": 1719,
      "end": 1729,
      "sentence": "Benzinga: Analyst With Sell Rating On AAPL Stock Warns...\nNegative Sentiment:\nJim Cramer urges Apple to curb buybacks and invest in AI, criticizing its capital allocation priorities.",
      "context": "Rating On AAPL Stock Warns...\nNegative Sentiment:\nJim Cramer urges Apple to curb buybacks and invest in AI, cr",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": true,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Apple",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1736,
      "end": 1741,
      "sentence": "Benzinga: Analyst With Sell Rating On AAPL Stock Warns...\nNegative Sentiment:\nJim Cramer urges Apple to curb buybacks and invest in AI, criticizing its capital allocation priorities.",
      "context": "ock Warns...\nNegative Sentiment:\nJim Cramer urges Apple to curb buybacks and invest in AI, criticizing it",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Benzinga",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1824,
      "end": 1832,
      "sentence": "Benzinga:",
      "context": "I, criticizing its capital allocation priorities.\nBenzinga: Cramer To Apple: Kick The Buyback Addiction - Bu",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Cramer",
      "label": "PERSON",
      "start": 1834,
      "end": 1840,
      "sentence": "Cramer To Apple: Kick The Buyback Addiction - Buy A Brain Instead",
      "context": "zing its capital allocation priorities.\nBenzinga: Cramer To Apple: Kick The Buyback Addiction - Buy A Brai",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": true,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Apple",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1844,
      "end": 1849,
      "sentence": "Cramer To Apple: Kick The Buyback Addiction - Buy A Brain Instead",
      "context": "apital allocation priorities.\nBenzinga: Cramer To Apple: Kick The Buyback Addiction - Buy A Brain Instead",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "August 19th",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 2031,
      "end": 2042,
      "sentence": "BusinessWire: Deadline on August 19th Coming Up in Lawsuit\nPosted 53m ago\nAI Generated.",
      "context": "rhang for shareholders.\nBusinessWire: Deadline on August 19th Coming Up in Lawsuit\nPosted 53m ago\nAI Generated.",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "53m ago",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 2071,
      "end": 2078,
      "sentence": "BusinessWire: Deadline on August 19th Coming Up in Lawsuit\nPosted 53m ago\nAI Generated.",
      "context": "adline on August 19th Coming Up in Lawsuit\nPosted 53m ago\nAI Generated. May Contain Errors.",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    }
  ],
  "relationships": [
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "calls",
      "verb": "temper",
      "object": "enthusiasm",
      "sentence": "Apple Inc. (AAPL) shares are moving on a mix of strategic supply-chain partnerships, ecosystem expansions and back-to-school incentives, while sell-side rotation calls and legal overhang temper investor enthusiasm.",
      "importance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Apple",
      "verb": "commits",
      "object": "million",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nApple commits $500 million to MP Materials for U.S.-based rare earth magnets, reducing reliance on China and strengthening its supply chain.",
      "importance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Apple",
      "verb": "invests",
      "object": "million",
      "sentence": "Apple invests $500 million in rare earths mine operator MP Materials\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "importance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "BloFin",
      "verb": "integrates",
      "object": "Pay",
      "sentence": "BloFin integrates Apple Pay, expanding Apple’s payment ecosystem and driving service adoption on its platform.",
      "importance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "BloFin",
      "verb": "Adds",
      "object": "Support",
      "sentence": "BloFin Adds Apple Pay Support",
      "importance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "states",
      "verb": "announce",
      "object": "holidays",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nNine states announce back-to-school sales tax holidays on Apple products, likely boosting consumer demand ahead of the fall season.\nBenzinga:",
      "importance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Cramer",
      "verb": "urges",
      "object": "Apple",
      "sentence": "Benzinga: Analyst With Sell Rating On AAPL Stock Warns...\nNegative Sentiment:\nJim Cramer urges Apple to curb buybacks and invest in AI, criticizing its capital allocation priorities.",
      "importance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "lawsuits",
      "verb": "pose",
      "object": "overhang",
      "sentence": "Negative Sentiment:\nClass action lawsuits and upcoming deadlines pose a legal overhang for shareholders.",
      "importance": 0
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Apple",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Inc.",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Apple Inc. (AAPL) shares are moving on a mix of strategic supply-chain partnerships, ecosystem expansions and back-to-school incentives, while sell-side rotation calls and legal overhang temper investor enthusiasm.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Apple",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "AAPL",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Apple Inc. (AAPL) shares are moving on a mix of strategic supply-chain partnerships, ecosystem expansions and back-to-school incentives, while sell-side rotation calls and legal overhang temper investor enthusiasm.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Inc.",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "AAPL",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Apple Inc. (AAPL) shares are moving on a mix of strategic supply-chain partnerships, ecosystem expansions and back-to-school incentives, while sell-side rotation calls and legal overhang temper investor enthusiasm.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Apple",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "$",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nApple commits $500 million to MP Materials for U.S.-based rare earth magnets, reducing reliance on China and strengthening its supply chain.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Apple",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "500",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nApple commits $500 million to MP Materials for U.S.-based rare earth magnets, reducing reliance on China and strengthening its supply chain.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Apple",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "million",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nApple commits $500 million to MP Materials for U.S.-based rare earth magnets, reducing reliance on China and strengthening its supply chain.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Apple",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "MP",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nApple commits $500 million to MP Materials for U.S.-based rare earth magnets, reducing reliance on China and strengthening its supply chain.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Apple",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Materials",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nApple commits $500 million to MP Materials for U.S.-based rare earth magnets, reducing reliance on China and strengthening its supply chain.",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Apple",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "U.S.-based",
      "entity2_type": "GPE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nApple commits $500 million to MP Materials for U.S.-based rare earth magnets, reducing reliance on China and strengthening its supply chain.",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Apple",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "China",
      "entity2_type": "GPE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nApple commits $500 million to MP Materials for U.S.-based rare earth magnets, reducing reliance on China and strengthening its supply chain.",
      "distance": 17
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "$",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "500",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nApple commits $500 million to MP Materials for U.S.-based rare earth magnets, reducing reliance on China and strengthening its supply chain.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "$",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "million",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nApple commits $500 million to MP Materials for U.S.-based rare earth magnets, reducing reliance on China and strengthening its supply chain.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "$",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "MP",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nApple commits $500 million to MP Materials for U.S.-based rare earth magnets, reducing reliance on China and strengthening its supply chain.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "$",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "Materials",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nApple commits $500 million to MP Materials for U.S.-based rare earth magnets, reducing reliance on China and strengthening its supply chain.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "$",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "U.S.-based",
      "entity2_type": "GPE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nApple commits $500 million to MP Materials for U.S.-based rare earth magnets, reducing reliance on China and strengthening its supply chain.",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "$",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "China",
      "entity2_type": "GPE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nApple commits $500 million to MP Materials for U.S.-based rare earth magnets, reducing reliance on China and strengthening its supply chain.",
      "distance": 15
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "500",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "million",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nApple commits $500 million to MP Materials for U.S.-based rare earth magnets, reducing reliance on China and strengthening its supply chain.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "500",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "MP",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nApple commits $500 million to MP Materials for U.S.-based rare earth magnets, reducing reliance on China and strengthening its supply chain.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "500",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "Materials",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nApple commits $500 million to MP Materials for U.S.-based rare earth magnets, reducing reliance on China and strengthening its supply chain.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "500",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "U.S.-based",
      "entity2_type": "GPE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nApple commits $500 million to MP Materials for U.S.-based rare earth magnets, reducing reliance on China and strengthening its supply chain.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "500",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "China",
      "entity2_type": "GPE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nApple commits $500 million to MP Materials for U.S.-based rare earth magnets, reducing reliance on China and strengthening its supply chain.",
      "distance": 14
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "million",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "MP",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nApple commits $500 million to MP Materials for U.S.-based rare earth magnets, reducing reliance on China and strengthening its supply chain.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "million",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "Materials",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nApple commits $500 million to MP Materials for U.S.-based rare earth magnets, reducing reliance on China and strengthening its supply chain.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "million",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "U.S.-based",
      "entity2_type": "GPE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nApple commits $500 million to MP Materials for U.S.-based rare earth magnets, reducing reliance on China and strengthening its supply chain.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "million",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "China",
      "entity2_type": "GPE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nApple commits $500 million to MP Materials for U.S.-based rare earth magnets, reducing reliance on China and strengthening its supply chain.",
      "distance": 13
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "MP",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Materials",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nApple commits $500 million to MP Materials for U.S.-based rare earth magnets, reducing reliance on China and strengthening its supply chain.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "MP",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "U.S.-based",
      "entity2_type": "GPE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nApple commits $500 million to MP Materials for U.S.-based rare earth magnets, reducing reliance on China and strengthening its supply chain.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "MP",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "China",
      "entity2_type": "GPE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nApple commits $500 million to MP Materials for U.S.-based rare earth magnets, reducing reliance on China and strengthening its supply chain.",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Materials",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "U.S.-based",
      "entity2_type": "GPE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nApple commits $500 million to MP Materials for U.S.-based rare earth magnets, reducing reliance on China and strengthening its supply chain.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Materials",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "China",
      "entity2_type": "GPE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nApple commits $500 million to MP Materials for U.S.-based rare earth magnets, reducing reliance on China and strengthening its supply chain.",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "U.S.-based",
      "entity1_type": "GPE",
      "entity2": "China",
      "entity2_type": "GPE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nApple commits $500 million to MP Materials for U.S.-based rare earth magnets, reducing reliance on China and strengthening its supply chain.",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Apple",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "$",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Apple invests $500 million in rare earths mine operator MP Materials\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Apple",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "500",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Apple invests $500 million in rare earths mine operator MP Materials\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Apple",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "million",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Apple invests $500 million in rare earths mine operator MP Materials\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Apple",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "MP",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Apple invests $500 million in rare earths mine operator MP Materials\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Apple",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Materials",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Apple invests $500 million in rare earths mine operator MP Materials\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "$",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "500",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Apple invests $500 million in rare earths mine operator MP Materials\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "$",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "million",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Apple invests $500 million in rare earths mine operator MP Materials\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "$",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "MP",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Apple invests $500 million in rare earths mine operator MP Materials\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "$",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "Materials",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Apple invests $500 million in rare earths mine operator MP Materials\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "500",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "million",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Apple invests $500 million in rare earths mine operator MP Materials\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "500",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "MP",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Apple invests $500 million in rare earths mine operator MP Materials\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "500",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "Materials",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Apple invests $500 million in rare earths mine operator MP Materials\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "million",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "MP",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Apple invests $500 million in rare earths mine operator MP Materials\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "million",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "Materials",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Apple invests $500 million in rare earths mine operator MP Materials\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "MP",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Materials",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Apple invests $500 million in rare earths mine operator MP Materials\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "BloFin",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Apple",
      "entity2_type": "PRODUCT",
      "sentence": "BloFin integrates Apple Pay, expanding Apple’s payment ecosystem and driving service adoption on its platform.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "BloFin",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Pay",
      "entity2_type": "PRODUCT",
      "sentence": "BloFin integrates Apple Pay, expanding Apple’s payment ecosystem and driving service adoption on its platform.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "BloFin",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Apple",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "BloFin integrates Apple Pay, expanding Apple’s payment ecosystem and driving service adoption on its platform.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Apple",
      "entity1_type": "PRODUCT",
      "entity2": "Pay",
      "entity2_type": "PRODUCT",
      "sentence": "BloFin integrates Apple Pay, expanding Apple’s payment ecosystem and driving service adoption on its platform.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Apple",
      "entity1_type": "PRODUCT",
      "entity2": "Apple",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "BloFin integrates Apple Pay, expanding Apple’s payment ecosystem and driving service adoption on its platform.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Pay",
      "entity1_type": "PRODUCT",
      "entity2": "Apple",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "BloFin integrates Apple Pay, expanding Apple’s payment ecosystem and driving service adoption on its platform.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "BloFin",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Apple",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "BloFin Adds Apple Pay Support",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "BloFin",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Pay",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "BloFin Adds Apple Pay Support",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Apple",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Pay",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "BloFin Adds Apple Pay Support",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Nine",
      "entity1_type": "CARDINAL",
      "entity2": "Apple",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nNine states announce back-to-school sales tax holidays on Apple products, likely boosting consumer demand ahead of the fall season.\nBenzinga:",
      "distance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Nine",
      "entity1_type": "CARDINAL",
      "entity2": "the",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nNine states announce back-to-school sales tax holidays on Apple products, likely boosting consumer demand ahead of the fall season.\nBenzinga:",
      "distance": 21
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Nine",
      "entity1_type": "CARDINAL",
      "entity2": "fall",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nNine states announce back-to-school sales tax holidays on Apple products, likely boosting consumer demand ahead of the fall season.\nBenzinga:",
      "distance": 22
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Nine",
      "entity1_type": "CARDINAL",
      "entity2": "season",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nNine states announce back-to-school sales tax holidays on Apple products, likely boosting consumer demand ahead of the fall season.\nBenzinga:",
      "distance": 23
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Apple",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "the",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nNine states announce back-to-school sales tax holidays on Apple products, likely boosting consumer demand ahead of the fall season.\nBenzinga:",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Apple",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "fall",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nNine states announce back-to-school sales tax holidays on Apple products, likely boosting consumer demand ahead of the fall season.\nBenzinga:",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Apple",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "season",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nNine states announce back-to-school sales tax holidays on Apple products, likely boosting consumer demand ahead of the fall season.\nBenzinga:",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "the",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "fall",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nNine states announce back-to-school sales tax holidays on Apple products, likely boosting consumer demand ahead of the fall season.\nBenzinga:",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "the",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "season",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nNine states announce back-to-school sales tax holidays on Apple products, likely boosting consumer demand ahead of the fall season.\nBenzinga:",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "fall",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "season",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nNine states announce back-to-school sales tax holidays on Apple products, likely boosting consumer demand ahead of the fall season.\nBenzinga:",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Cyberpunk",
      "entity1_type": "WORK_OF_ART",
      "entity2": "2077",
      "entity2_type": "WORK_OF_ART",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCyberpunk 2077 arrives on Mac, showcasing strengthened support for Apple Silicon and broadening the Mac’s appeal to gamers.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Cyberpunk",
      "entity1_type": "WORK_OF_ART",
      "entity2": "Mac",
      "entity2_type": "PRODUCT",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCyberpunk 2077 arrives on Mac, showcasing strengthened support for Apple Silicon and broadening the Mac’s appeal to gamers.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Cyberpunk",
      "entity1_type": "WORK_OF_ART",
      "entity2": "Apple",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCyberpunk 2077 arrives on Mac, showcasing strengthened support for Apple Silicon and broadening the Mac’s appeal to gamers.",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Cyberpunk",
      "entity1_type": "WORK_OF_ART",
      "entity2": "Mac",
      "entity2_type": "PRODUCT",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCyberpunk 2077 arrives on Mac, showcasing strengthened support for Apple Silicon and broadening the Mac’s appeal to gamers.",
      "distance": 15
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "2077",
      "entity1_type": "WORK_OF_ART",
      "entity2": "Mac",
      "entity2_type": "PRODUCT",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCyberpunk 2077 arrives on Mac, showcasing strengthened support for Apple Silicon and broadening the Mac’s appeal to gamers.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "2077",
      "entity1_type": "WORK_OF_ART",
      "entity2": "Apple",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCyberpunk 2077 arrives on Mac, showcasing strengthened support for Apple Silicon and broadening the Mac’s appeal to gamers.",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "2077",
      "entity1_type": "WORK_OF_ART",
      "entity2": "Mac",
      "entity2_type": "PRODUCT",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCyberpunk 2077 arrives on Mac, showcasing strengthened support for Apple Silicon and broadening the Mac’s appeal to gamers.",
      "distance": 14
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Mac",
      "entity1_type": "PRODUCT",
      "entity2": "Apple",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCyberpunk 2077 arrives on Mac, showcasing strengthened support for Apple Silicon and broadening the Mac’s appeal to gamers.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Mac",
      "entity1_type": "PRODUCT",
      "entity2": "Mac",
      "entity2_type": "PRODUCT",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCyberpunk 2077 arrives on Mac, showcasing strengthened support for Apple Silicon and broadening the Mac’s appeal to gamers.",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Apple",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Mac",
      "entity2_type": "PRODUCT",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCyberpunk 2077 arrives on Mac, showcasing strengthened support for Apple Silicon and broadening the Mac’s appeal to gamers.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "The",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Verge",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "The Verge: Cyberpunk 2077 is launching for Mac on July 17th\nNeutral Sentiment:\nApple appears in MarketBeat’s fitness and music stock watchlists, reflecting broad sector interest but offering limited immediate catalyst.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "The",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": ":",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "The Verge: Cyberpunk 2077 is launching for Mac on July 17th\nNeutral Sentiment:\nApple appears in MarketBeat’s fitness and music stock watchlists, reflecting broad sector interest but offering limited immediate catalyst.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "The",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Cyberpunk",
      "entity2_type": "WORK_OF_ART",
      "sentence": "The Verge: Cyberpunk 2077 is launching for Mac on July 17th\nNeutral Sentiment:\nApple appears in MarketBeat’s fitness and music stock watchlists, reflecting broad sector interest but offering limited immediate catalyst.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "The",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "2077",
      "entity2_type": "WORK_OF_ART",
      "sentence": "The Verge: Cyberpunk 2077 is launching for Mac on July 17th\nNeutral Sentiment:\nApple appears in MarketBeat’s fitness and music stock watchlists, reflecting broad sector interest but offering limited immediate catalyst.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "The",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "July",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "The Verge: Cyberpunk 2077 is launching for Mac on July 17th\nNeutral Sentiment:\nApple appears in MarketBeat’s fitness and music stock watchlists, reflecting broad sector interest but offering limited immediate catalyst.",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "The",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "17th",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "The Verge: Cyberpunk 2077 is launching for Mac on July 17th\nNeutral Sentiment:\nApple appears in MarketBeat’s fitness and music stock watchlists, reflecting broad sector interest but offering limited immediate catalyst.",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "The",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Apple",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "The Verge: Cyberpunk 2077 is launching for Mac on July 17th\nNeutral Sentiment:\nApple appears in MarketBeat’s fitness and music stock watchlists, reflecting broad sector interest but offering limited immediate catalyst.",
      "distance": 17
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "The",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "MarketBeat",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "The Verge: Cyberpunk 2077 is launching for Mac on July 17th\nNeutral Sentiment:\nApple appears in MarketBeat’s fitness and music stock watchlists, reflecting broad sector interest but offering limited immediate catalyst.",
      "distance": 20
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Verge",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": ":",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "The Verge: Cyberpunk 2077 is launching for Mac on July 17th\nNeutral Sentiment:\nApple appears in MarketBeat’s fitness and music stock watchlists, reflecting broad sector interest but offering limited immediate catalyst.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Verge",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Cyberpunk",
      "entity2_type": "WORK_OF_ART",
      "sentence": "The Verge: Cyberpunk 2077 is launching for Mac on July 17th\nNeutral Sentiment:\nApple appears in MarketBeat’s fitness and music stock watchlists, reflecting broad sector interest but offering limited immediate catalyst.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Verge",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "2077",
      "entity2_type": "WORK_OF_ART",
      "sentence": "The Verge: Cyberpunk 2077 is launching for Mac on July 17th\nNeutral Sentiment:\nApple appears in MarketBeat’s fitness and music stock watchlists, reflecting broad sector interest but offering limited immediate catalyst.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Verge",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "July",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "The Verge: Cyberpunk 2077 is launching for Mac on July 17th\nNeutral Sentiment:\nApple appears in MarketBeat’s fitness and music stock watchlists, reflecting broad sector interest but offering limited immediate catalyst.",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Verge",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "17th",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "The Verge: Cyberpunk 2077 is launching for Mac on July 17th\nNeutral Sentiment:\nApple appears in MarketBeat’s fitness and music stock watchlists, reflecting broad sector interest but offering limited immediate catalyst.",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Verge",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Apple",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "The Verge: Cyberpunk 2077 is launching for Mac on July 17th\nNeutral Sentiment:\nApple appears in MarketBeat’s fitness and music stock watchlists, reflecting broad sector interest but offering limited immediate catalyst.",
      "distance": 16
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Verge",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "MarketBeat",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "The Verge: Cyberpunk 2077 is launching for Mac on July 17th\nNeutral Sentiment:\nApple appears in MarketBeat’s fitness and music stock watchlists, reflecting broad sector interest but offering limited immediate catalyst.",
      "distance": 19
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": ":",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Cyberpunk",
      "entity2_type": "WORK_OF_ART",
      "sentence": "The Verge: Cyberpunk 2077 is launching for Mac on July 17th\nNeutral Sentiment:\nApple appears in MarketBeat’s fitness and music stock watchlists, reflecting broad sector interest but offering limited immediate catalyst.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": ":",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "2077",
      "entity2_type": "WORK_OF_ART",
      "sentence": "The Verge: Cyberpunk 2077 is launching for Mac on July 17th\nNeutral Sentiment:\nApple appears in MarketBeat’s fitness and music stock watchlists, reflecting broad sector interest but offering limited immediate catalyst.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": ":",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "July",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "The Verge: Cyberpunk 2077 is launching for Mac on July 17th\nNeutral Sentiment:\nApple appears in MarketBeat’s fitness and music stock watchlists, reflecting broad sector interest but offering limited immediate catalyst.",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": ":",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "17th",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "The Verge: Cyberpunk 2077 is launching for Mac on July 17th\nNeutral Sentiment:\nApple appears in MarketBeat’s fitness and music stock watchlists, reflecting broad sector interest but offering limited immediate catalyst.",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": ":",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Apple",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "The Verge: Cyberpunk 2077 is launching for Mac on July 17th\nNeutral Sentiment:\nApple appears in MarketBeat’s fitness and music stock watchlists, reflecting broad sector interest but offering limited immediate catalyst.",
      "distance": 15
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": ":",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "MarketBeat",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "The Verge: Cyberpunk 2077 is launching for Mac on July 17th\nNeutral Sentiment:\nApple appears in MarketBeat’s fitness and music stock watchlists, reflecting broad sector interest but offering limited immediate catalyst.",
      "distance": 18
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Cyberpunk",
      "entity1_type": "WORK_OF_ART",
      "entity2": "2077",
      "entity2_type": "WORK_OF_ART",
      "sentence": "The Verge: Cyberpunk 2077 is launching for Mac on July 17th\nNeutral Sentiment:\nApple appears in MarketBeat’s fitness and music stock watchlists, reflecting broad sector interest but offering limited immediate catalyst.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Cyberpunk",
      "entity1_type": "WORK_OF_ART",
      "entity2": "July",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "The Verge: Cyberpunk 2077 is launching for Mac on July 17th\nNeutral Sentiment:\nApple appears in MarketBeat’s fitness and music stock watchlists, reflecting broad sector interest but offering limited immediate catalyst.",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Cyberpunk",
      "entity1_type": "WORK_OF_ART",
      "entity2": "17th",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "The Verge: Cyberpunk 2077 is launching for Mac on July 17th\nNeutral Sentiment:\nApple appears in MarketBeat’s fitness and music stock watchlists, reflecting broad sector interest but offering limited immediate catalyst.",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Cyberpunk",
      "entity1_type": "WORK_OF_ART",
      "entity2": "Apple",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "The Verge: Cyberpunk 2077 is launching for Mac on July 17th\nNeutral Sentiment:\nApple appears in MarketBeat’s fitness and music stock watchlists, reflecting broad sector interest but offering limited immediate catalyst.",
      "distance": 14
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Cyberpunk",
      "entity1_type": "WORK_OF_ART",
      "entity2": "MarketBeat",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "The Verge: Cyberpunk 2077 is launching for Mac on July 17th\nNeutral Sentiment:\nApple appears in MarketBeat’s fitness and music stock watchlists, reflecting broad sector interest but offering limited immediate catalyst.",
      "distance": 17
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "2077",
      "entity1_type": "WORK_OF_ART",
      "entity2": "July",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "The Verge: Cyberpunk 2077 is launching for Mac on July 17th\nNeutral Sentiment:\nApple appears in MarketBeat’s fitness and music stock watchlists, reflecting broad sector interest but offering limited immediate catalyst.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "2077",
      "entity1_type": "WORK_OF_ART",
      "entity2": "17th",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "The Verge: Cyberpunk 2077 is launching for Mac on July 17th\nNeutral Sentiment:\nApple appears in MarketBeat’s fitness and music stock watchlists, reflecting broad sector interest but offering limited immediate catalyst.",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "2077",
      "entity1_type": "WORK_OF_ART",
      "entity2": "Apple",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "The Verge: Cyberpunk 2077 is launching for Mac on July 17th\nNeutral Sentiment:\nApple appears in MarketBeat’s fitness and music stock watchlists, reflecting broad sector interest but offering limited immediate catalyst.",
      "distance": 13
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "2077",
      "entity1_type": "WORK_OF_ART",
      "entity2": "MarketBeat",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "The Verge: Cyberpunk 2077 is launching for Mac on July 17th\nNeutral Sentiment:\nApple appears in MarketBeat’s fitness and music stock watchlists, reflecting broad sector interest but offering limited immediate catalyst.",
      "distance": 16
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "July",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "17th",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "The Verge: Cyberpunk 2077 is launching for Mac on July 17th\nNeutral Sentiment:\nApple appears in MarketBeat’s fitness and music stock watchlists, reflecting broad sector interest but offering limited immediate catalyst.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "July",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "Apple",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "The Verge: Cyberpunk 2077 is launching for Mac on July 17th\nNeutral Sentiment:\nApple appears in MarketBeat’s fitness and music stock watchlists, reflecting broad sector interest but offering limited immediate catalyst.",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "July",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "MarketBeat",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "The Verge: Cyberpunk 2077 is launching for Mac on July 17th\nNeutral Sentiment:\nApple appears in MarketBeat’s fitness and music stock watchlists, reflecting broad sector interest but offering limited immediate catalyst.",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "17th",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "Apple",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "The Verge: Cyberpunk 2077 is launching for Mac on July 17th\nNeutral Sentiment:\nApple appears in MarketBeat’s fitness and music stock watchlists, reflecting broad sector interest but offering limited immediate catalyst.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "17th",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "MarketBeat",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "The Verge: Cyberpunk 2077 is launching for Mac on July 17th\nNeutral Sentiment:\nApple appears in MarketBeat’s fitness and music stock watchlists, reflecting broad sector interest but offering limited immediate catalyst.",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Apple",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "MarketBeat",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "The Verge: Cyberpunk 2077 is launching for Mac on July 17th\nNeutral Sentiment:\nApple appears in MarketBeat’s fitness and music stock watchlists, reflecting broad sector interest but offering limited immediate catalyst.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Apple",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "iPhone",
      "entity2_type": "PRODUCT",
      "sentence": "Fund manager calls to rotate out of Apple, citing stagnant iPhone demand, sketchy AI strategy and tariff-related supply risks.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Tesla",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Apple",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "MarketBeat: This Fund Manager Says You Should Get Out of Tesla and Apple—",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "AAPL",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Jim",
      "entity2_type": "PERSON",
      "sentence": "Benzinga: Analyst With Sell Rating On AAPL Stock Warns...\nNegative Sentiment:\nJim Cramer urges Apple to curb buybacks and invest in AI, criticizing its capital allocation priorities.",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "AAPL",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Cramer",
      "entity2_type": "PERSON",
      "sentence": "Benzinga: Analyst With Sell Rating On AAPL Stock Warns...\nNegative Sentiment:\nJim Cramer urges Apple to curb buybacks and invest in AI, criticizing its capital allocation priorities.",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "AAPL",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Apple",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Benzinga: Analyst With Sell Rating On AAPL Stock Warns...\nNegative Sentiment:\nJim Cramer urges Apple to curb buybacks and invest in AI, criticizing its capital allocation priorities.",
      "distance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Jim",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "Cramer",
      "entity2_type": "PERSON",
      "sentence": "Benzinga: Analyst With Sell Rating On AAPL Stock Warns...\nNegative Sentiment:\nJim Cramer urges Apple to curb buybacks and invest in AI, criticizing its capital allocation priorities.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Jim",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "Apple",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Benzinga: Analyst With Sell Rating On AAPL Stock Warns...\nNegative Sentiment:\nJim Cramer urges Apple to curb buybacks and invest in AI, criticizing its capital allocation priorities.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Cramer",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "Apple",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Benzinga: Analyst With Sell Rating On AAPL Stock Warns...\nNegative Sentiment:\nJim Cramer urges Apple to curb buybacks and invest in AI, criticizing its capital allocation priorities.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Cramer",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "Apple",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Cramer To Apple: Kick The Buyback Addiction - Buy A Brain Instead",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "August",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "19th",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "BusinessWire: Deadline on August 19th Coming Up in Lawsuit\nPosted 53m ago\nAI Generated.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "August",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "53",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "BusinessWire: Deadline on August 19th Coming Up in Lawsuit\nPosted 53m ago\nAI Generated.",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "August",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "m",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "BusinessWire: Deadline on August 19th Coming Up in Lawsuit\nPosted 53m ago\nAI Generated.",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "August",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "ago",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "BusinessWire: Deadline on August 19th Coming Up in Lawsuit\nPosted 53m ago\nAI Generated.",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "19th",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "53",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "BusinessWire: Deadline on August 19th Coming Up in Lawsuit\nPosted 53m ago\nAI Generated.",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "19th",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "m",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "BusinessWire: Deadline on August 19th Coming Up in Lawsuit\nPosted 53m ago\nAI Generated.",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "19th",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "ago",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "BusinessWire: Deadline on August 19th Coming Up in Lawsuit\nPosted 53m ago\nAI Generated.",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "53",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "m",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "BusinessWire: Deadline on August 19th Coming Up in Lawsuit\nPosted 53m ago\nAI Generated.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "53",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "ago",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "BusinessWire: Deadline on August 19th Coming Up in Lawsuit\nPosted 53m ago\nAI Generated.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "m",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "ago",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "BusinessWire: Deadline on August 19th Coming Up in Lawsuit\nPosted 53m ago\nAI Generated.",
      "distance": 1
    }
  ],
  "key_phrases": [
    {
      "text": "a mix",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "strategic supply-chain partnerships",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "ecosystem expansions",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "sell-side rotation calls",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "legal overhang",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "investor enthusiasm",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "Positive Sentiment",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "MP Materials",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "U.S.-based rare earth magnets",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "its supply chain",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "rare earths mine operator MP Materials",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "Positive Sentiment",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "Apple Pay",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "Apple’s payment ecosystem",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "service adoption",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "its platform",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "Apple Pay Support",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "Positive Sentiment",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "Nine states",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "Apple products",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "consumer demand",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "the fall season",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "Apple Stock",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "market_term"
    },
    {
      "text": "Positive Sentiment",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "strengthened support",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "Apple Silicon",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "the Mac’s appeal",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "July 17th",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "MarketBeat’s fitness and music stock watchlists",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "market_term"
    },
    {
      "text": "broad sector interest",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "limited immediate catalyst",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "Fitness Stocks",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "market_term"
    },
    {
      "text": "Your Watchlist",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "Music Stocks",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "market_term"
    },
    {
      "text": "Negative Sentiment",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "Fund manager",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "stagnant iPhone demand",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "sketchy AI strategy",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "tariff-related supply risks",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "This Fund Manager",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "Negative Sentiment",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "its innovation roadmap",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "Sell Rating",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "AAPL Stock",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "market_term"
    },
    {
      "text": "Jim Cramer",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "its capital allocation priorities",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "The Buyback Addiction",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "A Brain",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "Negative Sentiment",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "Class action lawsuits",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "upcoming deadlines",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "a legal overhang",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "August 19th",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "$500 million",
      "type": "pattern",
      "category": "money"
    },
    {
      "text": "$500 million",
      "type": "pattern",
      "category": "money"
    },
    {
      "text": "Stock",
      "type": "pattern",
      "category": "market_term"
    },
    {
      "text": "stock",
      "type": "pattern",
      "category": "market_term"
    },
    {
      "text": "Stock",
      "type": "pattern",
      "category": "market_term"
    }
  ],
  "important_sentences": [
    {
      "text": "The Verge: Cyberpunk 2077 is launching for Mac on July 17th\nNeutral Sentiment:\nApple appears in MarketBeat’s fitness and music stock watchlists, reflecting broad sector interest but offering limited immediate catalyst.",
      "importance_score": 39,
      "entity_count": 9,
      "financial_keyword_count": 3,
      "money_count": 0,
      "company_count": 3,
      "sentiment": "neutral"
    },
    {
      "text": "Benzinga: Analyst With Sell Rating On AAPL Stock Warns...\nNegative Sentiment:\nJim Cramer urges Apple to curb buybacks and invest in AI, criticizing its capital allocation priorities.",
      "importance_score": 31,
      "entity_count": 4,
      "financial_keyword_count": 5,
      "money_count": 0,
      "company_count": 2,
      "sentiment": "negative"
    },
    {
      "text": "Positive Sentiment:\nApple commits $500 million to MP Materials for U.S.-based rare earth magnets, reducing reliance on China and strengthening its supply chain.",
      "importance_score": 29,
      "entity_count": 8,
      "financial_keyword_count": 0,
      "money_count": 1,
      "company_count": 2,
      "sentiment": "positive"
    },
    {
      "text": "Apple invests $500 million in rare earths mine operator MP Materials\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "importance_score": 25,
      "entity_count": 6,
      "financial_keyword_count": 0,
      "money_count": 1,
      "company_count": 2,
      "sentiment": "positive"
    },
    {
      "text": "BloFin integrates Apple Pay, expanding Apple’s payment ecosystem and driving service adoption on its platform.",
      "importance_score": 19,
      "entity_count": 4,
      "financial_keyword_count": 1,
      "money_count": 0,
      "company_count": 2,
      "sentiment": "neutral"
    },
    {
      "text": "Apple Inc. (AAPL) shares are moving on a mix of strategic supply-chain partnerships, ecosystem expansions and back-to-school incentives, while sell-side rotation calls and legal overhang temper investor enthusiasm.",
      "importance_score": 17,
      "entity_count": 3,
      "financial_keyword_count": 1,
      "money_count": 0,
      "company_count": 2,
      "sentiment": "neutral"
    },
    {
      "text": "Positive Sentiment:\nNine states announce back-to-school sales tax holidays on Apple products, likely boosting consumer demand ahead of the fall season.\nBenzinga:",
      "importance_score": 17,
      "entity_count": 5,
      "financial_keyword_count": 1,
      "money_count": 0,
      "company_count": 1,
      "sentiment": "neutral"
    },
    {
      "text": "Fund manager calls to rotate out of Apple, citing stagnant iPhone demand, sketchy AI strategy and tariff-related supply risks.",
      "importance_score": 17,
      "entity_count": 2,
      "financial_keyword_count": 3,
      "money_count": 0,
      "company_count": 1,
      "sentiment": "neutral"
    },
    {
      "text": "BusinessWire: Deadline on August 19th Coming Up in Lawsuit\nPosted 53m ago\nAI Generated.",
      "importance_score": 16,
      "entity_count": 5,
      "financial_keyword_count": 2,
      "money_count": 0,
      "company_count": 0,
      "sentiment": "neutral"
    },
    {
      "text": "Analyst warns Apple is “unprepared for something transformational”, questioning its innovation roadmap.",
      "importance_score": 15,
      "entity_count": 1,
      "financial_keyword_count": 3,
      "money_count": 0,
      "company_count": 1,
      "sentiment": "neutral"
    }
  ],
  "entity_statistics": {
    "total_entities": 42,
    "unique_entities": 24,
    "type_counts": {
      "ORG": 25,
      "MONEY": 2,
      "GPE": 2,
      "PRODUCT": 4,
      "CARDINAL": 1,
      "DATE": 4,
      "WORK_OF_ART": 2,
      "PERSON": 2
    },
    "type_distribution": {
      "ORG": 0.5952380952380952,
      "MONEY": 0.047619047619047616,
      "GPE": 0.047619047619047616,
      "PRODUCT": 0.09523809523809523,
      "CARDINAL": 0.023809523809523808,
      "DATE": 0.09523809523809523,
      "WORK_OF_ART": 0.047619047619047616,
      "PERSON": 0.047619047619047616
    },
    "most_common_entities": [
      [
        "Apple",
        12
      ],
      [
        "AAPL",
        2
      ],
      [
        "$500 million",
        2
      ],
      [
        "MP Materials",
        2
      ],
      [
        "BloFin",
        2
      ],
      [
        "Apple Pay",
        2
      ],
      [
        "Cyberpunk 2077",
        2
      ],
      [
        "Mac",
        2
      ],
      [
        "Apple Inc.",
        1
      ],
      [
        "U.S.-based",
        1
      ]
    ],
    "entity_types_found": [
      "ORG",
      "MONEY",
      "GPE",
      "PRODUCT",
      "CARDINAL",
      "DATE",
      "WORK_OF_ART",
      "PERSON"
    ],
    "company_entities": 25,
    "person_entities": 2,
    "financial_entities": 2,
    "entity_density": 0.14046822742474915
  },
  "financial_analysis": {
    "money_amounts": [
      "$500 million",
      "$500 million"
    ],
    "percentages": [],
    "companies": [
      "Apple Inc.",
      "AAPL",
      "Apple",
      "MP Materials",
      "Reuters",
      "Apple",
      "MP Materials",
      "BloFin",
      "Apple",
      "BloFin",
      "Apple Pay",
      "Apple",
      "Apple",
      "Apple",
      "The Verge:",
      "Apple",
      "MarketBeat",
      "Apple",
      "Tesla",
      "Apple",
      "Apple",
      "AAPL",
      "Apple",
      "Benzinga",
      "Apple"
    ],
    "people": [
      "Jim Cramer",
      "Cramer"
    ],
    "dates": [
      "the fall season",
      "July 17th",
      "August 19th",
      "53m ago"
    ],
    "financial_terms": [
      "Stock",
      "stock"
    ],
    "financial_metrics": [],
    "market_indicators": [
      "Rating"
    ]
  },
  "temporal_analysis": {
    "dates": [
      "the fall season",
      "July 17th",
      "August 19th",
      "53m ago"
    ],
    "time_expressions": [],
    "temporal_relationships": [
      "upcoming"
    ],
    "quarters": [],
    "years": [],
    "time_periods": []
  },
  "sentiment_analysis": {
    "positive_words": 5,
    "negative_words": 5,
    "positive_ratio": 0.016722408026755852,
    "negative_ratio": 0.016722408026755852,
    "sentiment_score": 0.0,
    "sentiment_label": "neutral",
    "sentiment_strength": 0.0,
    "confidence": 0.0
  },
  "industry_analysis": {
    "dominant_industry": "tech",
    "industry_scores": {
      "tech": 3,
      "finance": 1,
      "healthcare": 0,
      "energy": 0,
      "retail": 1,
      "automotive": 1,
      "media": 2,
      "industrial": 2,
      "real_estate": 0,
      "telecom": 0,
      "food_beverage": 0,
      "travel": 0,
      "education": 3,
      "professional": 3,
      "mining": 1,
      "aerospace": 0,
      "environmental": 0,
      "cannabis": 0
    },
    "confidence": 0.17647058823529413
  },
  "market_analysis": {
    "market_sentiment": "bearish",
    "bullish_indicators": 0,
    "bearish_indicators": 1,
    "market_conditions": {
      "volatility": "normal",
      "volume": "normal",
      "trend": "bearish"
    },
    "trading_activity": "normal"
  },
  "competitor_analysis": {
    "companies_mentioned": [
      "Apple Inc.",
      "AAPL",
      "Apple",
      "MP Materials",
      "Reuters",
      "Apple",
      "MP Materials",
      "BloFin",
      "Apple",
      "BloFin",
      "Apple Pay",
      "Apple",
      "Apple",
      "Apple",
      "The Verge:",
      "Apple",
      "MarketBeat",
      "Apple",
      "Tesla",
      "Apple",
      "Apple",
      "AAPL",
      "Apple",
      "Benzinga",
      "Apple"
    ],
    "competitive_context": [],
    "competitor_count": 25,
    "has_competitive_language": false
  },
  "risk_analysis": {
    "risk_sentences": [
      "Fund manager calls to rotate out of Apple, citing stagnant iPhone demand, sketchy AI strategy and tariff-related supply risks."
    ],
    "risk_count": 1,
    "risk_level": "low"
  },
  "opportunity_analysis": {
    "opportunity_sentences": [
      "Apple Inc. (AAPL) shares are moving on a mix of strategic supply-chain partnerships, ecosystem expansions and back-to-school incentives, while sell-side rotation calls and legal overhang temper investor enthusiasm.",
      "Analyst warns Apple is “unprepared for something transformational”, questioning its innovation roadmap."
    ],
    "opportunity_count": 2,
    "opportunity_level": "medium"
  },
  "processing_metadata": {
    "timestamp": "2025-07-17T04:40:11.082489",
    "model_used": "en_core_web_trf",
    "text_length": 2112
  }
}