{
  "ticker": "AMD",
  "entities": [
    {
      "text": "Advanced Micro Devices, Inc.",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 0,
      "end": 28,
      "sentence": "Advanced Micro Devices, Inc. (NASDAQ:AMD) shares are moving on a mix of analyst updates, institutional activity, and insider transactions.",
      "context": "Advanced Micro Devices, Inc. (NASDAQ:AMD) shares are moving on a mix of analys",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "AMD",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 37,
      "end": 40,
      "sentence": "Advanced Micro Devices, Inc. (NASDAQ:AMD) shares are moving on a mix of analyst updates, institutional activity, and insider transactions.",
      "context": "Advanced Micro Devices, Inc. (NASDAQ:AMD) shares are moving on a mix of analyst updates, i",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Citigroup",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 195,
      "end": 204,
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "context": "what investors need to know:\nPositive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "AMD",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 234,
      "end": 237,
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "context": "Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confi",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "165.00",
      "label": "MONEY",
      "start": 242,
      "end": 248,
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "context": "t:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in th",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": true
    },
    {
      "text": "145.00",
      "label": "MONEY",
      "start": 255,
      "end": 261,
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "context": "boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s o",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": true
    },
    {
      "text": "Advanced Micro Devices",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 319,
      "end": 341,
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "context": "ting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Far",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Wells Fargo",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 382,
      "end": 393,
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "context": "o Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased i",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "AMD",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 462,
      "end": 465,
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "context": "rweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center G",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "185",
      "label": "MONEY",
      "start": 477,
      "end": 480,
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "context": "and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.\nAMD",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": true
    },
    {
      "text": "AMD",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 526,
      "end": 529,
      "sentence": "AMD Price Target Hike\nPositive Sentiment:\nCathie Wood’s ARK Invest made significant new allocations to AMD stock as part of its AI and robotics bets, signaling strong institutional interest.",
      "context": "$185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.\nAMD Price Target Hike\nPositive Sentiment:\nCathie Wood",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Cathie Wood’s",
      "label": "PERSON",
      "start": 568,
      "end": 581,
      "sentence": "AMD Price Target Hike\nPositive Sentiment:\nCathie Wood’s ARK Invest made significant new allocations to AMD stock as part of its AI and robotics bets, signaling strong institutional interest.",
      "context": "growth.\nAMD Price Target Hike\nPositive Sentiment:\nCathie Wood’s ARK Invest made significant new allocations to AM",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": true,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "ARK Invest",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 582,
      "end": 592,
      "sentence": "AMD Price Target Hike\nPositive Sentiment:\nCathie Wood’s ARK Invest made significant new allocations to AMD stock as part of its AI and robotics bets, signaling strong institutional interest.",
      "context": "ice Target Hike\nPositive Sentiment:\nCathie Wood’s ARK Invest made significant new allocations to AMD stock as",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "AMD",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 629,
      "end": 632,
      "sentence": "AMD Price Target Hike\nPositive Sentiment:\nCathie Wood’s ARK Invest made significant new allocations to AMD stock as part of its AI and robotics bets, signaling strong institutional interest.",
      "context": "’s ARK Invest made significant new allocations to AMD stock as part of its AI and robotics bets, signal",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Cathie Wood’s",
      "label": "PERSON",
      "start": 717,
      "end": 730,
      "sentence": "Cathie Wood’s AI & Robotics Bets\nPositive Sentiment:\nEvercore noted that AMD’s MI308X chip is set to resume sales in China, which could drive revenue upside in 2025.",
      "context": "cs bets, signaling strong institutional interest.\nCathie Wood’s AI & Robotics Bets\nPositive Sentiment:\nEvercore n",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": true,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Evercore",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 770,
      "end": 778,
      "sentence": "Cathie Wood’s AI & Robotics Bets\nPositive Sentiment:\nEvercore noted that AMD’s MI308X chip is set to resume sales in China, which could drive revenue upside in 2025.",
      "context": "hie Wood’s AI & Robotics Bets\nPositive Sentiment:\nEvercore noted that AMD’s MI308X chip is set to resume sal",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "AMD",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 790,
      "end": 793,
      "sentence": "Cathie Wood’s AI & Robotics Bets\nPositive Sentiment:\nEvercore noted that AMD’s MI308X chip is set to resume sales in China, which could drive revenue upside in 2025.",
      "context": "tics Bets\nPositive Sentiment:\nEvercore noted that AMD’s MI308X chip is set to resume sales in China, wh",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "MI308X",
      "label": "PRODUCT",
      "start": 796,
      "end": 802,
      "sentence": "Cathie Wood’s AI & Robotics Bets\nPositive Sentiment:\nEvercore noted that AMD’s MI308X chip is set to resume sales in China, which could drive revenue upside in 2025.",
      "context": "ets\nPositive Sentiment:\nEvercore noted that AMD’s MI308X chip is set to resume sales in China, which could",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "China",
      "label": "GPE",
      "start": 834,
      "end": 839,
      "sentence": "Cathie Wood’s AI & Robotics Bets\nPositive Sentiment:\nEvercore noted that AMD’s MI308X chip is set to resume sales in China, which could drive revenue upside in 2025.",
      "context": "that AMD’s MI308X chip is set to resume sales in China, which could drive revenue upside in 2025.\nAMD Re",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": true,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "2025",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 877,
      "end": 881,
      "sentence": "Cathie Wood’s AI & Robotics Bets\nPositive Sentiment:\nEvercore noted that AMD’s MI308X chip is set to resume sales in China, which could drive revenue upside in 2025.",
      "context": "les in China, which could drive revenue upside in 2025.\nAMD Revenue Upside from China Sales\nPositive Sen",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "AMD",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 883,
      "end": 886,
      "sentence": "AMD Revenue Upside from China Sales\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "context": "China, which could drive revenue upside in 2025.\nAMD Revenue Upside from China Sales\nPositive Sentimen",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "China",
      "label": "GPE",
      "start": 907,
      "end": 912,
      "sentence": "AMD Revenue Upside from China Sales\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "context": "e revenue upside in 2025.\nAMD Revenue Upside from China Sales\nPositive Sentiment:\nJefferies forecast stro",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": true,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Jefferies",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 939,
      "end": 948,
      "sentence": "Jefferies forecast strong price appreciation for AMD shares, reinforcing a bullish outlook on the chipmaker.",
      "context": "venue Upside from China Sales\nPositive Sentiment:\nJefferies forecast strong price appreciation for AMD shares",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "AMD",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 988,
      "end": 991,
      "sentence": "Jefferies forecast strong price appreciation for AMD shares, reinforcing a bullish outlook on the chipmaker.",
      "context": "Jefferies forecast strong price appreciation for AMD shares, reinforcing a bullish outlook on the chip",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Jefferies",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1048,
      "end": 1057,
      "sentence": "Jefferies Forecast on AMD\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "context": ", reinforcing a bullish outlook on the chipmaker.\nJefferies Forecast on AMD\nPositive Sentiment:\nMarketBeat’s",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Week in Review",
      "label": "EVENT",
      "start": 1107,
      "end": 1121,
      "sentence": "MarketBeat’s Week in Review highlighted a technical indicator suggesting AMD stock is poised for a breakout, fueling momentum-driven buying.",
      "context": "Forecast on AMD\nPositive Sentiment:\nMarketBeat’s Week in Review highlighted a technical indicator suggesting AMD",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "AMD",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1167,
      "end": 1170,
      "sentence": "MarketBeat’s Week in Review highlighted a technical indicator suggesting AMD stock is poised for a breakout, fueling momentum-driven buying.",
      "context": "view highlighted a technical indicator suggesting AMD stock is poised for a breakout, fueling momentum-",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "AMD",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1235,
      "end": 1238,
      "sentence": "AMD Technical Breakout Signal\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "context": "d for a breakout, fueling momentum-driven buying.\nAMD Technical Breakout Signal\nNeutral Sentiment:\nCiti",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Citigroup",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1284,
      "end": 1293,
      "sentence": "Citigroup maintained a “neutral” rating on AMD despite raising its target price, indicating balanced risk-reward expectations.\nBenzinga:",
      "context": "AMD Technical Breakout Signal\nNeutral Sentiment:\nCitigroup maintained a “neutral” rating on AMD despite rais",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "AMD",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1327,
      "end": 1330,
      "sentence": "Citigroup maintained a “neutral” rating on AMD despite raising its target price, indicating balanced risk-reward expectations.\nBenzinga:",
      "context": "iment:\nCitigroup maintained a “neutral” rating on AMD despite raising its target price, indicating bala",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Citi",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1421,
      "end": 1425,
      "sentence": "Citi",
      "context": "ting balanced risk-reward expectations.\nBenzinga: Citi Neutral Rating\nNegative Sentiment:\nShares dipped",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "AMD",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1494,
      "end": 1497,
      "sentence": "Shares dipped after reports that AMD insiders, including EVP Mark Papermaster, sold shares worth $2.8 million, suggesting profit-taking at the executive level.",
      "context": "ative Sentiment:\nShares dipped after reports that AMD insiders, including EVP Mark Papermaster, sold sh",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Mark Papermaster",
      "label": "PERSON",
      "start": 1522,
      "end": 1538,
      "sentence": "Shares dipped after reports that AMD insiders, including EVP Mark Papermaster, sold shares worth $2.8 million, suggesting profit-taking at the executive level.",
      "context": "ed after reports that AMD insiders, including EVP Mark Papermaster, sold shares worth $2.8 million, suggesting profi",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": true,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "$2.8 million",
      "label": "MONEY",
      "start": 1558,
      "end": 1570,
      "sentence": "Shares dipped after reports that AMD insiders, including EVP Mark Papermaster, sold shares worth $2.8 million, suggesting profit-taking at the executive level.",
      "context": "including EVP Mark Papermaster, sold shares worth $2.8 million, suggesting profit-taking at the executive level.",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": true
    },
    {
      "text": "AMD",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1664,
      "end": 1667,
      "sentence": "AMD shares traded down following the disclosure of insider selling, with a 2.4% drop attributed to market reaction to the executives’ stock sales.",
      "context": "level.\nInsider Selling Report\nNegative Sentiment:\nAMD shares traded down following the disclosure of in",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "2.4%",
      "label": "PERCENT",
      "start": 1739,
      "end": 1743,
      "sentence": "AMD shares traded down following the disclosure of insider selling, with a 2.4% drop attributed to market reaction to the executives’ stock sales.",
      "context": "llowing the disclosure of insider selling, with a 2.4% drop attributed to market reaction to the executi",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": true
    },
    {
      "text": "1+ days ago",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 1853,
      "end": 1864,
      "sentence": "Trading Down After Insider Selling\nPosted 1+ days ago\nAI Generated.",
      "context": "sales.\nTrading Down After Insider Selling\nPosted 1+ days ago\nAI Generated. May Contain Errors.",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "AI",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1865,
      "end": 1867,
      "sentence": "Trading Down After Insider Selling\nPosted 1+ days ago\nAI Generated.",
      "context": "ing Down After Insider Selling\nPosted 1+ days ago\nAI Generated. May Contain Errors.",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    }
  ],
  "relationships": [
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Citigroup",
      "verb": "boosted",
      "object": "target",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "importance": 19
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Fargo",
      "verb": "reiterated",
      "object": "rating",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "importance": 19
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Invest",
      "verb": "made",
      "object": "allocations",
      "sentence": "AMD Price Target Hike\nPositive Sentiment:\nCathie Wood’s ARK Invest made significant new allocations to AMD stock as part of its AI and robotics bets, signaling strong institutional interest.",
      "importance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "which",
      "verb": "drive",
      "object": "upside",
      "sentence": "Cathie Wood’s AI & Robotics Bets\nPositive Sentiment:\nEvercore noted that AMD’s MI308X chip is set to resume sales in China, which could drive revenue upside in 2025.",
      "importance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Jefferies",
      "verb": "forecast",
      "object": "appreciation",
      "sentence": "Jefferies forecast strong price appreciation for AMD shares, reinforcing a bullish outlook on the chipmaker.",
      "importance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Week",
      "verb": "highlighted",
      "object": "indicator",
      "sentence": "MarketBeat’s Week in Review highlighted a technical indicator suggesting AMD stock is poised for a breakout, fueling momentum-driven buying.",
      "importance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Citigroup",
      "verb": "maintained",
      "object": "rating",
      "sentence": "Citigroup maintained a “neutral” rating on AMD despite raising its target price, indicating balanced risk-reward expectations.\nBenzinga:",
      "importance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "insiders",
      "verb": "sold",
      "object": "shares",
      "sentence": "Shares dipped after reports that AMD insiders, including EVP Mark Papermaster, sold shares worth $2.8 million, suggesting profit-taking at the executive level.",
      "importance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Advanced",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Micro",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Advanced Micro Devices, Inc. (NASDAQ:AMD) shares are moving on a mix of analyst updates, institutional activity, and insider transactions.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Advanced",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Devices",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Advanced Micro Devices, Inc. (NASDAQ:AMD) shares are moving on a mix of analyst updates, institutional activity, and insider transactions.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Advanced",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": ",",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Advanced Micro Devices, Inc. (NASDAQ:AMD) shares are moving on a mix of analyst updates, institutional activity, and insider transactions.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Advanced",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Inc.",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Advanced Micro Devices, Inc. (NASDAQ:AMD) shares are moving on a mix of analyst updates, institutional activity, and insider transactions.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Advanced",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "AMD",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Advanced Micro Devices, Inc. (NASDAQ:AMD) shares are moving on a mix of analyst updates, institutional activity, and insider transactions.",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Micro",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Devices",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Advanced Micro Devices, Inc. (NASDAQ:AMD) shares are moving on a mix of analyst updates, institutional activity, and insider transactions.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Micro",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": ",",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Advanced Micro Devices, Inc. (NASDAQ:AMD) shares are moving on a mix of analyst updates, institutional activity, and insider transactions.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Micro",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Inc.",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Advanced Micro Devices, Inc. (NASDAQ:AMD) shares are moving on a mix of analyst updates, institutional activity, and insider transactions.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Micro",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "AMD",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Advanced Micro Devices, Inc. (NASDAQ:AMD) shares are moving on a mix of analyst updates, institutional activity, and insider transactions.",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Devices",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": ",",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Advanced Micro Devices, Inc. (NASDAQ:AMD) shares are moving on a mix of analyst updates, institutional activity, and insider transactions.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Devices",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Inc.",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Advanced Micro Devices, Inc. (NASDAQ:AMD) shares are moving on a mix of analyst updates, institutional activity, and insider transactions.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Devices",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "AMD",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Advanced Micro Devices, Inc. (NASDAQ:AMD) shares are moving on a mix of analyst updates, institutional activity, and insider transactions.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": ",",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Inc.",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Advanced Micro Devices, Inc. (NASDAQ:AMD) shares are moving on a mix of analyst updates, institutional activity, and insider transactions.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": ",",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "AMD",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Advanced Micro Devices, Inc. (NASDAQ:AMD) shares are moving on a mix of analyst updates, institutional activity, and insider transactions.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Inc.",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "AMD",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Advanced Micro Devices, Inc. (NASDAQ:AMD) shares are moving on a mix of analyst updates, institutional activity, and insider transactions.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Citigroup",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "AMD",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Citigroup",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "165.00",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Citigroup",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "145.00",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Citigroup",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Advanced",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 24
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Citigroup",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Micro",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 25
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Citigroup",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Devices",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 26
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Citigroup",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Wells",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 35
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Citigroup",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Fargo",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 36
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Citigroup",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "AMD",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 49
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Citigroup",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "185",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 53
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "AMD",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "165.00",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "AMD",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "145.00",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "AMD",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Advanced",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 18
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "AMD",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Micro",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 19
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "AMD",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Devices",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 20
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "AMD",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Wells",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 29
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "AMD",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Fargo",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 30
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "AMD",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "AMD",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 43
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "AMD",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "185",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 47
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "165.00",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "145.00",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "165.00",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "Advanced",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 15
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "165.00",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "Micro",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 16
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "165.00",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "Devices",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 17
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "165.00",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "Wells",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 26
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "165.00",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "Fargo",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 27
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "165.00",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "AMD",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 40
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "165.00",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "185",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 44
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "145.00",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "Advanced",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "145.00",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "Micro",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 13
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "145.00",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "Devices",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 14
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "145.00",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "Wells",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 23
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "145.00",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "Fargo",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 24
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "145.00",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "AMD",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 37
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "145.00",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "185",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 41
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Advanced",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Micro",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Advanced",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Devices",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Advanced",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Wells",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Advanced",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Fargo",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Advanced",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "AMD",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 25
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Advanced",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "185",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 29
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Micro",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Devices",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Micro",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Wells",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Micro",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Fargo",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Micro",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "AMD",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 24
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Micro",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "185",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 28
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Devices",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Wells",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Devices",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Fargo",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Devices",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "AMD",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 23
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Devices",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "185",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 27
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Wells",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Fargo",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Wells",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "AMD",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 14
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Wells",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "185",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 18
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Fargo",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "AMD",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 13
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Fargo",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "185",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 17
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "AMD",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "185",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "AMD",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Cathie",
      "entity2_type": "PERSON",
      "sentence": "AMD Price Target Hike\nPositive Sentiment:\nCathie Wood’s ARK Invest made significant new allocations to AMD stock as part of its AI and robotics bets, signaling strong institutional interest.",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "AMD",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Wood",
      "entity2_type": "PERSON",
      "sentence": "AMD Price Target Hike\nPositive Sentiment:\nCathie Wood’s ARK Invest made significant new allocations to AMD stock as part of its AI and robotics bets, signaling strong institutional interest.",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "AMD",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "’s",
      "entity2_type": "PERSON",
      "sentence": "AMD Price Target Hike\nPositive Sentiment:\nCathie Wood’s ARK Invest made significant new allocations to AMD stock as part of its AI and robotics bets, signaling strong institutional interest.",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "AMD",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "ARK",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "AMD Price Target Hike\nPositive Sentiment:\nCathie Wood’s ARK Invest made significant new allocations to AMD stock as part of its AI and robotics bets, signaling strong institutional interest.",
      "distance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "AMD",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Invest",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "AMD Price Target Hike\nPositive Sentiment:\nCathie Wood’s ARK Invest made significant new allocations to AMD stock as part of its AI and robotics bets, signaling strong institutional interest.",
      "distance": 13
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "AMD",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "AMD",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "AMD Price Target Hike\nPositive Sentiment:\nCathie Wood’s ARK Invest made significant new allocations to AMD stock as part of its AI and robotics bets, signaling strong institutional interest.",
      "distance": 19
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Cathie",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "Wood",
      "entity2_type": "PERSON",
      "sentence": "AMD Price Target Hike\nPositive Sentiment:\nCathie Wood’s ARK Invest made significant new allocations to AMD stock as part of its AI and robotics bets, signaling strong institutional interest.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Cathie",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "’s",
      "entity2_type": "PERSON",
      "sentence": "AMD Price Target Hike\nPositive Sentiment:\nCathie Wood’s ARK Invest made significant new allocations to AMD stock as part of its AI and robotics bets, signaling strong institutional interest.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Cathie",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "ARK",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "AMD Price Target Hike\nPositive Sentiment:\nCathie Wood’s ARK Invest made significant new allocations to AMD stock as part of its AI and robotics bets, signaling strong institutional interest.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Cathie",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "Invest",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "AMD Price Target Hike\nPositive Sentiment:\nCathie Wood’s ARK Invest made significant new allocations to AMD stock as part of its AI and robotics bets, signaling strong institutional interest.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Cathie",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "AMD",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "AMD Price Target Hike\nPositive Sentiment:\nCathie Wood’s ARK Invest made significant new allocations to AMD stock as part of its AI and robotics bets, signaling strong institutional interest.",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Wood",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "’s",
      "entity2_type": "PERSON",
      "sentence": "AMD Price Target Hike\nPositive Sentiment:\nCathie Wood’s ARK Invest made significant new allocations to AMD stock as part of its AI and robotics bets, signaling strong institutional interest.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Wood",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "ARK",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "AMD Price Target Hike\nPositive Sentiment:\nCathie Wood’s ARK Invest made significant new allocations to AMD stock as part of its AI and robotics bets, signaling strong institutional interest.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Wood",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "Invest",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "AMD Price Target Hike\nPositive Sentiment:\nCathie Wood’s ARK Invest made significant new allocations to AMD stock as part of its AI and robotics bets, signaling strong institutional interest.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Wood",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "AMD",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "AMD Price Target Hike\nPositive Sentiment:\nCathie Wood’s ARK Invest made significant new allocations to AMD stock as part of its AI and robotics bets, signaling strong institutional interest.",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "’s",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "ARK",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "AMD Price Target Hike\nPositive Sentiment:\nCathie Wood’s ARK Invest made significant new allocations to AMD stock as part of its AI and robotics bets, signaling strong institutional interest.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "’s",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "Invest",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "AMD Price Target Hike\nPositive Sentiment:\nCathie Wood’s ARK Invest made significant new allocations to AMD stock as part of its AI and robotics bets, signaling strong institutional interest.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "’s",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "AMD",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "AMD Price Target Hike\nPositive Sentiment:\nCathie Wood’s ARK Invest made significant new allocations to AMD stock as part of its AI and robotics bets, signaling strong institutional interest.",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "ARK",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Invest",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "AMD Price Target Hike\nPositive Sentiment:\nCathie Wood’s ARK Invest made significant new allocations to AMD stock as part of its AI and robotics bets, signaling strong institutional interest.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "ARK",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "AMD",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "AMD Price Target Hike\nPositive Sentiment:\nCathie Wood’s ARK Invest made significant new allocations to AMD stock as part of its AI and robotics bets, signaling strong institutional interest.",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Invest",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "AMD",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "AMD Price Target Hike\nPositive Sentiment:\nCathie Wood’s ARK Invest made significant new allocations to AMD stock as part of its AI and robotics bets, signaling strong institutional interest.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Cathie",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "Wood",
      "entity2_type": "PERSON",
      "sentence": "Cathie Wood’s AI & Robotics Bets\nPositive Sentiment:\nEvercore noted that AMD’s MI308X chip is set to resume sales in China, which could drive revenue upside in 2025.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Cathie",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "’s",
      "entity2_type": "PERSON",
      "sentence": "Cathie Wood’s AI & Robotics Bets\nPositive Sentiment:\nEvercore noted that AMD’s MI308X chip is set to resume sales in China, which could drive revenue upside in 2025.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Cathie",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "Evercore",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Cathie Wood’s AI & Robotics Bets\nPositive Sentiment:\nEvercore noted that AMD’s MI308X chip is set to resume sales in China, which could drive revenue upside in 2025.",
      "distance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Cathie",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "AMD",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Cathie Wood’s AI & Robotics Bets\nPositive Sentiment:\nEvercore noted that AMD’s MI308X chip is set to resume sales in China, which could drive revenue upside in 2025.",
      "distance": 15
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Cathie",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "MI308X",
      "entity2_type": "PRODUCT",
      "sentence": "Cathie Wood’s AI & Robotics Bets\nPositive Sentiment:\nEvercore noted that AMD’s MI308X chip is set to resume sales in China, which could drive revenue upside in 2025.",
      "distance": 17
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Cathie",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "China",
      "entity2_type": "GPE",
      "sentence": "Cathie Wood’s AI & Robotics Bets\nPositive Sentiment:\nEvercore noted that AMD’s MI308X chip is set to resume sales in China, which could drive revenue upside in 2025.",
      "distance": 25
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Cathie",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "2025",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Cathie Wood’s AI & Robotics Bets\nPositive Sentiment:\nEvercore noted that AMD’s MI308X chip is set to resume sales in China, which could drive revenue upside in 2025.",
      "distance": 33
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Wood",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "’s",
      "entity2_type": "PERSON",
      "sentence": "Cathie Wood’s AI & Robotics Bets\nPositive Sentiment:\nEvercore noted that AMD’s MI308X chip is set to resume sales in China, which could drive revenue upside in 2025.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Wood",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "Evercore",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Cathie Wood’s AI & Robotics Bets\nPositive Sentiment:\nEvercore noted that AMD’s MI308X chip is set to resume sales in China, which could drive revenue upside in 2025.",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Wood",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "AMD",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Cathie Wood’s AI & Robotics Bets\nPositive Sentiment:\nEvercore noted that AMD’s MI308X chip is set to resume sales in China, which could drive revenue upside in 2025.",
      "distance": 14
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Wood",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "MI308X",
      "entity2_type": "PRODUCT",
      "sentence": "Cathie Wood’s AI & Robotics Bets\nPositive Sentiment:\nEvercore noted that AMD’s MI308X chip is set to resume sales in China, which could drive revenue upside in 2025.",
      "distance": 16
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Wood",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "China",
      "entity2_type": "GPE",
      "sentence": "Cathie Wood’s AI & Robotics Bets\nPositive Sentiment:\nEvercore noted that AMD’s MI308X chip is set to resume sales in China, which could drive revenue upside in 2025.",
      "distance": 24
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Wood",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "2025",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Cathie Wood’s AI & Robotics Bets\nPositive Sentiment:\nEvercore noted that AMD’s MI308X chip is set to resume sales in China, which could drive revenue upside in 2025.",
      "distance": 32
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "’s",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "Evercore",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Cathie Wood’s AI & Robotics Bets\nPositive Sentiment:\nEvercore noted that AMD’s MI308X chip is set to resume sales in China, which could drive revenue upside in 2025.",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "’s",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "AMD",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Cathie Wood’s AI & Robotics Bets\nPositive Sentiment:\nEvercore noted that AMD’s MI308X chip is set to resume sales in China, which could drive revenue upside in 2025.",
      "distance": 13
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "’s",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "MI308X",
      "entity2_type": "PRODUCT",
      "sentence": "Cathie Wood’s AI & Robotics Bets\nPositive Sentiment:\nEvercore noted that AMD’s MI308X chip is set to resume sales in China, which could drive revenue upside in 2025.",
      "distance": 15
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "’s",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "China",
      "entity2_type": "GPE",
      "sentence": "Cathie Wood’s AI & Robotics Bets\nPositive Sentiment:\nEvercore noted that AMD’s MI308X chip is set to resume sales in China, which could drive revenue upside in 2025.",
      "distance": 23
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "’s",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "2025",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Cathie Wood’s AI & Robotics Bets\nPositive Sentiment:\nEvercore noted that AMD’s MI308X chip is set to resume sales in China, which could drive revenue upside in 2025.",
      "distance": 31
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Evercore",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "AMD",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Cathie Wood’s AI & Robotics Bets\nPositive Sentiment:\nEvercore noted that AMD’s MI308X chip is set to resume sales in China, which could drive revenue upside in 2025.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Evercore",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "MI308X",
      "entity2_type": "PRODUCT",
      "sentence": "Cathie Wood’s AI & Robotics Bets\nPositive Sentiment:\nEvercore noted that AMD’s MI308X chip is set to resume sales in China, which could drive revenue upside in 2025.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Evercore",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "China",
      "entity2_type": "GPE",
      "sentence": "Cathie Wood’s AI & Robotics Bets\nPositive Sentiment:\nEvercore noted that AMD’s MI308X chip is set to resume sales in China, which could drive revenue upside in 2025.",
      "distance": 13
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Evercore",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "2025",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Cathie Wood’s AI & Robotics Bets\nPositive Sentiment:\nEvercore noted that AMD’s MI308X chip is set to resume sales in China, which could drive revenue upside in 2025.",
      "distance": 21
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "AMD",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "MI308X",
      "entity2_type": "PRODUCT",
      "sentence": "Cathie Wood’s AI & Robotics Bets\nPositive Sentiment:\nEvercore noted that AMD’s MI308X chip is set to resume sales in China, which could drive revenue upside in 2025.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "AMD",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "China",
      "entity2_type": "GPE",
      "sentence": "Cathie Wood’s AI & Robotics Bets\nPositive Sentiment:\nEvercore noted that AMD’s MI308X chip is set to resume sales in China, which could drive revenue upside in 2025.",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "AMD",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "2025",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Cathie Wood’s AI & Robotics Bets\nPositive Sentiment:\nEvercore noted that AMD’s MI308X chip is set to resume sales in China, which could drive revenue upside in 2025.",
      "distance": 18
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "MI308X",
      "entity1_type": "PRODUCT",
      "entity2": "China",
      "entity2_type": "GPE",
      "sentence": "Cathie Wood’s AI & Robotics Bets\nPositive Sentiment:\nEvercore noted that AMD’s MI308X chip is set to resume sales in China, which could drive revenue upside in 2025.",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "MI308X",
      "entity1_type": "PRODUCT",
      "entity2": "2025",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Cathie Wood’s AI & Robotics Bets\nPositive Sentiment:\nEvercore noted that AMD’s MI308X chip is set to resume sales in China, which could drive revenue upside in 2025.",
      "distance": 16
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "China",
      "entity1_type": "GPE",
      "entity2": "2025",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Cathie Wood’s AI & Robotics Bets\nPositive Sentiment:\nEvercore noted that AMD’s MI308X chip is set to resume sales in China, which could drive revenue upside in 2025.",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "AMD",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "China",
      "entity2_type": "GPE",
      "sentence": "AMD Revenue Upside from China Sales\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Jefferies",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "AMD",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Jefferies forecast strong price appreciation for AMD shares, reinforcing a bullish outlook on the chipmaker.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Week",
      "entity1_type": "EVENT",
      "entity2": "in",
      "entity2_type": "EVENT",
      "sentence": "MarketBeat’s Week in Review highlighted a technical indicator suggesting AMD stock is poised for a breakout, fueling momentum-driven buying.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Week",
      "entity1_type": "EVENT",
      "entity2": "Review",
      "entity2_type": "EVENT",
      "sentence": "MarketBeat’s Week in Review highlighted a technical indicator suggesting AMD stock is poised for a breakout, fueling momentum-driven buying.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Week",
      "entity1_type": "EVENT",
      "entity2": "AMD",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "MarketBeat’s Week in Review highlighted a technical indicator suggesting AMD stock is poised for a breakout, fueling momentum-driven buying.",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "in",
      "entity1_type": "EVENT",
      "entity2": "Review",
      "entity2_type": "EVENT",
      "sentence": "MarketBeat’s Week in Review highlighted a technical indicator suggesting AMD stock is poised for a breakout, fueling momentum-driven buying.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "in",
      "entity1_type": "EVENT",
      "entity2": "AMD",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "MarketBeat’s Week in Review highlighted a technical indicator suggesting AMD stock is poised for a breakout, fueling momentum-driven buying.",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Review",
      "entity1_type": "EVENT",
      "entity2": "AMD",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "MarketBeat’s Week in Review highlighted a technical indicator suggesting AMD stock is poised for a breakout, fueling momentum-driven buying.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Citigroup",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "AMD",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Citigroup maintained a “neutral” rating on AMD despite raising its target price, indicating balanced risk-reward expectations.\nBenzinga:",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "AMD",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Mark",
      "entity2_type": "PERSON",
      "sentence": "Shares dipped after reports that AMD insiders, including EVP Mark Papermaster, sold shares worth $2.8 million, suggesting profit-taking at the executive level.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "AMD",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Papermaster",
      "entity2_type": "PERSON",
      "sentence": "Shares dipped after reports that AMD insiders, including EVP Mark Papermaster, sold shares worth $2.8 million, suggesting profit-taking at the executive level.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "AMD",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "$",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Shares dipped after reports that AMD insiders, including EVP Mark Papermaster, sold shares worth $2.8 million, suggesting profit-taking at the executive level.",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "AMD",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "2.8",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Shares dipped after reports that AMD insiders, including EVP Mark Papermaster, sold shares worth $2.8 million, suggesting profit-taking at the executive level.",
      "distance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "AMD",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "million",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Shares dipped after reports that AMD insiders, including EVP Mark Papermaster, sold shares worth $2.8 million, suggesting profit-taking at the executive level.",
      "distance": 13
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Mark",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "Papermaster",
      "entity2_type": "PERSON",
      "sentence": "Shares dipped after reports that AMD insiders, including EVP Mark Papermaster, sold shares worth $2.8 million, suggesting profit-taking at the executive level.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Mark",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "$",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Shares dipped after reports that AMD insiders, including EVP Mark Papermaster, sold shares worth $2.8 million, suggesting profit-taking at the executive level.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Mark",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "2.8",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Shares dipped after reports that AMD insiders, including EVP Mark Papermaster, sold shares worth $2.8 million, suggesting profit-taking at the executive level.",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Mark",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "million",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Shares dipped after reports that AMD insiders, including EVP Mark Papermaster, sold shares worth $2.8 million, suggesting profit-taking at the executive level.",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Papermaster",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "$",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Shares dipped after reports that AMD insiders, including EVP Mark Papermaster, sold shares worth $2.8 million, suggesting profit-taking at the executive level.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Papermaster",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "2.8",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Shares dipped after reports that AMD insiders, including EVP Mark Papermaster, sold shares worth $2.8 million, suggesting profit-taking at the executive level.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Papermaster",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "million",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Shares dipped after reports that AMD insiders, including EVP Mark Papermaster, sold shares worth $2.8 million, suggesting profit-taking at the executive level.",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "$",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "2.8",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Shares dipped after reports that AMD insiders, including EVP Mark Papermaster, sold shares worth $2.8 million, suggesting profit-taking at the executive level.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "$",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "million",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Shares dipped after reports that AMD insiders, including EVP Mark Papermaster, sold shares worth $2.8 million, suggesting profit-taking at the executive level.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "2.8",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "million",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Shares dipped after reports that AMD insiders, including EVP Mark Papermaster, sold shares worth $2.8 million, suggesting profit-taking at the executive level.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "AMD",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "2.4",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "AMD shares traded down following the disclosure of insider selling, with a 2.4% drop attributed to market reaction to the executives’ stock sales.",
      "distance": 13
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "AMD",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "%",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "AMD shares traded down following the disclosure of insider selling, with a 2.4% drop attributed to market reaction to the executives’ stock sales.",
      "distance": 14
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "2.4",
      "entity1_type": "PERCENT",
      "entity2": "%",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "AMD shares traded down following the disclosure of insider selling, with a 2.4% drop attributed to market reaction to the executives’ stock sales.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "1",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "+",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Trading Down After Insider Selling\nPosted 1+ days ago\nAI Generated.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "1",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "days",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Trading Down After Insider Selling\nPosted 1+ days ago\nAI Generated.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "1",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "ago",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Trading Down After Insider Selling\nPosted 1+ days ago\nAI Generated.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "1",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "AI",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trading Down After Insider Selling\nPosted 1+ days ago\nAI Generated.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "+",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "days",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Trading Down After Insider Selling\nPosted 1+ days ago\nAI Generated.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "+",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "ago",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Trading Down After Insider Selling\nPosted 1+ days ago\nAI Generated.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "+",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "AI",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trading Down After Insider Selling\nPosted 1+ days ago\nAI Generated.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "days",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "ago",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Trading Down After Insider Selling\nPosted 1+ days ago\nAI Generated.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "days",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "AI",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trading Down After Insider Selling\nPosted 1+ days ago\nAI Generated.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "ago",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "AI",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trading Down After Insider Selling\nPosted 1+ days ago\nAI Generated.",
      "distance": 2
    }
  ],
  "key_phrases": [
    {
      "text": "a mix",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "analyst updates",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "institutional activity",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "insider transactions",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "Positive Sentiment",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "its price target",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "analyst confidence",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "the company’s outlook",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "Advanced Micro Devices Price Target",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "Positive Sentiment",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "Wells Fargo",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "an “Overweight” rating",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "its price target",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "AMD shares",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "market_term"
    },
    {
      "text": "accelerating data-center GPU growth",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "trend"
    },
    {
      "text": "AMD Price Target Hike",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "Positive Sentiment",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "Cathie Wood’s ARK Invest",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "significant new allocations",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "AMD stock",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "market_term"
    },
    {
      "text": "its AI and robotics bets",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "strong institutional interest",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "Cathie Wood’s AI & Robotics Bets",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "Positive Sentiment",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "AMD’s MI308X chip",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "revenue upside",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "financial_metric"
    },
    {
      "text": "AMD Revenue Upside",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "financial_metric"
    },
    {
      "text": "China Sales",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "Positive Sentiment",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "strong price appreciation",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "AMD shares",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "market_term"
    },
    {
      "text": "a bullish outlook",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "the chipmaker",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "Jefferies Forecast",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "Positive Sentiment",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "MarketBeat’s Week",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "market_term"
    },
    {
      "text": "a technical indicator",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "AMD stock",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "market_term"
    },
    {
      "text": "a breakout",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "momentum-driven buying",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "AMD Technical Breakout Signal\nNeutral Sentiment",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "a “neutral” rating",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "its target price",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "balanced risk-reward expectations",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "Negative Sentiment",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "AMD insiders",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "EVP Mark Papermaster",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "the executive level",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "Insider Selling",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "Negative Sentiment",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "AMD shares",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "market_term"
    },
    {
      "text": "the disclosure",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "insider selling",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "a 2.4% drop",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "market reaction",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "market_term"
    },
    {
      "text": "the executives’ stock sales",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "market_term"
    },
    {
      "text": "Insider Selling",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "$165.00",
      "type": "pattern",
      "category": "money"
    },
    {
      "text": "$145.00",
      "type": "pattern",
      "category": "money"
    },
    {
      "text": "$185,",
      "type": "pattern",
      "category": "money"
    },
    {
      "text": "$2",
      "type": "pattern",
      "category": "money"
    },
    {
      "text": "2.4%",
      "type": "pattern",
      "category": "percentage"
    },
    {
      "text": "growth",
      "type": "pattern",
      "category": "financial_metric"
    },
    {
      "text": "revenue",
      "type": "pattern",
      "category": "financial_metric"
    },
    {
      "text": "Revenue",
      "type": "pattern",
      "category": "financial_metric"
    },
    {
      "text": "profit",
      "type": "pattern",
      "category": "financial_metric"
    },
    {
      "text": "stock",
      "type": "pattern",
      "category": "market_term"
    },
    {
      "text": "stock",
      "type": "pattern",
      "category": "market_term"
    },
    {
      "text": "market",
      "type": "pattern",
      "category": "market_term"
    },
    {
      "text": "stock",
      "type": "pattern",
      "category": "market_term"
    },
    {
      "text": "Trading",
      "type": "pattern",
      "category": "market_term"
    }
  ],
  "important_sentences": [
    {
      "text": "Positive Sentiment:\nCitigroup boosted its price target for AMD to $165.00 from $145.00, reflecting analyst confidence in the company’s outlook.\nAdvanced Micro Devices Price Target Raised\nPositive Sentiment:\nWells Fargo reiterated an “Overweight” rating and increased its price target on AMD shares to $185, citing accelerating data-center GPU growth.",
      "importance_score": 81,
      "entity_count": 11,
      "financial_keyword_count": 8,
      "money_count": 3,
      "company_count": 5,
      "sentiment": "positive"
    },
    {
      "text": "AMD Price Target Hike\nPositive Sentiment:\nCathie Wood’s ARK Invest made significant new allocations to AMD stock as part of its AI and robotics bets, signaling strong institutional interest.",
      "importance_score": 38,
      "entity_count": 7,
      "financial_keyword_count": 4,
      "money_count": 0,
      "company_count": 3,
      "sentiment": "positive"
    },
    {
      "text": "Cathie Wood’s AI & Robotics Bets\nPositive Sentiment:\nEvercore noted that AMD’s MI308X chip is set to resume sales in China, which could drive revenue upside in 2025.",
      "importance_score": 33,
      "entity_count": 8,
      "financial_keyword_count": 3,
      "money_count": 0,
      "company_count": 2,
      "sentiment": "positive"
    },
    {
      "text": "Shares dipped after reports that AMD insiders, including EVP Mark Papermaster, sold shares worth $2.8 million, suggesting profit-taking at the executive level.",
      "importance_score": 24,
      "entity_count": 6,
      "financial_keyword_count": 1,
      "money_count": 1,
      "company_count": 1,
      "sentiment": "positive"
    },
    {
      "text": "Advanced Micro Devices, Inc. (NASDAQ:AMD) shares are moving on a mix of analyst updates, institutional activity, and insider transactions.",
      "importance_score": 23,
      "entity_count": 6,
      "financial_keyword_count": 1,
      "money_count": 0,
      "company_count": 2,
      "sentiment": "neutral"
    },
    {
      "text": "Citigroup maintained a “neutral” rating on AMD despite raising its target price, indicating balanced risk-reward expectations.\nBenzinga:",
      "importance_score": 21,
      "entity_count": 2,
      "financial_keyword_count": 3,
      "money_count": 0,
      "company_count": 2,
      "sentiment": "neutral"
    },
    {
      "text": "Trading Down After Insider Selling\nPosted 1+ days ago\nAI Generated.",
      "importance_score": 20,
      "entity_count": 5,
      "financial_keyword_count": 2,
      "money_count": 0,
      "company_count": 1,
      "sentiment": "neutral"
    },
    {
      "text": "AMD shares traded down following the disclosure of insider selling, with a 2.4% drop attributed to market reaction to the executives’ stock sales.",
      "importance_score": 19,
      "entity_count": 3,
      "financial_keyword_count": 3,
      "money_count": 0,
      "company_count": 1,
      "sentiment": "negative"
    },
    {
      "text": "Jefferies forecast strong price appreciation for AMD shares, reinforcing a bullish outlook on the chipmaker.",
      "importance_score": 18,
      "entity_count": 2,
      "financial_keyword_count": 2,
      "money_count": 0,
      "company_count": 2,
      "sentiment": "positive"
    },
    {
      "text": "MarketBeat’s Week in Review highlighted a technical indicator suggesting AMD stock is poised for a breakout, fueling momentum-driven buying.",
      "importance_score": 18,
      "entity_count": 4,
