{
  "ticker": "COIN",
  "entities": [
    {
      "text": "Coinbase Global, Inc.",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 0,
      "end": 21,
      "sentence": "Coinbase Global, Inc. (NASDAQ:COIN) saw its shares move today on a mix of regulatory progress, institutional flows, analyst actions and insider transactions.",
      "context": "Coinbase Global, Inc. (NASDAQ:COIN) saw its shares move today on a mix",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "COIN",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 30,
      "end": 34,
      "sentence": "Coinbase Global, Inc. (NASDAQ:COIN) saw its shares move today on a mix of regulatory progress, institutional flows, analyst actions and insider transactions.",
      "context": "Coinbase Global, Inc. (NASDAQ:COIN) saw its shares move today on a mix of regulatory",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "today",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 56,
      "end": 61,
      "sentence": "Coinbase Global, Inc. (NASDAQ:COIN) saw its shares move today on a mix of regulatory progress, institutional flows, analyst actions and insider transactions.",
      "context": "se Global, Inc. (NASDAQ:COIN) saw its shares move today on a mix of regulatory progress, institutional fl",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "52-week",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 195,
      "end": 202,
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nShares hit a new 52-week high as Washington advances bipartisan crypto legislation, lifting investor optimism.",
      "context": "ransactions.\nPositive Sentiment:\nShares hit a new 52-week high as Washington advances bipartisan crypto leg",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Washington",
      "label": "GPE",
      "start": 211,
      "end": 221,
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nShares hit a new 52-week high as Washington advances bipartisan crypto legislation, lifting investor optimism.",
      "context": "itive Sentiment:\nShares hit a new 52-week high as Washington advances bipartisan crypto legislation, lifting i",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": true,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Coinbase Global Stock",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 293,
      "end": 314,
      "sentence": "Why Coinbase Global Stock Hit A New 52-Week High Today\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "context": "rypto legislation, lifting investor optimism.\nWhy Coinbase Global Stock Hit A New 52-Week High Today\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "52-Week",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 325,
      "end": 332,
      "sentence": "Why Coinbase Global Stock Hit A New 52-Week High Today\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "context": "tor optimism.\nWhy Coinbase Global Stock Hit A New 52-Week High Today\nPositive Sentiment:\nBig-money inflows",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Today",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 338,
      "end": 343,
      "sentence": "Why Coinbase Global Stock Hit A New 52-Week High Today\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "context": "Why Coinbase Global Stock Hit A New 52-Week High Today\nPositive Sentiment:\nBig-money inflows accelerate,",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "four",
      "label": "CARDINAL",
      "start": 399,
      "end": 403,
      "sentence": "Big-money inflows accelerate, with four outlier buy signals over two months driving sustained upside in COIN shares.",
      "context": "ive Sentiment:\nBig-money inflows accelerate, with four outlier buy signals over two months driving susta",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "two months",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 429,
      "end": 439,
      "sentence": "Big-money inflows accelerate, with four outlier buy signals over two months driving sustained upside in COIN shares.",
      "context": "ws accelerate, with four outlier buy signals over two months driving sustained upside in COIN shares.\nCoinbase",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "COIN",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 468,
      "end": 472,
      "sentence": "Big-money inflows accelerate, with four outlier buy signals over two months driving sustained upside in COIN shares.",
      "context": "gnals over two months driving sustained upside in COIN shares.\nCoinbase on Fire from Sustained Big Money",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Coinbase",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 481,
      "end": 489,
      "sentence": "Coinbase on Fire from Sustained Big Money Buys\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "context": "o months driving sustained upside in COIN shares.\nCoinbase on Fire from Sustained Big Money Buys\nPositive Se",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "American Banking News",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 572,
      "end": 593,
      "sentence": "An analyst upgrade from American Banking News helped lift COIN nearly 2% after revising its rating higher.",
      "context": "Buys\nPositive Sentiment:\nAn analyst upgrade from American Banking News helped lift COIN nearly 2% after revising its rat",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "COIN",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 606,
      "end": 610,
      "sentence": "An analyst upgrade from American Banking News helped lift COIN nearly 2% after revising its rating higher.",
      "context": "st upgrade from American Banking News helped lift COIN nearly 2% after revising its rating higher.\nCoinb",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "nearly 2%",
      "label": "PERCENT",
      "start": 611,
      "end": 620,
      "sentence": "An analyst upgrade from American Banking News helped lift COIN nearly 2% after revising its rating higher.",
      "context": "grade from American Banking News helped lift COIN nearly 2% after revising its rating higher.\nCoinbase Global",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": true
    },
    {
      "text": "Coinbase Global",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 655,
      "end": 670,
      "sentence": "Coinbase Global (NASDAQ:COIN) Trading 1.9% Higher Following Analyst Upgrade\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "context": "COIN nearly 2% after revising its rating higher.\nCoinbase Global (NASDAQ:COIN) Trading 1.9% Higher Following Analy",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "1.9%",
      "label": "PERCENT",
      "start": 693,
      "end": 697,
      "sentence": "Coinbase Global (NASDAQ:COIN) Trading 1.9% Higher Following Analyst Upgrade\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "context": "ing higher.\nCoinbase Global (NASDAQ:COIN) Trading 1.9% Higher Following Analyst Upgrade\nPositive Sentime",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": true
    },
    {
      "text": "Oppenheimer",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 751,
      "end": 762,
      "sentence": "Oppenheimer raised its price target to $417 and reiterated a Buy rating, citing bullish regulatory outlook.",
      "context": "her Following Analyst Upgrade\nPositive Sentiment:\nOppenheimer raised its price target to $417 and reiterated a",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "417",
      "label": "MONEY",
      "start": 791,
      "end": 794,
      "sentence": "Oppenheimer raised its price target to $417 and reiterated a Buy rating, citing bullish regulatory outlook.",
      "context": "entiment:\nOppenheimer raised its price target to $417 and reiterated a Buy rating, citing bullish regul",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": true
    },
    {
      "text": "Coinbase",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 878,
      "end": 886,
      "sentence": "Top Analyst Raises Coinbase Stock (COIN) Price Target as U.S. Enters ‘Crypto Week’\nPositive Sentiment:\nCalifornia’s “Breakthrough Project” teams Coinbase with Ripple and MoonPay on state-backed crypto initiatives.",
      "context": "ng bullish regulatory outlook.\nTop Analyst Raises Coinbase Stock (COIN) Price Target as U.S. Enters ‘Crypto",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "U.S.",
      "label": "GPE",
      "start": 916,
      "end": 920,
      "sentence": "Top Analyst Raises Coinbase Stock (COIN) Price Target as U.S. Enters ‘Crypto Week’\nPositive Sentiment:\nCalifornia’s “Breakthrough Project” teams Coinbase with Ripple and MoonPay on state-backed crypto initiatives.",
      "context": "lyst Raises Coinbase Stock (COIN) Price Target as U.S. Enters ‘Crypto Week’\nPositive Sentiment:\nCaliforn",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": true,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Crypto Week",
      "label": "EVENT",
      "start": 929,
      "end": 940,
      "sentence": "Top Analyst Raises Coinbase Stock (COIN) Price Target as U.S. Enters ‘Crypto Week’\nPositive Sentiment:\nCalifornia’s “Breakthrough Project” teams Coinbase with Ripple and MoonPay on state-backed crypto initiatives.",
      "context": "oinbase Stock (COIN) Price Target as U.S. Enters ‘Crypto Week’\nPositive Sentiment:\nCalifornia’s “Breakthrough P",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "California",
      "label": "GPE",
      "start": 962,
      "end": 972,
      "sentence": "Top Analyst Raises Coinbase Stock (COIN) Price Target as U.S. Enters ‘Crypto Week’\nPositive Sentiment:\nCalifornia’s “Breakthrough Project” teams Coinbase with Ripple and MoonPay on state-backed crypto initiatives.",
      "context": "as U.S. Enters ‘Crypto Week’\nPositive Sentiment:\nCalifornia’s “Breakthrough Project” teams Coinbase with Ripp",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": true,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Coinbase",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1004,
      "end": 1012,
      "sentence": "Top Analyst Raises Coinbase Stock (COIN) Price Target as U.S. Enters ‘Crypto Week’\nPositive Sentiment:\nCalifornia’s “Breakthrough Project” teams Coinbase with Ripple and MoonPay on state-backed crypto initiatives.",
      "context": "timent:\nCalifornia’s “Breakthrough Project” teams Coinbase with Ripple and MoonPay on state-backed crypto in",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Ripple",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1018,
      "end": 1024,
      "sentence": "Top Analyst Raises Coinbase Stock (COIN) Price Target as U.S. Enters ‘Crypto Week’\nPositive Sentiment:\nCalifornia’s “Breakthrough Project” teams Coinbase with Ripple and MoonPay on state-backed crypto initiatives.",
      "context": "rnia’s “Breakthrough Project” teams Coinbase with Ripple and MoonPay on state-backed crypto initiatives.\nC",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "MoonPay",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1029,
      "end": 1036,
      "sentence": "Top Analyst Raises Coinbase Stock (COIN) Price Target as U.S. Enters ‘Crypto Week’\nPositive Sentiment:\nCalifornia’s “Breakthrough Project” teams Coinbase with Ripple and MoonPay on state-backed crypto initiatives.",
      "context": "akthrough Project” teams Coinbase with Ripple and MoonPay on state-backed crypto initiatives.\nCalifornia Un",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "California",
      "label": "GPE",
      "start": 1073,
      "end": 1083,
      "sentence": "California Unveils Breakthrough Project With Ripple, Coinbase, And MoonPay\nPositive Sentiment:\nVirtune launched a new Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq Stockholm, expanding institutional access to Coinbase-backed crypto benchmarks.",
      "context": "e and MoonPay on state-backed crypto initiatives.\nCalifornia Unveils Breakthrough Project With Ripple, Coinbas",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": true,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Ripple",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1118,
      "end": 1124,
      "sentence": "California Unveils Breakthrough Project With Ripple, Coinbase, And MoonPay\nPositive Sentiment:\nVirtune launched a new Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq Stockholm, expanding institutional access to Coinbase-backed crypto benchmarks.",
      "context": "ves.\nCalifornia Unveils Breakthrough Project With Ripple, Coinbase, And MoonPay\nPositive Sentiment:\nVirtun",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Coinbase",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1126,
      "end": 1134,
      "sentence": "California Unveils Breakthrough Project With Ripple, Coinbase, And MoonPay\nPositive Sentiment:\nVirtune launched a new Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq Stockholm, expanding institutional access to Coinbase-backed crypto benchmarks.",
      "context": "ifornia Unveils Breakthrough Project With Ripple, Coinbase, And MoonPay\nPositive Sentiment:\nVirtune launched",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "MoonPay",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1140,
      "end": 1147,
      "sentence": "California Unveils Breakthrough Project With Ripple, Coinbase, And MoonPay\nPositive Sentiment:\nVirtune launched a new Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq Stockholm, expanding institutional access to Coinbase-backed crypto benchmarks.",
      "context": "s Breakthrough Project With Ripple, Coinbase, And MoonPay\nPositive Sentiment:\nVirtune launched a new Coinba",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Virtune",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1168,
      "end": 1175,
      "sentence": "California Unveils Breakthrough Project With Ripple, Coinbase, And MoonPay\nPositive Sentiment:\nVirtune launched a new Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq Stockholm, expanding institutional access to Coinbase-backed crypto benchmarks.",
      "context": "Ripple, Coinbase, And MoonPay\nPositive Sentiment:\nVirtune launched a new Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq St",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Nasdaq Stockholm",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1216,
      "end": 1232,
      "sentence": "California Unveils Breakthrough Project With Ripple, Coinbase, And MoonPay\nPositive Sentiment:\nVirtune launched a new Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq Stockholm, expanding institutional access to Coinbase-backed crypto benchmarks.",
      "context": ":\nVirtune launched a new Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq Stockholm, expanding institutional access to Coinbase-backe",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Coinbase",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1268,
      "end": 1276,
      "sentence": "California Unveils Breakthrough Project With Ripple, Coinbase, And MoonPay\nPositive Sentiment:\nVirtune launched a new Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq Stockholm, expanding institutional access to Coinbase-backed crypto benchmarks.",
      "context": "sdaq Stockholm, expanding institutional access to Coinbase-backed crypto benchmarks.\nVirtune launches Virtun",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Virtune",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1303,
      "end": 1310,
      "sentence": "Virtune launches Virtune Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq Stockholm\nPositive Sentiment:\nBitcoin’s ongoing rally underpins crypto equities, with Coinbase among the top beneficiaries of the sector’s surge.\nBitcoin’s 2025 surge isn’t over yet: 5 reasons the rally could keep going\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "context": "onal access to Coinbase-backed crypto benchmarks.\nVirtune launches Virtune Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Coinbase",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1446,
      "end": 1454,
      "sentence": "Virtune launches Virtune Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq Stockholm\nPositive Sentiment:\nBitcoin’s ongoing rally underpins crypto equities, with Coinbase among the top beneficiaries of the sector’s surge.\nBitcoin’s 2025 surge isn’t over yet: 5 reasons the rally could keep going\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "context": "n’s ongoing rally underpins crypto equities, with Coinbase among the top beneficiaries of the sector’s surge",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "2025",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 1516,
      "end": 1520,
      "sentence": "Virtune launches Virtune Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq Stockholm\nPositive Sentiment:\nBitcoin’s ongoing rally underpins crypto equities, with Coinbase among the top beneficiaries of the sector’s surge.\nBitcoin’s 2025 surge isn’t over yet: 5 reasons the rally could keep going\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "context": "op beneficiaries of the sector’s surge.\nBitcoin’s 2025 surge isn’t over yet: 5 reasons the rally could k",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "5",
      "label": "CARDINAL",
      "start": 1543,
      "end": 1544,
      "sentence": "Virtune launches Virtune Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq Stockholm\nPositive Sentiment:\nBitcoin’s ongoing rally underpins crypto equities, with Coinbase among the top beneficiaries of the sector’s surge.\nBitcoin’s 2025 surge isn’t over yet: 5 reasons the rally could keep going\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "context": "tor’s surge.\nBitcoin’s 2025 surge isn’t over yet: 5 reasons the rally could keep going\nNeutral Sentim",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Zacks",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1601,
      "end": 1606,
      "sentence": "A Zacks commentary highlights crypto names including Coinbase as potential multi-year outperformers in a late-cycle tech bubble.",
      "context": "s the rally could keep going\nNeutral Sentiment:\nA Zacks commentary highlights crypto names including Coin",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Coinbase",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1652,
      "end": 1660,
      "sentence": "A Zacks commentary highlights crypto names including Coinbase as potential multi-year outperformers in a late-cycle tech bubble.",
      "context": "acks commentary highlights crypto names including Coinbase as potential multi-year outperformers in a late-c",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "multi-year",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 1674,
      "end": 1684,
      "sentence": "A Zacks commentary highlights crypto names including Coinbase as potential multi-year outperformers in a late-cycle tech bubble.",
      "context": "ghts crypto names including Coinbase as potential multi-year outperformers in a late-cycle tech bubble.\nThe Ne",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "late-cycle",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 1704,
      "end": 1714,
      "sentence": "A Zacks commentary highlights crypto names including Coinbase as potential multi-year outperformers in a late-cycle tech bubble.",
      "context": "inbase as potential multi-year outperformers in a late-cycle tech bubble.\nThe Next Great Bubble: Riding Quantu",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "$100 million",
      "label": "MONEY",
      "start": 1816,
      "end": 1828,
      "sentence": "The Next Great Bubble: Riding Quantum, AI, and Crypto Stocks\nNeutral Sentiment:\nDespite $100 million in PAC funding, key crypto bills remain unsigned, prompting Coinbase to lobby Congress for clarity.",
      "context": "AI, and Crypto Stocks\nNeutral Sentiment:\nDespite $100 million in PAC funding, key crypto bills remain unsigned,",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": true
    },
    {
      "text": "Coinbase",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1889,
      "end": 1897,
      "sentence": "The Next Great Bubble: Riding Quantum, AI, and Crypto Stocks\nNeutral Sentiment:\nDespite $100 million in PAC funding, key crypto bills remain unsigned, prompting Coinbase to lobby Congress for clarity.",
      "context": "ding, key crypto bills remain unsigned, prompting Coinbase to lobby Congress for clarity.\n$100M In PAC Fundi",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Congress",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1907,
      "end": 1915,
      "sentence": "The Next Great Bubble: Riding Quantum, AI, and Crypto Stocks\nNeutral Sentiment:\nDespite $100 million in PAC funding, key crypto bills remain unsigned, prompting Coinbase to lobby Congress for clarity.",
      "context": "ills remain unsigned, prompting Coinbase to lobby Congress for clarity.\n$100M In PAC Funding, But Still No C",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "$100",
      "label": "MONEY",
      "start": 1929,
      "end": 1933,
      "sentence": "$100M In PAC Funding, But Still No Crypto Laws — What Coinbase Wants Washington To Know\nNeutral Sentiment:\nHouse Republicans’ “crypto week” stalled, delaying expected legislation that could affect Coinbase’s operating environment.",
      "context": "prompting Coinbase to lobby Congress for clarity.\n$100M In PAC Funding, But Still No Crypto Laws — What",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": true
    },
    {
      "text": "Coinbase",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1983,
      "end": 1991,
      "sentence": "$100M In PAC Funding, But Still No Crypto Laws — What Coinbase Wants Washington To Know\nNeutral Sentiment:\nHouse Republicans’ “crypto week” stalled, delaying expected legislation that could affect Coinbase’s operating environment.",
      "context": "M In PAC Funding, But Still No Crypto Laws — What Coinbase Wants Washington To Know\nNeutral Sentiment:\nHouse",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Washington",
      "label": "GPE",
      "start": 1998,
      "end": 2008,
      "sentence": "$100M In PAC Funding, But Still No Crypto Laws — What Coinbase Wants Washington To Know\nNeutral Sentiment:\nHouse Republicans’ “crypto week” stalled, delaying expected legislation that could affect Coinbase’s operating environment.",
      "context": "g, But Still No Crypto Laws — What Coinbase Wants Washington To Know\nNeutral Sentiment:\nHouse Republicans’ “cr",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": true,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "House",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 2036,
      "end": 2041,
      "sentence": "$100M In PAC Funding, But Still No Crypto Laws — What Coinbase Wants Washington To Know\nNeutral Sentiment:\nHouse Republicans’ “crypto week” stalled, delaying expected legislation that could affect Coinbase’s operating environment.",
      "context": "nbase Wants Washington To Know\nNeutral Sentiment:\nHouse Republicans’ “crypto week” stalled, delaying expe",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Republicans",
      "label": "NORP",
      "start": 2042,
      "end": 2053,
      "sentence": "$100M In PAC Funding, But Still No Crypto Laws — What Coinbase Wants Washington To Know\nNeutral Sentiment:\nHouse Republicans’ “crypto week” stalled, delaying expected legislation that could affect Coinbase’s operating environment.",
      "context": "Wants Washington To Know\nNeutral Sentiment:\nHouse Republicans’ “crypto week” stalled, delaying expected legisla",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Coinbase",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 2126,
      "end": 2134,
      "sentence": "$100M In PAC Funding, But Still No Crypto Laws — What Coinbase Wants Washington To Know\nNeutral Sentiment:\nHouse Republicans’ “crypto week” stalled, delaying expected legislation that could affect Coinbase’s operating environment.",
      "context": ", delaying expected legislation that could affect Coinbase’s operating environment.\nRepublicans declared it",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Republicans",
      "label": "NORP",
      "start": 2160,
      "end": 2171,
      "sentence": "Republicans declared it 'crypto' week in the House.",
      "context": "at could affect Coinbase’s operating environment.\nRepublicans declared it 'crypto' week in the House. It's not",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "crypto' week",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 2185,
      "end": 2197,
      "sentence": "Republicans declared it 'crypto' week in the House.",
      "context": "s operating environment.\nRepublicans declared it 'crypto' week in the House. It's not going as planned\nNegative",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "House",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 2205,
      "end": 2210,
      "sentence": "Republicans declared it 'crypto' week in the House.",
      "context": "ent.\nRepublicans declared it 'crypto' week in the House. It's not going as planned\nNegative Sentiment:\nHC",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "HC Wainwright",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 2258,
      "end": 2271,
      "sentence": "It's not going as planned\nNegative Sentiment:\nHC Wainwright cut Q3 2025 EPS estimates sharply to $0.43 and assigned a Sell rating with a $300 target.",
      "context": "se. It's not going as planned\nNegative Sentiment:\nHC Wainwright cut Q3 2025 EPS estimates sharply to $0.43 and as",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Q3 2025",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 2276,
      "end": 2283,
      "sentence": "It's not going as planned\nNegative Sentiment:\nHC Wainwright cut Q3 2025 EPS estimates sharply to $0.43 and assigned a Sell rating with a $300 target.",
      "context": "as planned\nNegative Sentiment:\nHC Wainwright cut Q3 2025 EPS estimates sharply to $0.43 and assigned a Sel",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "0.43",
      "label": "MONEY",
      "start": 2310,
      "end": 2314,
      "sentence": "It's not going as planned\nNegative Sentiment:\nHC Wainwright cut Q3 2025 EPS estimates sharply to $0.43 and assigned a Sell rating with a $300 target.",
      "context": "Wainwright cut Q3 2025 EPS estimates sharply to $0.43 and assigned a Sell rating with a $300 target.\nCo",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": true
    },
    {
      "text": "300",
      "label": "MONEY",
      "start": 2350,
      "end": 2353,
      "sentence": "It's not going as planned\nNegative Sentiment:\nHC Wainwright cut Q3 2025 EPS estimates sharply to $0.43 and assigned a Sell rating with a $300 target.",
      "context": "arply to $0.43 and assigned a Sell rating with a $300 target.\nCoinbase Global, Inc. (NASDAQ:COIN) CEO S",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": true
    },
    {
      "text": "Coinbase Global, Inc.",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 2362,
      "end": 2383,
      "sentence": "Coinbase Global, Inc. (NASDAQ:COIN) CEO Sells $10,796,526.55 in Stock\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "context": "43 and assigned a Sell rating with a $300 target.\nCoinbase Global, Inc. (NASDAQ:COIN) CEO Sells $10,796,526.55 in Stock\nN",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "COIN",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 2392,
      "end": 2396,
      "sentence": "Coinbase Global, Inc. (NASDAQ:COIN) CEO Sells $10,796,526.55 in Stock\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "context": "with a $300 target.\nCoinbase Global, Inc. (NASDAQ:COIN) CEO Sells $10,796,526.55 in Stock\nNegative Senti",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "10,796,526.55",
      "label": "MONEY",
      "start": 2409,
      "end": 2422,
      "sentence": "Coinbase Global, Inc. (NASDAQ:COIN) CEO Sells $10,796,526.55 in Stock\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "context": "t.\nCoinbase Global, Inc. (NASDAQ:COIN) CEO Sells $10,796,526.55 in Stock\nNegative Sentiment:\nCEO Brian Armstrong",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": true
    },
    {
      "text": "Brian Armstrong",
      "label": "PERSON",
      "start": 2456,
      "end": 2471,
      "sentence": "CEO Brian Armstrong sold over $75 million worth of COIN shares in recent transactions, reducing his stake to under 0.01%.",
      "context": "s $10,796,526.55 in Stock\nNegative Sentiment:\nCEO Brian Armstrong sold over $75 million worth of COIN shares in rec",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": true,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "$75 million",
      "label": "MONEY",
      "start": 2482,
      "end": 2493,
      "sentence": "CEO Brian Armstrong sold over $75 million worth of COIN shares in recent transactions, reducing his stake to under 0.01%.",
      "context": "Negative Sentiment:\nCEO Brian Armstrong sold over $75 million worth of COIN shares in recent transactions, redu",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": true
    },
    {
      "text": "COIN",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 2503,
      "end": 2507,
      "sentence": "CEO Brian Armstrong sold over $75 million worth of COIN shares in recent transactions, reducing his stake to under 0.01%.",
      "context": "EO Brian Armstrong sold over $75 million worth of COIN shares in recent transactions, reducing his stake",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "under 0.01%",
      "label": "PERCENT",
      "start": 2561,
      "end": 2572,
      "sentence": "CEO Brian Armstrong sold over $75 million worth of COIN shares in recent transactions, reducing his stake to under 0.01%.",
      "context": "res in recent transactions, reducing his stake to under 0.01%.\nInsider Selling: Coinbase Global, Inc. (NASDAQ:C",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": true
    },
    {
      "text": "Coinbase Global, Inc.",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 2591,
      "end": 2612,
      "sentence": "Coinbase Global, Inc. (NASDAQ:COIN) CEO Sells 27,751 Shares of Stock\nPosted 51m ago\nAI Generated.",
      "context": "ducing his stake to under 0.01%.\nInsider Selling: Coinbase Global, Inc. (NASDAQ:COIN) CEO Sells 27,751 Shares of Stock\nPo",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "COIN",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 2621,
      "end": 2625,
      "sentence": "Coinbase Global, Inc. (NASDAQ:COIN) CEO Sells 27,751 Shares of Stock\nPosted 51m ago\nAI Generated.",
      "context": "%.\nInsider Selling: Coinbase Global, Inc. (NASDAQ:COIN) CEO Sells 27,751 Shares of Stock\nPosted 51m ago",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "27,751",
      "label": "CARDINAL",
      "start": 2637,
      "end": 2643,
      "sentence": "Coinbase Global, Inc. (NASDAQ:COIN) CEO Sells 27,751 Shares of Stock\nPosted 51m ago\nAI Generated.",
      "context": "ng: Coinbase Global, Inc. (NASDAQ:COIN) CEO Sells 27,751 Shares of Stock\nPosted 51m ago\nAI Generated. May",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "51m ago",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 2667,
      "end": 2674,
      "sentence": "Coinbase Global, Inc. (NASDAQ:COIN) CEO Sells 27,751 Shares of Stock\nPosted 51m ago\nAI Generated.",
      "context": "DAQ:COIN) CEO Sells 27,751 Shares of Stock\nPosted 51m ago\nAI Generated. May Contain Errors.",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    }
  ],
  "relationships": [
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Shares",
      "verb": "hit",
      "object": "high",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nShares hit a new 52-week high as Washington advances bipartisan crypto legislation, lifting investor optimism.",
      "importance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Washington",
      "verb": "advances",
      "object": "legislation",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nShares hit a new 52-week high as Washington advances bipartisan crypto legislation, lifting investor optimism.",
      "importance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Stock",
      "verb": "Hit",
      "object": "High",
      "sentence": "Why Coinbase Global Stock Hit A New 52-Week High Today\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "importance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "signals",
      "verb": "driving",
      "object": "upside",
      "sentence": "Big-money inflows accelerate, with four outlier buy signals over two months driving sustained upside in COIN shares.",
      "importance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Oppenheimer",
      "verb": "raised",
      "object": "target",
      "sentence": "Oppenheimer raised its price target to $417 and reiterated a Buy rating, citing bullish regulatory outlook.",
      "importance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Analyst",
      "verb": "Raises",
      "object": "Target",
      "sentence": "Top Analyst Raises Coinbase Stock (COIN) Price Target as U.S. Enters ‘Crypto Week’\nPositive Sentiment:\nCalifornia’s “Breakthrough Project” teams Coinbase with Ripple and MoonPay on state-backed crypto initiatives.",
      "importance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "U.S.",
      "verb": "Enters",
      "object": "Week",
      "sentence": "Top Analyst Raises Coinbase Stock (COIN) Price Target as U.S. Enters ‘Crypto Week’\nPositive Sentiment:\nCalifornia’s “Breakthrough Project” teams Coinbase with Ripple and MoonPay on state-backed crypto initiatives.",
      "importance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Project",
      "verb": "teams",
      "object": "Coinbase",
      "sentence": "Top Analyst Raises Coinbase Stock (COIN) Price Target as U.S. Enters ‘Crypto Week’\nPositive Sentiment:\nCalifornia’s “Breakthrough Project” teams Coinbase with Ripple and MoonPay on state-backed crypto initiatives.",
      "importance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "California",
      "verb": "Unveils",
      "object": "Project",
      "sentence": "California Unveils Breakthrough Project With Ripple, Coinbase, And MoonPay\nPositive Sentiment:\nVirtune launched a new Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq Stockholm, expanding institutional access to Coinbase-backed crypto benchmarks.",
      "importance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Virtune",
      "verb": "launched",
      "object": "ETP",
      "sentence": "California Unveils Breakthrough Project With Ripple, Coinbase, And MoonPay\nPositive Sentiment:\nVirtune launched a new Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq Stockholm, expanding institutional access to Coinbase-backed crypto benchmarks.",
      "importance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Virtune",
      "verb": "launches",
      "object": "ETP",
      "sentence": "Virtune launches Virtune Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq Stockholm\nPositive Sentiment:\nBitcoin’s ongoing rally underpins crypto equities, with Coinbase among the top beneficiaries of the sector’s surge.\nBitcoin’s 2025 surge isn’t over yet: 5 reasons the rally could keep going\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "importance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "rally",
      "verb": "underpins",
      "object": "equities",
      "sentence": "Virtune launches Virtune Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq Stockholm\nPositive Sentiment:\nBitcoin’s ongoing rally underpins crypto equities, with Coinbase among the top beneficiaries of the sector’s surge.\nBitcoin’s 2025 surge isn’t over yet: 5 reasons the rally could keep going\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "importance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "commentary",
      "verb": "highlights",
      "object": "names",
      "sentence": "A Zacks commentary highlights crypto names including Coinbase as potential multi-year outperformers in a late-cycle tech bubble.",
      "importance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Washington",
      "verb": "Know",
      "object": "What",
      "sentence": "$100M In PAC Funding, But Still No Crypto Laws — What Coinbase Wants Washington To Know\nNeutral Sentiment:\nHouse Republicans’ “crypto week” stalled, delaying expected legislation that could affect Coinbase’s operating environment.",
      "importance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "that",
      "verb": "affect",
      "object": "environment",
      "sentence": "$100M In PAC Funding, But Still No Crypto Laws — What Coinbase Wants Washington To Know\nNeutral Sentiment:\nHouse Republicans’ “crypto week” stalled, delaying expected legislation that could affect Coinbase’s operating environment.",
      "importance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Wainwright",
      "verb": "cut",
      "object": "estimates",
      "sentence": "It's not going as planned\nNegative Sentiment:\nHC Wainwright cut Q3 2025 EPS estimates sharply to $0.43 and assigned a Sell rating with a $300 target.",
      "importance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "CEO",
      "verb": "Sells",
      "object": "10,796,526.55",
      "sentence": "Coinbase Global, Inc. (NASDAQ:COIN) CEO Sells $10,796,526.55 in Stock\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "importance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Armstrong",
      "verb": "sold",
      "object": "worth",
      "sentence": "CEO Brian Armstrong sold over $75 million worth of COIN shares in recent transactions, reducing his stake to under 0.01%.",
      "importance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "CEO",
      "verb": "Sells",
      "object": "Shares",
      "sentence": "Coinbase Global, Inc. (NASDAQ:COIN) CEO Sells 27,751 Shares of Stock\nPosted 51m ago\nAI Generated.",
      "importance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Coinbase",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Global",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Coinbase Global, Inc. (NASDAQ:COIN) saw its shares move today on a mix of regulatory progress, institutional flows, analyst actions and insider transactions.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Coinbase",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": ",",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Coinbase Global, Inc. (NASDAQ:COIN) saw its shares move today on a mix of regulatory progress, institutional flows, analyst actions and insider transactions.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Coinbase",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Inc.",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Coinbase Global, Inc. (NASDAQ:COIN) saw its shares move today on a mix of regulatory progress, institutional flows, analyst actions and insider transactions.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Coinbase",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "COIN",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Coinbase Global, Inc. (NASDAQ:COIN) saw its shares move today on a mix of regulatory progress, institutional flows, analyst actions and insider transactions.",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Coinbase",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "today",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Coinbase Global, Inc. (NASDAQ:COIN) saw its shares move today on a mix of regulatory progress, institutional flows, analyst actions and insider transactions.",
      "distance": 13
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Global",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": ",",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Coinbase Global, Inc. (NASDAQ:COIN) saw its shares move today on a mix of regulatory progress, institutional flows, analyst actions and insider transactions.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Global",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Inc.",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Coinbase Global, Inc. (NASDAQ:COIN) saw its shares move today on a mix of regulatory progress, institutional flows, analyst actions and insider transactions.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Global",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "COIN",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Coinbase Global, Inc. (NASDAQ:COIN) saw its shares move today on a mix of regulatory progress, institutional flows, analyst actions and insider transactions.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Global",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "today",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Coinbase Global, Inc. (NASDAQ:COIN) saw its shares move today on a mix of regulatory progress, institutional flows, analyst actions and insider transactions.",
      "distance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": ",",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Inc.",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Coinbase Global, Inc. (NASDAQ:COIN) saw its shares move today on a mix of regulatory progress, institutional flows, analyst actions and insider transactions.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": ",",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "COIN",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Coinbase Global, Inc. (NASDAQ:COIN) saw its shares move today on a mix of regulatory progress, institutional flows, analyst actions and insider transactions.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": ",",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "today",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Coinbase Global, Inc. (NASDAQ:COIN) saw its shares move today on a mix of regulatory progress, institutional flows, analyst actions and insider transactions.",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Inc.",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "COIN",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Coinbase Global, Inc. (NASDAQ:COIN) saw its shares move today on a mix of regulatory progress, institutional flows, analyst actions and insider transactions.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Inc.",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "today",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Coinbase Global, Inc. (NASDAQ:COIN) saw its shares move today on a mix of regulatory progress, institutional flows, analyst actions and insider transactions.",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "COIN",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "today",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Coinbase Global, Inc. (NASDAQ:COIN) saw its shares move today on a mix of regulatory progress, institutional flows, analyst actions and insider transactions.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "52",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nShares hit a new 52-week high as Washington advances bipartisan crypto legislation, lifting investor optimism.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "52",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "week",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nShares hit a new 52-week high as Washington advances bipartisan crypto legislation, lifting investor optimism.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "52",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "Washington",
      "entity2_type": "GPE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nShares hit a new 52-week high as Washington advances bipartisan crypto legislation, lifting investor optimism.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "week",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nShares hit a new 52-week high as Washington advances bipartisan crypto legislation, lifting investor optimism.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "Washington",
      "entity2_type": "GPE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nShares hit a new 52-week high as Washington advances bipartisan crypto legislation, lifting investor optimism.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "week",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "Washington",
      "entity2_type": "GPE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nShares hit a new 52-week high as Washington advances bipartisan crypto legislation, lifting investor optimism.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Coinbase",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Global",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Why Coinbase Global Stock Hit A New 52-Week High Today\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Coinbase",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Stock",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Why Coinbase Global Stock Hit A New 52-Week High Today\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Coinbase",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "52",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Why Coinbase Global Stock Hit A New 52-Week High Today\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Coinbase",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Why Coinbase Global Stock Hit A New 52-Week High Today\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Coinbase",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Week",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Why Coinbase Global Stock Hit A New 52-Week High Today\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Coinbase",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Today",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Why Coinbase Global Stock Hit A New 52-Week High Today\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Global",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Stock",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Why Coinbase Global Stock Hit A New 52-Week High Today\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Global",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "52",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Why Coinbase Global Stock Hit A New 52-Week High Today\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Global",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Why Coinbase Global Stock Hit A New 52-Week High Today\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Global",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Week",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Why Coinbase Global Stock Hit A New 52-Week High Today\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Global",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Today",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Why Coinbase Global Stock Hit A New 52-Week High Today\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Stock",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "52",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Why Coinbase Global Stock Hit A New 52-Week High Today\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Stock",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Why Coinbase Global Stock Hit A New 52-Week High Today\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Stock",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Week",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Why Coinbase Global Stock Hit A New 52-Week High Today\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Stock",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Today",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Why Coinbase Global Stock Hit A New 52-Week High Today\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "52",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Why Coinbase Global Stock Hit A New 52-Week High Today\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "52",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "Week",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Why Coinbase Global Stock Hit A New 52-Week High Today\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "52",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "Today",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Why Coinbase Global Stock Hit A New 52-Week High Today\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "Week",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Why Coinbase Global Stock Hit A New 52-Week High Today\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "Today",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Why Coinbase Global Stock Hit A New 52-Week High Today\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Week",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "Today",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Why Coinbase Global Stock Hit A New 52-Week High Today\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "four",
      "entity1_type": "CARDINAL",
      "entity2": "two",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Big-money inflows accelerate, with four outlier buy signals over two months driving sustained upside in COIN shares.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "four",
      "entity1_type": "CARDINAL",
      "entity2": "months",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Big-money inflows accelerate, with four outlier buy signals over two months driving sustained upside in COIN shares.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "four",
      "entity1_type": "CARDINAL",
      "entity2": "COIN",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Big-money inflows accelerate, with four outlier buy signals over two months driving sustained upside in COIN shares.",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "two",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "months",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Big-money inflows accelerate, with four outlier buy signals over two months driving sustained upside in COIN shares.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "two",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "COIN",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Big-money inflows accelerate, with four outlier buy signals over two months driving sustained upside in COIN shares.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "months",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "COIN",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Big-money inflows accelerate, with four outlier buy signals over two months driving sustained upside in COIN shares.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "American",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Banking",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "An analyst upgrade from American Banking News helped lift COIN nearly 2% after revising its rating higher.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "American",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "News",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "An analyst upgrade from American Banking News helped lift COIN nearly 2% after revising its rating higher.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "American",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "COIN",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "An analyst upgrade from American Banking News helped lift COIN nearly 2% after revising its rating higher.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "American",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "nearly",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "An analyst upgrade from American Banking News helped lift COIN nearly 2% after revising its rating higher.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "American",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "2",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "An analyst upgrade from American Banking News helped lift COIN nearly 2% after revising its rating higher.",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "American",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "%",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "An analyst upgrade from American Banking News helped lift COIN nearly 2% after revising its rating higher.",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Banking",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "News",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "An analyst upgrade from American Banking News helped lift COIN nearly 2% after revising its rating higher.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Banking",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "COIN",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "An analyst upgrade from American Banking News helped lift COIN nearly 2% after revising its rating higher.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Banking",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "nearly",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "An analyst upgrade from American Banking News helped lift COIN nearly 2% after revising its rating higher.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Banking",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "2",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "An analyst upgrade from American Banking News helped lift COIN nearly 2% after revising its rating higher.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Banking",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "%",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "An analyst upgrade from American Banking News helped lift COIN nearly 2% after revising its rating higher.",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "News",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "COIN",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "An analyst upgrade from American Banking News helped lift COIN nearly 2% after revising its rating higher.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "News",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "nearly",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "An analyst upgrade from American Banking News helped lift COIN nearly 2% after revising its rating higher.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "News",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "2",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "An analyst upgrade from American Banking News helped lift COIN nearly 2% after revising its rating higher.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "News",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "%",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "An analyst upgrade from American Banking News helped lift COIN nearly 2% after revising its rating higher.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "COIN",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "nearly",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "An analyst upgrade from American Banking News helped lift COIN nearly 2% after revising its rating higher.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "COIN",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "2",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "An analyst upgrade from American Banking News helped lift COIN nearly 2% after revising its rating higher.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "COIN",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "%",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "An analyst upgrade from American Banking News helped lift COIN nearly 2% after revising its rating higher.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "nearly",
      "entity1_type": "PERCENT",
      "entity2": "2",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "An analyst upgrade from American Banking News helped lift COIN nearly 2% after revising its rating higher.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "nearly",
      "entity1_type": "PERCENT",
      "entity2": "%",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "An analyst upgrade from American Banking News helped lift COIN nearly 2% after revising its rating higher.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "2",
      "entity1_type": "PERCENT",
      "entity2": "%",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "An analyst upgrade from American Banking News helped lift COIN nearly 2% after revising its rating higher.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Coinbase",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Global",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Coinbase Global (NASDAQ:COIN) Trading 1.9% Higher Following Analyst Upgrade\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Coinbase",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "1.9",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "Coinbase Global (NASDAQ:COIN) Trading 1.9% Higher Following Analyst Upgrade\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Coinbase",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "%",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "Coinbase Global (NASDAQ:COIN) Trading 1.9% Higher Following Analyst Upgrade\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Global",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "1.9",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "Coinbase Global (NASDAQ:COIN) Trading 1.9% Higher Following Analyst Upgrade\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Global",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "%",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "Coinbase Global (NASDAQ:COIN) Trading 1.9% Higher Following Analyst Upgrade\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "1.9",
      "entity1_type": "PERCENT",
      "entity2": "%",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "Coinbase Global (NASDAQ:COIN) Trading 1.9% Higher Following Analyst Upgrade\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Oppenheimer",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "417",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Oppenheimer raised its price target to $417 and reiterated a Buy rating, citing bullish regulatory outlook.",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Coinbase",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "U.S.",
      "entity2_type": "GPE",
      "sentence": "Top Analyst Raises Coinbase Stock (COIN) Price Target as U.S. Enters ‘Crypto Week’\nPositive Sentiment:\nCalifornia’s “Breakthrough Project” teams Coinbase with Ripple and MoonPay on state-backed crypto initiatives.",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Coinbase",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Crypto",
      "entity2_type": "EVENT",
      "sentence": "Top Analyst Raises Coinbase Stock (COIN) Price Target as U.S. Enters ‘Crypto Week’\nPositive Sentiment:\nCalifornia’s “Breakthrough Project” teams Coinbase with Ripple and MoonPay on state-backed crypto initiatives.",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Coinbase",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Week",
      "entity2_type": "EVENT",
      "sentence": "Top Analyst Raises Coinbase Stock (COIN) Price Target as U.S. Enters ‘Crypto Week’\nPositive Sentiment:\nCalifornia’s “Breakthrough Project” teams Coinbase with Ripple and MoonPay on state-backed crypto initiatives.",
      "distance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Coinbase",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "California",
      "entity2_type": "GPE",
      "sentence": "Top Analyst Raises Coinbase Stock (COIN) Price Target as U.S. Enters ‘Crypto Week’\nPositive Sentiment:\nCalifornia’s “Breakthrough Project” teams Coinbase with Ripple and MoonPay on state-backed crypto initiatives.",
      "distance": 19
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Coinbase",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Coinbase",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Top Analyst Raises Coinbase Stock (COIN) Price Target as U.S. Enters ‘Crypto Week’\nPositive Sentiment:\nCalifornia’s “Breakthrough Project” teams Coinbase with Ripple and MoonPay on state-backed crypto initiatives.",
      "distance": 26
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Coinbase",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Ripple",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Top Analyst Raises Coinbase Stock (COIN) Price Target as U.S. Enters ‘Crypto Week’\nPositive Sentiment:\nCalifornia’s “Breakthrough Project” teams Coinbase with Ripple and MoonPay on state-backed crypto initiatives.",
      "distance": 28
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Coinbase",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "MoonPay",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Top Analyst Raises Coinbase Stock (COIN) Price Target as U.S. Enters ‘Crypto Week’\nPositive Sentiment:\nCalifornia’s “Breakthrough Project” teams Coinbase with Ripple and MoonPay on state-backed crypto initiatives.",
      "distance": 30
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "U.S.",
      "entity1_type": "GPE",
      "entity2": "Crypto",
      "entity2_type": "EVENT",
      "sentence": "Top Analyst Raises Coinbase Stock (COIN) Price Target as U.S. Enters ‘Crypto Week’\nPositive Sentiment:\nCalifornia’s “Breakthrough Project” teams Coinbase with Ripple and MoonPay on state-backed crypto initiatives.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "U.S.",
      "entity1_type": "GPE",
      "entity2": "Week",
      "entity2_type": "EVENT",
      "sentence": "Top Analyst Raises Coinbase Stock (COIN) Price Target as U.S. Enters ‘Crypto Week’\nPositive Sentiment:\nCalifornia’s “Breakthrough Project” teams Coinbase with Ripple and MoonPay on state-backed crypto initiatives.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "U.S.",
      "entity1_type": "GPE",
      "entity2": "California",
      "entity2_type": "GPE",
      "sentence": "Top Analyst Raises Coinbase Stock (COIN) Price Target as U.S. Enters ‘Crypto Week’\nPositive Sentiment:\nCalifornia’s “Breakthrough Project” teams Coinbase with Ripple and MoonPay on state-backed crypto initiatives.",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "U.S.",
      "entity1_type": "GPE",
      "entity2": "Coinbase",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Top Analyst Raises Coinbase Stock (COIN) Price Target as U.S. Enters ‘Crypto Week’\nPositive Sentiment:\nCalifornia’s “Breakthrough Project” teams Coinbase with Ripple and MoonPay on state-backed crypto initiatives.",
      "distance": 18
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "U.S.",
      "entity1_type": "GPE",
      "entity2": "Ripple",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Top Analyst Raises Coinbase Stock (COIN) Price Target as U.S. Enters ‘Crypto Week’\nPositive Sentiment:\nCalifornia’s “Breakthrough Project” teams Coinbase with Ripple and MoonPay on state-backed crypto initiatives.",
      "distance": 20
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "U.S.",
      "entity1_type": "GPE",
      "entity2": "MoonPay",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Top Analyst Raises Coinbase Stock (COIN) Price Target as U.S. Enters ‘Crypto Week’\nPositive Sentiment:\nCalifornia’s “Breakthrough Project” teams Coinbase with Ripple and MoonPay on state-backed crypto initiatives.",
      "distance": 22
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Crypto",
      "entity1_type": "EVENT",
      "entity2": "Week",
      "entity2_type": "EVENT",
      "sentence": "Top Analyst Raises Coinbase Stock (COIN) Price Target as U.S. Enters ‘Crypto Week’\nPositive Sentiment:\nCalifornia’s “Breakthrough Project” teams Coinbase with Ripple and MoonPay on state-backed crypto initiatives.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Crypto",
      "entity1_type": "EVENT",
      "entity2": "California",
      "entity2_type": "GPE",
      "sentence": "Top Analyst Raises Coinbase Stock (COIN) Price Target as U.S. Enters ‘Crypto Week’\nPositive Sentiment:\nCalifornia’s “Breakthrough Project” teams Coinbase with Ripple and MoonPay on state-backed crypto initiatives.",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Crypto",
      "entity1_type": "EVENT",
      "entity2": "Coinbase",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Top Analyst Raises Coinbase Stock (COIN) Price Target as U.S. Enters ‘Crypto Week’\nPositive Sentiment:\nCalifornia’s “Breakthrough Project” teams Coinbase with Ripple and MoonPay on state-backed crypto initiatives.",
      "distance": 15
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Crypto",
      "entity1_type": "EVENT",
      "entity2": "Ripple",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Top Analyst Raises Coinbase Stock (COIN) Price Target as U.S. Enters ‘Crypto Week’\nPositive Sentiment:\nCalifornia’s “Breakthrough Project” teams Coinbase with Ripple and MoonPay on state-backed crypto initiatives.",
      "distance": 17
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Crypto",
      "entity1_type": "EVENT",
      "entity2": "MoonPay",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Top Analyst Raises Coinbase Stock (COIN) Price Target as U.S. Enters ‘Crypto Week’\nPositive Sentiment:\nCalifornia’s “Breakthrough Project” teams Coinbase with Ripple and MoonPay on state-backed crypto initiatives.",
      "distance": 19
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Week",
      "entity1_type": "EVENT",
      "entity2": "California",
      "entity2_type": "GPE",
      "sentence": "Top Analyst Raises Coinbase Stock (COIN) Price Target as U.S. Enters ‘Crypto Week’\nPositive Sentiment:\nCalifornia’s “Breakthrough Project” teams Coinbase with Ripple and MoonPay on state-backed crypto initiatives.",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Week",
      "entity1_type": "EVENT",
      "entity2": "Coinbase",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Top Analyst Raises Coinbase Stock (COIN) Price Target as U.S. Enters ‘Crypto Week’\nPositive Sentiment:\nCalifornia’s “Breakthrough Project” teams Coinbase with Ripple and MoonPay on state-backed crypto initiatives.",
      "distance": 14
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Week",
      "entity1_type": "EVENT",
      "entity2": "Ripple",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Top Analyst Raises Coinbase Stock (COIN) Price Target as U.S. Enters ‘Crypto Week’\nPositive Sentiment:\nCalifornia’s “Breakthrough Project” teams Coinbase with Ripple and MoonPay on state-backed crypto initiatives.",
      "distance": 16
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Week",
      "entity1_type": "EVENT",
      "entity2": "MoonPay",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Top Analyst Raises Coinbase Stock (COIN) Price Target as U.S. Enters ‘Crypto Week’\nPositive Sentiment:\nCalifornia’s “Breakthrough Project” teams Coinbase with Ripple and MoonPay on state-backed crypto initiatives.",
      "distance": 18
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "California",
      "entity1_type": "GPE",
      "entity2": "Coinbase",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Top Analyst Raises Coinbase Stock (COIN) Price Target as U.S. Enters ‘Crypto Week’\nPositive Sentiment:\nCalifornia’s “Breakthrough Project” teams Coinbase with Ripple and MoonPay on state-backed crypto initiatives.",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "California",
      "entity1_type": "GPE",
      "entity2": "Ripple",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Top Analyst Raises Coinbase Stock (COIN) Price Target as U.S. Enters ‘Crypto Week’\nPositive Sentiment:\nCalifornia’s “Breakthrough Project” teams Coinbase with Ripple and MoonPay on state-backed crypto initiatives.",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "California",
      "entity1_type": "GPE",
      "entity2": "MoonPay",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Top Analyst Raises Coinbase Stock (COIN) Price Target as U.S. Enters ‘Crypto Week’\nPositive Sentiment:\nCalifornia’s “Breakthrough Project” teams Coinbase with Ripple and MoonPay on state-backed crypto initiatives.",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Coinbase",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Ripple",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Top Analyst Raises Coinbase Stock (COIN) Price Target as U.S. Enters ‘Crypto Week’\nPositive Sentiment:\nCalifornia’s “Breakthrough Project” teams Coinbase with Ripple and MoonPay on state-backed crypto initiatives.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Coinbase",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "MoonPay",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Top Analyst Raises Coinbase Stock (COIN) Price Target as U.S. Enters ‘Crypto Week’\nPositive Sentiment:\nCalifornia’s “Breakthrough Project” teams Coinbase with Ripple and MoonPay on state-backed crypto initiatives.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Ripple",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "MoonPay",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Top Analyst Raises Coinbase Stock (COIN) Price Target as U.S. Enters ‘Crypto Week’\nPositive Sentiment:\nCalifornia’s “Breakthrough Project” teams Coinbase with Ripple and MoonPay on state-backed crypto initiatives.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "California",
      "entity1_type": "GPE",
      "entity2": "Ripple",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "California Unveils Breakthrough Project With Ripple, Coinbase, And MoonPay\nPositive Sentiment:\nVirtune launched a new Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq Stockholm, expanding institutional access to Coinbase-backed crypto benchmarks.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "California",
      "entity1_type": "GPE",
      "entity2": "Coinbase",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "California Unveils Breakthrough Project With Ripple, Coinbase, And MoonPay\nPositive Sentiment:\nVirtune launched a new Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq Stockholm, expanding institutional access to Coinbase-backed crypto benchmarks.",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "California",
      "entity1_type": "GPE",
      "entity2": "MoonPay",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "California Unveils Breakthrough Project With Ripple, Coinbase, And MoonPay\nPositive Sentiment:\nVirtune launched a new Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq Stockholm, expanding institutional access to Coinbase-backed crypto benchmarks.",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "California",
      "entity1_type": "GPE",
      "entity2": "Virtune",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "California Unveils Breakthrough Project With Ripple, Coinbase, And MoonPay\nPositive Sentiment:\nVirtune launched a new Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq Stockholm, expanding institutional access to Coinbase-backed crypto benchmarks.",
      "distance": 16
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "California",
      "entity1_type": "GPE",
      "entity2": "Nasdaq",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "California Unveils Breakthrough Project With Ripple, Coinbase, And MoonPay\nPositive Sentiment:\nVirtune launched a new Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq Stockholm, expanding institutional access to Coinbase-backed crypto benchmarks.",
      "distance": 25
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "California",
      "entity1_type": "GPE",
      "entity2": "Stockholm",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "California Unveils Breakthrough Project With Ripple, Coinbase, And MoonPay\nPositive Sentiment:\nVirtune launched a new Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq Stockholm, expanding institutional access to Coinbase-backed crypto benchmarks.",
      "distance": 26
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "California",
      "entity1_type": "GPE",
      "entity2": "Coinbase",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "California Unveils Breakthrough Project With Ripple, Coinbase, And MoonPay\nPositive Sentiment:\nVirtune launched a new Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq Stockholm, expanding institutional access to Coinbase-backed crypto benchmarks.",
      "distance": 32
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Ripple",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Coinbase",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "California Unveils Breakthrough Project With Ripple, Coinbase, And MoonPay\nPositive Sentiment:\nVirtune launched a new Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq Stockholm, expanding institutional access to Coinbase-backed crypto benchmarks.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Ripple",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "MoonPay",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "California Unveils Breakthrough Project With Ripple, Coinbase, And MoonPay\nPositive Sentiment:\nVirtune launched a new Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq Stockholm, expanding institutional access to Coinbase-backed crypto benchmarks.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Ripple",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Virtune",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "California Unveils Breakthrough Project With Ripple, Coinbase, And MoonPay\nPositive Sentiment:\nVirtune launched a new Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq Stockholm, expanding institutional access to Coinbase-backed crypto benchmarks.",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Ripple",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Nasdaq",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "California Unveils Breakthrough Project With Ripple, Coinbase, And MoonPay\nPositive Sentiment:\nVirtune launched a new Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq Stockholm, expanding institutional access to Coinbase-backed crypto benchmarks.",
      "distance": 20
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Ripple",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Stockholm",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "California Unveils Breakthrough Project With Ripple, Coinbase, And MoonPay\nPositive Sentiment:\nVirtune launched a new Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq Stockholm, expanding institutional access to Coinbase-backed crypto benchmarks.",
      "distance": 21
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Ripple",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Coinbase",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "California Unveils Breakthrough Project With Ripple, Coinbase, And MoonPay\nPositive Sentiment:\nVirtune launched a new Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq Stockholm, expanding institutional access to Coinbase-backed crypto benchmarks.",
      "distance": 27
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Coinbase",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "MoonPay",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "California Unveils Breakthrough Project With Ripple, Coinbase, And MoonPay\nPositive Sentiment:\nVirtune launched a new Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq Stockholm, expanding institutional access to Coinbase-backed crypto benchmarks.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Coinbase",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Virtune",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "California Unveils Breakthrough Project With Ripple, Coinbase, And MoonPay\nPositive Sentiment:\nVirtune launched a new Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq Stockholm, expanding institutional access to Coinbase-backed crypto benchmarks.",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Coinbase",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Nasdaq",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "California Unveils Breakthrough Project With Ripple, Coinbase, And MoonPay\nPositive Sentiment:\nVirtune launched a new Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq Stockholm, expanding institutional access to Coinbase-backed crypto benchmarks.",
      "distance": 18
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Coinbase",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Stockholm",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "California Unveils Breakthrough Project With Ripple, Coinbase, And MoonPay\nPositive Sentiment:\nVirtune launched a new Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq Stockholm, expanding institutional access to Coinbase-backed crypto benchmarks.",
      "distance": 19
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Coinbase",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Coinbase",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "California Unveils Breakthrough Project With Ripple, Coinbase, And MoonPay\nPositive Sentiment:\nVirtune launched a new Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq Stockholm, expanding institutional access to Coinbase-backed crypto benchmarks.",
      "distance": 25
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "MoonPay",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Virtune",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "California Unveils Breakthrough Project With Ripple, Coinbase, And MoonPay\nPositive Sentiment:\nVirtune launched a new Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq Stockholm, expanding institutional access to Coinbase-backed crypto benchmarks.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "MoonPay",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Nasdaq",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "California Unveils Breakthrough Project With Ripple, Coinbase, And MoonPay\nPositive Sentiment:\nVirtune launched a new Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq Stockholm, expanding institutional access to Coinbase-backed crypto benchmarks.",
      "distance": 15
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "MoonPay",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Stockholm",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "California Unveils Breakthrough Project With Ripple, Coinbase, And MoonPay\nPositive Sentiment:\nVirtune launched a new Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq Stockholm, expanding institutional access to Coinbase-backed crypto benchmarks.",
      "distance": 16
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "MoonPay",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Coinbase",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "California Unveils Breakthrough Project With Ripple, Coinbase, And MoonPay\nPositive Sentiment:\nVirtune launched a new Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq Stockholm, expanding institutional access to Coinbase-backed crypto benchmarks.",
      "distance": 22
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Virtune",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Nasdaq",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "California Unveils Breakthrough Project With Ripple, Coinbase, And MoonPay\nPositive Sentiment:\nVirtune launched a new Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq Stockholm, expanding institutional access to Coinbase-backed crypto benchmarks.",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Virtune",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Stockholm",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "California Unveils Breakthrough Project With Ripple, Coinbase, And MoonPay\nPositive Sentiment:\nVirtune launched a new Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq Stockholm, expanding institutional access to Coinbase-backed crypto benchmarks.",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Virtune",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Coinbase",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "California Unveils Breakthrough Project With Ripple, Coinbase, And MoonPay\nPositive Sentiment:\nVirtune launched a new Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq Stockholm, expanding institutional access to Coinbase-backed crypto benchmarks.",
      "distance": 16
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Nasdaq",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Stockholm",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "California Unveils Breakthrough Project With Ripple, Coinbase, And MoonPay\nPositive Sentiment:\nVirtune launched a new Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq Stockholm, expanding institutional access to Coinbase-backed crypto benchmarks.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Nasdaq",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Coinbase",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "California Unveils Breakthrough Project With Ripple, Coinbase, And MoonPay\nPositive Sentiment:\nVirtune launched a new Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq Stockholm, expanding institutional access to Coinbase-backed crypto benchmarks.",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Stockholm",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Coinbase",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "California Unveils Breakthrough Project With Ripple, Coinbase, And MoonPay\nPositive Sentiment:\nVirtune launched a new Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq Stockholm, expanding institutional access to Coinbase-backed crypto benchmarks.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Virtune",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Coinbase",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Virtune launches Virtune Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq Stockholm\nPositive Sentiment:\nBitcoin’s ongoing rally underpins crypto equities, with Coinbase among the top beneficiaries of the sector’s surge.\nBitcoin’s 2025 surge isn’t over yet: 5 reasons the rally could keep going\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 24
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Virtune",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "2025",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Virtune launches Virtune Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq Stockholm\nPositive Sentiment:\nBitcoin’s ongoing rally underpins crypto equities, with Coinbase among the top beneficiaries of the sector’s surge.\nBitcoin’s 2025 surge isn’t over yet: 5 reasons the rally could keep going\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 38
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Virtune",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "5",
      "entity2_type": "CARDINAL",
      "sentence": "Virtune launches Virtune Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq Stockholm\nPositive Sentiment:\nBitcoin’s ongoing rally underpins crypto equities, with Coinbase among the top beneficiaries of the sector’s surge.\nBitcoin’s 2025 surge isn’t over yet: 5 reasons the rally could keep going\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 45
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Coinbase",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "2025",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Virtune launches Virtune Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq Stockholm\nPositive Sentiment:\nBitcoin’s ongoing rally underpins crypto equities, with Coinbase among the top beneficiaries of the sector’s surge.\nBitcoin’s 2025 surge isn’t over yet: 5 reasons the rally could keep going\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 14
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Coinbase",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "5",
      "entity2_type": "CARDINAL",
      "sentence": "Virtune launches Virtune Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq Stockholm\nPositive Sentiment:\nBitcoin’s ongoing rally underpins crypto equities, with Coinbase among the top beneficiaries of the sector’s surge.\nBitcoin’s 2025 surge isn’t over yet: 5 reasons the rally could keep going\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 21
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "2025",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "5",
      "entity2_type": "CARDINAL",
      "sentence": "Virtune launches Virtune Coinbase 50 Index ETP on Nasdaq Stockholm\nPositive Sentiment:\nBitcoin’s ongoing rally underpins crypto equities, with Coinbase among the top beneficiaries of the sector’s surge.\nBitcoin’s 2025 surge isn’t over yet: 5 reasons the rally could keep going\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Zacks",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Coinbase",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "A Zacks commentary highlights crypto names including Coinbase as potential multi-year outperformers in a late-cycle tech bubble.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Zacks",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "multi",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "A Zacks commentary highlights crypto names including Coinbase as potential multi-year outperformers in a late-cycle tech bubble.",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Zacks",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "A Zacks commentary highlights crypto names including Coinbase as potential multi-year outperformers in a late-cycle tech bubble.",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Zacks",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "year",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "A Zacks commentary highlights crypto names including Coinbase as potential multi-year outperformers in a late-cycle tech bubble.",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Zacks",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "late",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "A Zacks commentary highlights crypto names including Coinbase as potential multi-year outperformers in a late-cycle tech bubble.",
      "distance": 15
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Zacks",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "A Zacks commentary highlights crypto names including Coinbase as potential multi-year outperformers in a late-cycle tech bubble.",
      "distance": 16
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Zacks",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "cycle",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "A Zacks commentary highlights crypto names including Coinbase as potential multi-year outperformers in a late-cycle tech bubble.",
      "distance": 17
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Coinbase",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "multi",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "A Zacks commentary highlights crypto names including Coinbase as potential multi-year outperformers in a late-cycle tech bubble.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Coinbase",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "A Zacks commentary highlights crypto names including Coinbase as potential multi-year outperformers in a late-cycle tech bubble.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Coinbase",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "year",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "A Zacks commentary highlights crypto names including Coinbase as potential multi-year outperformers in a late-cycle tech bubble.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Coinbase",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "late",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "A Zacks commentary highlights crypto names including Coinbase as potential multi-year outperformers in a late-cycle tech bubble.",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Coinbase",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "A Zacks commentary highlights crypto names including Coinbase as potential multi-year outperformers in a late-cycle tech bubble.",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Coinbase",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "cycle",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "A Zacks commentary highlights crypto names including Coinbase as potential multi-year outperformers in a late-cycle tech bubble.",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "multi",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "A Zacks commentary highlights crypto names including Coinbase as potential multi-year outperformers in a late-cycle tech bubble.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "multi",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "year",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "A Zacks commentary highlights crypto names including Coinbase as potential multi-year outperformers in a late-cycle tech bubble.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "multi",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "late",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "A Zacks commentary highlights crypto names including Coinbase as potential multi-year outperformers in a late-cycle tech bubble.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "multi",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "A Zacks commentary highlights crypto names including Coinbase as potential multi-year outperformers in a late-cycle tech bubble.",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "multi",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "cycle",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "A Zacks commentary highlights crypto names including Coinbase as potential multi-year outperformers in a late-cycle tech bubble.",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "year",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "A Zacks commentary highlights crypto names including Coinbase as potential multi-year outperformers in a late-cycle tech bubble.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "late",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "A Zacks commentary highlights crypto names including Coinbase as potential multi-year outperformers in a late-cycle tech bubble.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "A Zacks commentary highlights crypto names including Coinbase as potential multi-year outperformers in a late-cycle tech bubble.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "cycle",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "A Zacks commentary highlights crypto names including Coinbase as potential multi-year outperformers in a late-cycle tech bubble.",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "year",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "late",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "A Zacks commentary highlights crypto names including Coinbase as potential multi-year outperformers in a late-cycle tech bubble.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "year",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "A Zacks commentary highlights crypto names including Coinbase as potential multi-year outperformers in a late-cycle tech bubble.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "year",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "cycle",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "A Zacks commentary highlights crypto names including Coinbase as potential multi-year outperformers in a late-cycle tech bubble.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
