{
  "ticker": "CVS",
  "entities": [
    {
      "text": "CVS Health Corporation",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 0,
      "end": 22,
      "sentence": "CVS Health Corporation (NYSE:CVS) shares are seeing mixed movement as investors weigh recent strategic expansions and upbeat analyst revisions against hefty legal penalties.",
      "context": "CVS Health Corporation (NYSE:CVS) shares are seeing mixed movement as in",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "CVS",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 29,
      "end": 32,
      "sentence": "CVS Health Corporation (NYSE:CVS) shares are seeing mixed movement as investors weigh recent strategic expansions and upbeat analyst revisions against hefty legal penalties.",
      "context": "CVS Health Corporation (NYSE:CVS) shares are seeing mixed movement as investors we",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "CVS",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 194,
      "end": 197,
      "sentence": "CVS opened the first of 64 Pacific Northwest locations acquired from Rite Aid, expanding its retail footprint in a key region.",
      "context": "gainst hefty legal penalties.\nPositive Sentiment:\nCVS opened the first of 64 Pacific Northwest location",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "first",
      "label": "ORDINAL",
      "start": 209,
      "end": 214,
      "sentence": "CVS opened the first of 64 Pacific Northwest locations acquired from Rite Aid, expanding its retail footprint in a key region.",
      "context": "gal penalties.\nPositive Sentiment:\nCVS opened the first of 64 Pacific Northwest locations acquired from R",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "64",
      "label": "CARDINAL",
      "start": 218,
      "end": 220,
      "sentence": "CVS opened the first of 64 Pacific Northwest locations acquired from Rite Aid, expanding its retail footprint in a key region.",
      "context": "ties.\nPositive Sentiment:\nCVS opened the first of 64 Pacific Northwest locations acquired from Rite Ai",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Pacific Northwest",
      "label": "LOC",
      "start": 221,
      "end": 238,
      "sentence": "CVS opened the first of 64 Pacific Northwest locations acquired from Rite Aid, expanding its retail footprint in a key region.",
      "context": "s.\nPositive Sentiment:\nCVS opened the first of 64 Pacific Northwest locations acquired from Rite Aid, expanding its r",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": true,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Rite Aid",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 263,
      "end": 271,
      "sentence": "CVS opened the first of 64 Pacific Northwest locations acquired from Rite Aid, expanding its retail footprint in a key region.",
      "context": "t of 64 Pacific Northwest locations acquired from Rite Aid, expanding its retail footprint in a key region.",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "CVS",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 321,
      "end": 324,
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "context": ", expanding its retail footprint in a key region.\nCVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite A",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "first",
      "label": "ORDINAL",
      "start": 331,
      "end": 336,
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "context": "g its retail footprint in a key region.\nCVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "64",
      "label": "CARDINAL",
      "start": 340,
      "end": 342,
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "context": "ail footprint in a key region.\nCVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentim",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "PNW",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 343,
      "end": 346,
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "context": "footprint in a key region.\nCVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Rite Aid",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 368,
      "end": 376,
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "context": "n.\nCVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Leerink Partnrs",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 397,
      "end": 412,
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "context": "stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Healt",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "FY2025",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 424,
      "end": 430,
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "context": "id\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per sha",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "CVS Health",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 453,
      "end": 463,
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "context": "k Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "6.18",
      "label": "MONEY",
      "start": 468,
      "end": 472,
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "context": "d its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": true
    },
    {
      "text": "Leerink",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 514,
      "end": 521,
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "context": "to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Partnrs",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 522,
      "end": 529,
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "context": "per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "CVS Health",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 560,
      "end": 570,
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "context": "ns.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:\nThe female-focused supplement",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Health & Her",
      "label": "PRODUCT",
      "start": 627,
      "end": 639,
      "sentence": "The female-focused supplement brand Health & Her was added to CVS shelves, enhancing the retailer’s private-brand portfolio.\nHealth & Her enters CVS shelves\nPositive Sentiment:\nThrough a $1 million, five-year grant from the CVS Health Foundation, EngageWell and Rocket Doctor launched a virtual Healthy Aging program for adults over 60 in New York City.",
      "context": "ve Sentiment:\nThe female-focused supplement brand Health & Her was added to CVS shelves, enhancing the retailer’",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "CVS",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 653,
      "end": 656,
      "sentence": "The female-focused supplement brand Health & Her was added to CVS shelves, enhancing the retailer’s private-brand portfolio.\nHealth & Her enters CVS shelves\nPositive Sentiment:\nThrough a $1 million, five-year grant from the CVS Health Foundation, EngageWell and Rocket Doctor launched a virtual Healthy Aging program for adults over 60 in New York City.",
      "context": "ocused supplement brand Health & Her was added to CVS shelves, enhancing the retailer’s private-brand p",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Health & Her",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 716,
      "end": 728,
      "sentence": "The female-focused supplement brand Health & Her was added to CVS shelves, enhancing the retailer’s private-brand portfolio.\nHealth & Her enters CVS shelves\nPositive Sentiment:\nThrough a $1 million, five-year grant from the CVS Health Foundation, EngageWell and Rocket Doctor launched a virtual Healthy Aging program for adults over 60 in New York City.",
      "context": "enhancing the retailer’s private-brand portfolio.\nHealth & Her enters CVS shelves\nPositive Sentiment:\nThrough a",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "CVS",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 736,
      "end": 739,
      "sentence": "The female-focused supplement brand Health & Her was added to CVS shelves, enhancing the retailer’s private-brand portfolio.\nHealth & Her enters CVS shelves\nPositive Sentiment:\nThrough a $1 million, five-year grant from the CVS Health Foundation, EngageWell and Rocket Doctor launched a virtual Healthy Aging program for adults over 60 in New York City.",
      "context": "er’s private-brand portfolio.\nHealth & Her enters CVS shelves\nPositive Sentiment:\nThrough a $1 million,",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "$1 million",
      "label": "MONEY",
      "start": 778,
      "end": 788,
      "sentence": "The female-focused supplement brand Health & Her was added to CVS shelves, enhancing the retailer’s private-brand portfolio.\nHealth & Her enters CVS shelves\nPositive Sentiment:\nThrough a $1 million, five-year grant from the CVS Health Foundation, EngageWell and Rocket Doctor launched a virtual Healthy Aging program for adults over 60 in New York City.",
      "context": "enters CVS shelves\nPositive Sentiment:\nThrough a $1 million, five-year grant from the CVS Health Foundation,",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": true
    },
    {
      "text": "five-year",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 790,
      "end": 799,
      "sentence": "The female-focused supplement brand Health & Her was added to CVS shelves, enhancing the retailer’s private-brand portfolio.\nHealth & Her enters CVS shelves\nPositive Sentiment:\nThrough a $1 million, five-year grant from the CVS Health Foundation, EngageWell and Rocket Doctor launched a virtual Healthy Aging program for adults over 60 in New York City.",
      "context": "shelves\nPositive Sentiment:\nThrough a $1 million, five-year grant from the CVS Health Foundation, EngageWell",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "the CVS Health Foundation",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 811,
      "end": 836,
      "sentence": "The female-focused supplement brand Health & Her was added to CVS shelves, enhancing the retailer’s private-brand portfolio.\nHealth & Her enters CVS shelves\nPositive Sentiment:\nThrough a $1 million, five-year grant from the CVS Health Foundation, EngageWell and Rocket Doctor launched a virtual Healthy Aging program for adults over 60 in New York City.",
      "context": "iment:\nThrough a $1 million, five-year grant from the CVS Health Foundation, EngageWell and Rocket Doctor launched a virtual",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "EngageWell",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 838,
      "end": 848,
      "sentence": "The female-focused supplement brand Health & Her was added to CVS shelves, enhancing the retailer’s private-brand portfolio.\nHealth & Her enters CVS shelves\nPositive Sentiment:\nThrough a $1 million, five-year grant from the CVS Health Foundation, EngageWell and Rocket Doctor launched a virtual Healthy Aging program for adults over 60 in New York City.",
      "context": ", five-year grant from the CVS Health Foundation, EngageWell and Rocket Doctor launched a virtual Healthy Agin",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Rocket Doctor",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 853,
      "end": 866,
      "sentence": "The female-focused supplement brand Health & Her was added to CVS shelves, enhancing the retailer’s private-brand portfolio.\nHealth & Her enters CVS shelves\nPositive Sentiment:\nThrough a $1 million, five-year grant from the CVS Health Foundation, EngageWell and Rocket Doctor launched a virtual Healthy Aging program for adults over 60 in New York City.",
      "context": "nt from the CVS Health Foundation, EngageWell and Rocket Doctor launched a virtual Healthy Aging program for adul",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "60",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 924,
      "end": 926,
      "sentence": "The female-focused supplement brand Health & Her was added to CVS shelves, enhancing the retailer’s private-brand portfolio.\nHealth & Her enters CVS shelves\nPositive Sentiment:\nThrough a $1 million, five-year grant from the CVS Health Foundation, EngageWell and Rocket Doctor launched a virtual Healthy Aging program for adults over 60 in New York City.",
      "context": "d a virtual Healthy Aging program for adults over 60 in New York City.\nEngageWell, Rocket Doctor, and",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "New York City",
      "label": "GPE",
      "start": 930,
      "end": 943,
      "sentence": "The female-focused supplement brand Health & Her was added to CVS shelves, enhancing the retailer’s private-brand portfolio.\nHealth & Her enters CVS shelves\nPositive Sentiment:\nThrough a $1 million, five-year grant from the CVS Health Foundation, EngageWell and Rocket Doctor launched a virtual Healthy Aging program for adults over 60 in New York City.",
      "context": "rtual Healthy Aging program for adults over 60 in New York City.\nEngageWell, Rocket Doctor, and CVS Health Founda",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": true,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "EngageWell",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 945,
      "end": 955,
      "sentence": "EngageWell, Rocket Doctor, and CVS Health Foundation Launch Virtual Healthy Aging Program for Adults over 60",
      "context": "ging program for adults over 60 in New York City.\nEngageWell, Rocket Doctor, and CVS Health Foundation Launch",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Rocket Doctor",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 957,
      "end": 970,
      "sentence": "EngageWell, Rocket Doctor, and CVS Health Foundation Launch Virtual Healthy Aging Program for Adults over 60",
      "context": "for adults over 60 in New York City.\nEngageWell, Rocket Doctor, and CVS Health Foundation Launch Virtual Healthy",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "CVS Health Foundation",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 976,
      "end": 997,
      "sentence": "EngageWell, Rocket Doctor, and CVS Health Foundation Launch Virtual Healthy Aging Program for Adults over 60",
      "context": "in New York City.\nEngageWell, Rocket Doctor, and CVS Health Foundation Launch Virtual Healthy Aging Program for Adults o",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "60",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 1051,
      "end": 1053,
      "sentence": "EngageWell, Rocket Doctor, and CVS Health Foundation Launch Virtual Healthy Aging Program for Adults over 60",
      "context": "nch Virtual Healthy Aging Program for Adults over 60\nNeutral Sentiment:\nCVS plans to appeal a $948.8 m",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "CVS",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1073,
      "end": 1076,
      "sentence": "CVS plans to appeal a $948.8 million judgment over alleged false prescription claims, aiming to overturn or reduce the penalty.",
      "context": "ing Program for Adults over 60\nNeutral Sentiment:\nCVS plans to appeal a $948.8 million judgment over al",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "$948.8 million",
      "label": "MONEY",
      "start": 1095,
      "end": 1109,
      "sentence": "CVS plans to appeal a $948.8 million judgment over alleged false prescription claims, aiming to overturn or reduce the penalty.",
      "context": "over 60\nNeutral Sentiment:\nCVS plans to appeal a $948.8 million judgment over alleged false prescription claims,",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": true
    },
    {
      "text": "CVS Health",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1201,
      "end": 1211,
      "sentence": "CVS Health plans to appeal $948.8 million judgement\nNeutral Sentiment:\nThe company announced plans to close 271 underperforming stores in 2025 as part of network optimization efforts.",
      "context": "claims, aiming to overturn or reduce the penalty.\nCVS Health plans to appeal $948.8 million judgement\nNeutral",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "$948.8 million",
      "label": "MONEY",
      "start": 1228,
      "end": 1242,
      "sentence": "CVS Health plans to appeal $948.8 million judgement\nNeutral Sentiment:\nThe company announced plans to close 271 underperforming stores in 2025 as part of network optimization efforts.",
      "context": "or reduce the penalty.\nCVS Health plans to appeal $948.8 million judgement\nNeutral Sentiment:\nThe company announce",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": true
    },
    {
      "text": "271",
      "label": "CARDINAL",
      "start": 1309,
      "end": 1312,
      "sentence": "CVS Health plans to appeal $948.8 million judgement\nNeutral Sentiment:\nThe company announced plans to close 271 underperforming stores in 2025 as part of network optimization efforts.",
      "context": "l Sentiment:\nThe company announced plans to close 271 underperforming stores in 2025 as part of network",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "2025",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 1339,
      "end": 1343,
      "sentence": "CVS Health plans to appeal $948.8 million judgement\nNeutral Sentiment:\nThe company announced plans to close 271 underperforming stores in 2025 as part of network optimization efforts.",
      "context": "nced plans to close 271 underperforming stores in 2025 as part of network optimization efforts.\nCVS Plan",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "CVS",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1385,
      "end": 1388,
      "sentence": "CVS Plans to Close 271 Stores in 2025\nNegative Sentiment:\nCVS’s long-term–care pharmacy arm, Omnicare, was fined $948 million for filling false prescriptions, increasing legal liabilities.\nCVS’ Omnicare fined $948M for filling false prescriptions\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "context": "in 2025 as part of network optimization efforts.\nCVS Plans to Close 271 Stores in 2025\nNegative Sentim",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "271",
      "label": "CARDINAL",
      "start": 1404,
      "end": 1407,
      "sentence": "CVS Plans to Close 271 Stores in 2025\nNegative Sentiment:\nCVS’s long-term–care pharmacy arm, Omnicare, was fined $948 million for filling false prescriptions, increasing legal liabilities.\nCVS’ Omnicare fined $948M for filling false prescriptions\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "context": "network optimization efforts.\nCVS Plans to Close 271 Stores in 2025\nNegative Sentiment:\nCVS’s long-ter",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "2025",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 1418,
      "end": 1422,
      "sentence": "CVS Plans to Close 271 Stores in 2025\nNegative Sentiment:\nCVS’s long-term–care pharmacy arm, Omnicare, was fined $948 million for filling false prescriptions, increasing legal liabilities.\nCVS’ Omnicare fined $948M for filling false prescriptions\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "context": "ization efforts.\nCVS Plans to Close 271 Stores in 2025\nNegative Sentiment:\nCVS’s long-term–care pharmacy",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "CVS",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1443,
      "end": 1446,
      "sentence": "CVS Plans to Close 271 Stores in 2025\nNegative Sentiment:\nCVS’s long-term–care pharmacy arm, Omnicare, was fined $948 million for filling false prescriptions, increasing legal liabilities.\nCVS’ Omnicare fined $948M for filling false prescriptions\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "context": "s to Close 271 Stores in 2025\nNegative Sentiment:\nCVS’s long-term–care pharmacy arm, Omnicare, was fine",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Omnicare",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1478,
      "end": 1486,
      "sentence": "CVS Plans to Close 271 Stores in 2025\nNegative Sentiment:\nCVS’s long-term–care pharmacy arm, Omnicare, was fined $948 million for filling false prescriptions, increasing legal liabilities.\nCVS’ Omnicare fined $948M for filling false prescriptions\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "context": "ive Sentiment:\nCVS’s long-term–care pharmacy arm, Omnicare, was fined $948 million for filling false prescri",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "$948 million",
      "label": "MONEY",
      "start": 1498,
      "end": 1510,
      "sentence": "CVS Plans to Close 271 Stores in 2025\nNegative Sentiment:\nCVS’s long-term–care pharmacy arm, Omnicare, was fined $948 million for filling false prescriptions, increasing legal liabilities.\nCVS’ Omnicare fined $948M for filling false prescriptions\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "context": "long-term–care pharmacy arm, Omnicare, was fined $948 million for filling false prescriptions, increasing legal",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": true
    },
    {
      "text": "CVS",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1574,
      "end": 1577,
      "sentence": "CVS Plans to Close 271 Stores in 2025\nNegative Sentiment:\nCVS’s long-term–care pharmacy arm, Omnicare, was fined $948 million for filling false prescriptions, increasing legal liabilities.\nCVS’ Omnicare fined $948M for filling false prescriptions\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "context": "alse prescriptions, increasing legal liabilities.\nCVS’ Omnicare fined $948M for filling false prescript",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Omnicare",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1579,
      "end": 1587,
      "sentence": "CVS Plans to Close 271 Stores in 2025\nNegative Sentiment:\nCVS’s long-term–care pharmacy arm, Omnicare, was fined $948 million for filling false prescriptions, increasing legal liabilities.\nCVS’ Omnicare fined $948M for filling false prescriptions\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "context": "prescriptions, increasing legal liabilities.\nCVS’ Omnicare fined $948M for filling false prescriptions\nNegat",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "$948M",
      "label": "MONEY",
      "start": 1594,
      "end": 1599,
      "sentence": "CVS Plans to Close 271 Stores in 2025\nNegative Sentiment:\nCVS’s long-term–care pharmacy arm, Omnicare, was fined $948 million for filling false prescriptions, increasing legal liabilities.\nCVS’ Omnicare fined $948M for filling false prescriptions\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "context": "increasing legal liabilities.\nCVS’ Omnicare fined $948M for filling false prescriptions\nNegative Sentimen",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": true
    },
    {
      "text": "CVS Health",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1676,
      "end": 1686,
      "sentence": "A federal court ordered CVS Health to pay $949 million in a fraud lawsuit related to invalid prescription claims, marking a major judgment against the company.",
      "context": "tions\nNegative Sentiment:\nA federal court ordered CVS Health to pay $949 million in a fraud lawsuit related to",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "$949 million",
      "label": "MONEY",
      "start": 1694,
      "end": 1706,
      "sentence": "A federal court ordered CVS Health to pay $949 million in a fraud lawsuit related to invalid prescription claims, marking a major judgment against the company.",
      "context": "timent:\nA federal court ordered CVS Health to pay $949 million in a fraud lawsuit related to invalid prescriptio",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": true
    },
    {
      "text": "CVS Health",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1812,
      "end": 1822,
      "sentence": "CVS Health ordered to pay $949M in fraud case\nPosted 1+ days ago\nAI Generated.",
      "context": "ms, marking a major judgment against the company.\nCVS Health ordered to pay $949M in fraud case\nPosted 1+ days",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "$949M",
      "label": "MONEY",
      "start": 1838,
      "end": 1843,
      "sentence": "CVS Health ordered to pay $949M in fraud case\nPosted 1+ days ago\nAI Generated.",
      "context": "nt against the company.\nCVS Health ordered to pay $949M in fraud case\nPosted 1+ days ago\nAI Generated. Ma",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": true
    },
    {
      "text": "1+ days ago",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 1865,
      "end": 1876,
      "sentence": "CVS Health ordered to pay $949M in fraud case\nPosted 1+ days ago\nAI Generated.",
      "context": "Health ordered to pay $949M in fraud case\nPosted 1+ days ago\nAI Generated. May Contain Errors.",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "AI",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1877,
      "end": 1879,
      "sentence": "CVS Health ordered to pay $949M in fraud case\nPosted 1+ days ago\nAI Generated.",
      "context": "red to pay $949M in fraud case\nPosted 1+ days ago\nAI Generated. May Contain Errors.",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    }
  ],
  "relationships": [
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "shares",
      "verb": "seeing",
      "object": "movement",
      "sentence": "CVS Health Corporation (NYSE:CVS) shares are seeing mixed movement as investors weigh recent strategic expansions and upbeat analyst revisions against hefty legal penalties.",
      "importance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "investors",
      "verb": "weigh",
      "object": "expansions",
      "sentence": "CVS Health Corporation (NYSE:CVS) shares are seeing mixed movement as investors weigh recent strategic expansions and upbeat analyst revisions against hefty legal penalties.",
      "importance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "CVS",
      "verb": "opened",
      "object": "first",
      "sentence": "CVS opened the first of 64 Pacific Northwest locations acquired from Rite Aid, expanding its retail footprint in a key region.",
      "importance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "CVS",
      "verb": "opens",
      "object": "first",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "importance": 20
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Partnrs",
      "verb": "raised",
      "object": "estimate",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "importance": 20
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Partnrs",
      "verb": "Raises",
      "object": "Estimates",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "importance": 20
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Health",
      "verb": "enters",
      "object": "shelves",
      "sentence": "The female-focused supplement brand Health & Her was added to CVS shelves, enhancing the retailer’s private-brand portfolio.\nHealth & Her enters CVS shelves\nPositive Sentiment:\nThrough a $1 million, five-year grant from the CVS Health Foundation, EngageWell and Rocket Doctor launched a virtual Healthy Aging program for adults over 60 in New York City.",
      "importance": 26
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "EngageWell",
      "verb": "launched",
      "object": "program",
      "sentence": "The female-focused supplement brand Health & Her was added to CVS shelves, enhancing the retailer’s private-brand portfolio.\nHealth & Her enters CVS shelves\nPositive Sentiment:\nThrough a $1 million, five-year grant from the CVS Health Foundation, EngageWell and Rocket Doctor launched a virtual Healthy Aging program for adults over 60 in New York City.",
      "importance": 26
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "EngageWell",
      "verb": "Launch",
      "object": "Program",
      "sentence": "EngageWell, Rocket Doctor, and CVS Health Foundation Launch Virtual Healthy Aging Program for Adults over 60",
      "importance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "company",
      "verb": "announced",
      "object": "plans",
      "sentence": "CVS Health plans to appeal $948.8 million judgement\nNeutral Sentiment:\nThe company announced plans to close 271 underperforming stores in 2025 as part of network optimization efforts.",
      "importance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Omnicare",
      "verb": "fined",
      "object": "M",
      "sentence": "CVS Plans to Close 271 Stores in 2025\nNegative Sentiment:\nCVS’s long-term–care pharmacy arm, Omnicare, was fined $948 million for filling false prescriptions, increasing legal liabilities.\nCVS’ Omnicare fined $948M for filling false prescriptions\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "importance": 14
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "court",
      "verb": "ordered",
      "object": "Health",
      "sentence": "A federal court ordered CVS Health to pay $949 million in a fraud lawsuit related to invalid prescription claims, marking a major judgment against the company.",
      "importance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "CVS",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Health",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS Health Corporation (NYSE:CVS) shares are seeing mixed movement as investors weigh recent strategic expansions and upbeat analyst revisions against hefty legal penalties.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "CVS",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Corporation",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS Health Corporation (NYSE:CVS) shares are seeing mixed movement as investors weigh recent strategic expansions and upbeat analyst revisions against hefty legal penalties.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "CVS",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "CVS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS Health Corporation (NYSE:CVS) shares are seeing mixed movement as investors weigh recent strategic expansions and upbeat analyst revisions against hefty legal penalties.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Health",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Corporation",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS Health Corporation (NYSE:CVS) shares are seeing mixed movement as investors weigh recent strategic expansions and upbeat analyst revisions against hefty legal penalties.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Health",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "CVS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS Health Corporation (NYSE:CVS) shares are seeing mixed movement as investors weigh recent strategic expansions and upbeat analyst revisions against hefty legal penalties.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Corporation",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "CVS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS Health Corporation (NYSE:CVS) shares are seeing mixed movement as investors weigh recent strategic expansions and upbeat analyst revisions against hefty legal penalties.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "CVS",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "first",
      "entity2_type": "ORDINAL",
      "sentence": "CVS opened the first of 64 Pacific Northwest locations acquired from Rite Aid, expanding its retail footprint in a key region.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "CVS",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "64",
      "entity2_type": "CARDINAL",
      "sentence": "CVS opened the first of 64 Pacific Northwest locations acquired from Rite Aid, expanding its retail footprint in a key region.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "CVS",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Pacific",
      "entity2_type": "LOC",
      "sentence": "CVS opened the first of 64 Pacific Northwest locations acquired from Rite Aid, expanding its retail footprint in a key region.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "CVS",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Northwest",
      "entity2_type": "LOC",
      "sentence": "CVS opened the first of 64 Pacific Northwest locations acquired from Rite Aid, expanding its retail footprint in a key region.",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "CVS",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Rite",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opened the first of 64 Pacific Northwest locations acquired from Rite Aid, expanding its retail footprint in a key region.",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "CVS",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Aid",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opened the first of 64 Pacific Northwest locations acquired from Rite Aid, expanding its retail footprint in a key region.",
      "distance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "first",
      "entity1_type": "ORDINAL",
      "entity2": "64",
      "entity2_type": "CARDINAL",
      "sentence": "CVS opened the first of 64 Pacific Northwest locations acquired from Rite Aid, expanding its retail footprint in a key region.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "first",
      "entity1_type": "ORDINAL",
      "entity2": "Pacific",
      "entity2_type": "LOC",
      "sentence": "CVS opened the first of 64 Pacific Northwest locations acquired from Rite Aid, expanding its retail footprint in a key region.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "first",
      "entity1_type": "ORDINAL",
      "entity2": "Northwest",
      "entity2_type": "LOC",
      "sentence": "CVS opened the first of 64 Pacific Northwest locations acquired from Rite Aid, expanding its retail footprint in a key region.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "first",
      "entity1_type": "ORDINAL",
      "entity2": "Rite",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opened the first of 64 Pacific Northwest locations acquired from Rite Aid, expanding its retail footprint in a key region.",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "first",
      "entity1_type": "ORDINAL",
      "entity2": "Aid",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opened the first of 64 Pacific Northwest locations acquired from Rite Aid, expanding its retail footprint in a key region.",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "64",
      "entity1_type": "CARDINAL",
      "entity2": "Pacific",
      "entity2_type": "LOC",
      "sentence": "CVS opened the first of 64 Pacific Northwest locations acquired from Rite Aid, expanding its retail footprint in a key region.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "64",
      "entity1_type": "CARDINAL",
      "entity2": "Northwest",
      "entity2_type": "LOC",
      "sentence": "CVS opened the first of 64 Pacific Northwest locations acquired from Rite Aid, expanding its retail footprint in a key region.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "64",
      "entity1_type": "CARDINAL",
      "entity2": "Rite",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opened the first of 64 Pacific Northwest locations acquired from Rite Aid, expanding its retail footprint in a key region.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "64",
      "entity1_type": "CARDINAL",
      "entity2": "Aid",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opened the first of 64 Pacific Northwest locations acquired from Rite Aid, expanding its retail footprint in a key region.",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Pacific",
      "entity1_type": "LOC",
      "entity2": "Northwest",
      "entity2_type": "LOC",
      "sentence": "CVS opened the first of 64 Pacific Northwest locations acquired from Rite Aid, expanding its retail footprint in a key region.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Pacific",
      "entity1_type": "LOC",
      "entity2": "Rite",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opened the first of 64 Pacific Northwest locations acquired from Rite Aid, expanding its retail footprint in a key region.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Pacific",
      "entity1_type": "LOC",
      "entity2": "Aid",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opened the first of 64 Pacific Northwest locations acquired from Rite Aid, expanding its retail footprint in a key region.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Northwest",
      "entity1_type": "LOC",
      "entity2": "Rite",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opened the first of 64 Pacific Northwest locations acquired from Rite Aid, expanding its retail footprint in a key region.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Northwest",
      "entity1_type": "LOC",
      "entity2": "Aid",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opened the first of 64 Pacific Northwest locations acquired from Rite Aid, expanding its retail footprint in a key region.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Rite",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Aid",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opened the first of 64 Pacific Northwest locations acquired from Rite Aid, expanding its retail footprint in a key region.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "CVS",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "first",
      "entity2_type": "ORDINAL",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "CVS",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "64",
      "entity2_type": "CARDINAL",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "CVS",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "PNW",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "CVS",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Rite",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "CVS",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Aid",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "CVS",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Leerink",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 16
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "CVS",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Partnrs",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 17
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "CVS",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "FY2025",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 20
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "CVS",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "CVS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 24
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "CVS",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Health",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 25
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "CVS",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "6.18",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 28
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "CVS",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Leerink",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 37
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "CVS",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Partnrs",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 38
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "CVS",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "CVS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 43
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "CVS",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Health",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 44
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "first",
      "entity1_type": "ORDINAL",
      "entity2": "64",
      "entity2_type": "CARDINAL",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "first",
      "entity1_type": "ORDINAL",
      "entity2": "PNW",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "first",
      "entity1_type": "ORDINAL",
      "entity2": "Rite",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "first",
      "entity1_type": "ORDINAL",
      "entity2": "Aid",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "first",
      "entity1_type": "ORDINAL",
      "entity2": "Leerink",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 14
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "first",
      "entity1_type": "ORDINAL",
      "entity2": "Partnrs",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 15
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "first",
      "entity1_type": "ORDINAL",
      "entity2": "FY2025",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 18
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "first",
      "entity1_type": "ORDINAL",
      "entity2": "CVS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 22
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "first",
      "entity1_type": "ORDINAL",
      "entity2": "Health",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 23
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "first",
      "entity1_type": "ORDINAL",
      "entity2": "6.18",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 26
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "first",
      "entity1_type": "ORDINAL",
      "entity2": "Leerink",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 35
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "first",
      "entity1_type": "ORDINAL",
      "entity2": "Partnrs",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 36
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "first",
      "entity1_type": "ORDINAL",
      "entity2": "CVS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 41
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "first",
      "entity1_type": "ORDINAL",
      "entity2": "Health",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 42
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "64",
      "entity1_type": "CARDINAL",
      "entity2": "PNW",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "64",
      "entity1_type": "CARDINAL",
      "entity2": "Rite",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "64",
      "entity1_type": "CARDINAL",
      "entity2": "Aid",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "64",
      "entity1_type": "CARDINAL",
      "entity2": "Leerink",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "64",
      "entity1_type": "CARDINAL",
      "entity2": "Partnrs",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 13
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "64",
      "entity1_type": "CARDINAL",
      "entity2": "FY2025",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 16
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "64",
      "entity1_type": "CARDINAL",
      "entity2": "CVS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 20
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "64",
      "entity1_type": "CARDINAL",
      "entity2": "Health",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 21
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "64",
      "entity1_type": "CARDINAL",
      "entity2": "6.18",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 24
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "64",
      "entity1_type": "CARDINAL",
      "entity2": "Leerink",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 33
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "64",
      "entity1_type": "CARDINAL",
      "entity2": "Partnrs",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 34
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "64",
      "entity1_type": "CARDINAL",
      "entity2": "CVS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 39
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "64",
      "entity1_type": "CARDINAL",
      "entity2": "Health",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 40
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "PNW",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Rite",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "PNW",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Aid",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "PNW",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Leerink",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "PNW",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Partnrs",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "PNW",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "FY2025",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 15
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "PNW",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "CVS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 19
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "PNW",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Health",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 20
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "PNW",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "6.18",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 23
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "PNW",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Leerink",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 32
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "PNW",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Partnrs",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 33
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "PNW",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "CVS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 38
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "PNW",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Health",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 39
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Rite",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Aid",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Rite",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Leerink",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Rite",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Partnrs",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Rite",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "FY2025",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Rite",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "CVS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 15
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Rite",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Health",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 16
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Rite",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "6.18",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 19
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Rite",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Leerink",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 28
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Rite",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Partnrs",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 29
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Rite",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "CVS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 34
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Rite",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Health",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 35
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Aid",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Leerink",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Aid",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Partnrs",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Aid",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "FY2025",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Aid",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "CVS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 14
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Aid",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Health",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 15
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Aid",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "6.18",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 18
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Aid",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Leerink",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 27
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Aid",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Partnrs",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 28
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Aid",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "CVS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 33
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Aid",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Health",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 34
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Leerink",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Partnrs",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Leerink",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "FY2025",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Leerink",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "CVS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Leerink",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Health",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Leerink",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "6.18",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Leerink",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Leerink",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 21
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Leerink",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Partnrs",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 22
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Leerink",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "CVS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 27
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Leerink",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Health",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 28
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Partnrs",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "FY2025",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Partnrs",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "CVS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Partnrs",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Health",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Partnrs",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "6.18",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Partnrs",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Leerink",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 20
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Partnrs",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Partnrs",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 21
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Partnrs",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "CVS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 26
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Partnrs",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Health",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 27
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "FY2025",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "CVS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "FY2025",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "Health",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "FY2025",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "6.18",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "FY2025",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "Leerink",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 17
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "FY2025",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "Partnrs",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 18
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "FY2025",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "CVS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 23
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "FY2025",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "Health",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 24
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "CVS",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Health",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "CVS",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "6.18",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "CVS",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Leerink",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 13
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "CVS",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Partnrs",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 14
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "CVS",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "CVS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 19
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "CVS",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Health",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 20
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Health",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "6.18",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Health",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Leerink",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Health",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Partnrs",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 13
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Health",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "CVS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 18
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Health",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Health",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 19
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "6.18",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "Leerink",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "6.18",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "Partnrs",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "6.18",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "CVS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 15
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "6.18",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "Health",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "CVS opens first of 64 PNW stores acquired from Rite Aid\nPositive Sentiment:\nLeerink Partnrs raised its FY2025 earnings estimate for CVS Health to $6.18 per share, above consensus expectations.\nLeerink Partnrs Raises Earnings Estimates for CVS Health\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 16
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Leerink",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Partnrs",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
