{
  "ticker": "FCX",
  "entities": [
    {
      "text": "Freeport-McMoRan Inc.",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 0,
      "end": 21,
      "sentence": "Freeport-McMoRan Inc. (FCX) stock sentiment today is shaped by a mix of bullish analyst forecasts, upcoming earnings expectations and cautious commentary on copper demand.",
      "context": "Freeport-McMoRan Inc. (FCX) stock sentiment today is shaped by a mix of",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "FCX",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 23,
      "end": 26,
      "sentence": "Freeport-McMoRan Inc. (FCX) stock sentiment today is shaped by a mix of bullish analyst forecasts, upcoming earnings expectations and cautious commentary on copper demand.",
      "context": "Freeport-McMoRan Inc. (FCX) stock sentiment today is shaped by a mix of bull",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "today",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 44,
      "end": 49,
      "sentence": "Freeport-McMoRan Inc. (FCX) stock sentiment today is shaped by a mix of bullish analyst forecasts, upcoming earnings expectations and cautious commentary on copper demand.",
      "context": "Freeport-McMoRan Inc. (FCX) stock sentiment today is shaped by a mix of bullish analyst forecasts,",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "~15%",
      "label": "PERCENT",
      "start": 224,
      "end": 228,
      "sentence": "Analysts forecast an additional ~15% upside for FCX shares ahead of its Q2 earnings, citing a strong balance sheet (debt-to-equity ~0.30%) and rising copper demand under U.S. tariff and infrastructure tailwinds.",
      "context": "sitive Sentiment:\nAnalysts forecast an additional ~15% upside for FCX shares ahead of its Q2 earnings, c",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": true
    },
    {
      "text": "FCX",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 240,
      "end": 243,
      "sentence": "Analysts forecast an additional ~15% upside for FCX shares ahead of its Q2 earnings, citing a strong balance sheet (debt-to-equity ~0.30%) and rising copper demand under U.S. tariff and infrastructure tailwinds.",
      "context": ":\nAnalysts forecast an additional ~15% upside for FCX shares ahead of its Q2 earnings, citing a strong",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Q2",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 264,
      "end": 266,
      "sentence": "Analysts forecast an additional ~15% upside for FCX shares ahead of its Q2 earnings, citing a strong balance sheet (debt-to-equity ~0.30%) and rising copper demand under U.S. tariff and infrastructure tailwinds.",
      "context": "dditional ~15% upside for FCX shares ahead of its Q2 earnings, citing a strong balance sheet (debt-to-",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "~0.30%",
      "label": "PERCENT",
      "start": 323,
      "end": 329,
      "sentence": "Analysts forecast an additional ~15% upside for FCX shares ahead of its Q2 earnings, citing a strong balance sheet (debt-to-equity ~0.30%) and rising copper demand under U.S. tariff and infrastructure tailwinds.",
      "context": "gs, citing a strong balance sheet (debt-to-equity ~0.30%) and rising copper demand under U.S. tariff and i",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": true
    },
    {
      "text": "U.S.",
      "label": "GPE",
      "start": 362,
      "end": 366,
      "sentence": "Analysts forecast an additional ~15% upside for FCX shares ahead of its Q2 earnings, citing a strong balance sheet (debt-to-equity ~0.30%) and rising copper demand under U.S. tariff and infrastructure tailwinds.",
      "context": "-to-equity ~0.30%) and rising copper demand under U.S. tariff and infrastructure tailwinds.\n3 Stocks Off",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": true,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "3",
      "label": "CARDINAL",
      "start": 404,
      "end": 405,
      "sentence": "3 Stocks Offering Diversification in Trump’s Tariff & Trade Reset\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "context": "d under U.S. tariff and infrastructure tailwinds.\n3 Stocks Offering Diversification in Trump’s Tariff",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Trump",
      "label": "PERSON",
      "start": 441,
      "end": 446,
      "sentence": "3 Stocks Offering Diversification in Trump’s Tariff & Trade Reset\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "context": "e tailwinds.\n3 Stocks Offering Diversification in Trump’s Tariff & Trade Reset\nPositive Sentiment:\nFCX is",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": true,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "FCX",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 490,
      "end": 493,
      "sentence": "FCX is positioned to beat Q2 earnings estimates thanks to favorable commodity prices and operational efficiency, potentially supporting further stock gains.",
      "context": "Trump’s Tariff & Trade Reset\nPositive Sentiment:\nFCX is positioned to beat Q2 earnings estimates thank",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Q2",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 516,
      "end": 518,
      "sentence": "FCX is positioned to beat Q2 earnings estimates thanks to favorable commodity prices and operational efficiency, potentially supporting further stock gains.",
      "context": "set\nPositive Sentiment:\nFCX is positioned to beat Q2 earnings estimates thanks to favorable commodity",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Freeport-McMoRan",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 647,
      "end": 663,
      "sentence": "Freeport-McMoRan (FCX) Expected to Beat Earnings Estimates\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "context": "ency, potentially supporting further stock gains.\nFreeport-McMoRan (FCX) Expected to Beat Earnings Estimates\nPositiv",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Zacks",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 728,
      "end": 733,
      "sentence": "A Zacks report highlights FCX as a top long-term growth stock given its scale in copper production and strong style scores.",
      "context": "to Beat Earnings Estimates\nPositive Sentiment:\nA Zacks report highlights FCX as a top long-term growth s",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "FCX",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 752,
      "end": 755,
      "sentence": "A Zacks report highlights FCX as a top long-term growth stock given its scale in copper production and strong style scores.",
      "context": "tes\nPositive Sentiment:\nA Zacks report highlights FCX as a top long-term growth stock given its scale i",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Freeport-McMoRan",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 854,
      "end": 870,
      "sentence": "Why Freeport-McMoRan (FCX) is a Top Growth Stock for the Long-Term\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "context": "in copper production and strong style scores.\nWhy Freeport-McMoRan (FCX) is a Top Growth Stock for the Long-Term\nNeu",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "FCX",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 953,
      "end": 956,
      "sentence": "MarketBeat notes FCX will report Q2 results on July 22, setting the stage for volatility around the release.",
      "context": "the Long-Term\nNeutral Sentiment:\nMarketBeat notes FCX will report Q2 results on July 22, setting the st",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Q2",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 969,
      "end": 971,
      "sentence": "MarketBeat notes FCX will report Q2 results on July 22, setting the stage for volatility around the release.",
      "context": "utral Sentiment:\nMarketBeat notes FCX will report Q2 results on July 22, setting the stage for volatil",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "July 22",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 983,
      "end": 990,
      "sentence": "MarketBeat notes FCX will report Q2 results on July 22, setting the stage for volatility around the release.",
      "context": "t:\nMarketBeat notes FCX will report Q2 results on July 22, setting the stage for volatility around the rele",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Freeport-McMoRan",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1045,
      "end": 1061,
      "sentence": "Freeport-McMoRan (FCX) to Release Earnings on Tuesday\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "context": "ting the stage for volatility around the release.\nFreeport-McMoRan (FCX) to Release Earnings on Tuesday\nNeutral Sent",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "FCX",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1063,
      "end": 1066,
      "sentence": "Freeport-McMoRan (FCX) to Release Earnings on Tuesday\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "context": "volatility around the release.\nFreeport-McMoRan (FCX) to Release Earnings on Tuesday\nNeutral Sentiment",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Tuesday",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 1091,
      "end": 1098,
      "sentence": "Freeport-McMoRan (FCX) to Release Earnings on Tuesday\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "context": "se.\nFreeport-McMoRan (FCX) to Release Earnings on Tuesday\nNeutral Sentiment:\nA Forbes preview outlines what",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Forbes",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1120,
      "end": 1126,
      "sentence": "A Forbes preview outlines what to expect from Freeport‐McMoRan's Q2, focusing on copper prices, production guidance and cost control.",
      "context": "Release Earnings on Tuesday\nNeutral Sentiment:\nA Forbes preview outlines what to expect from Freeport‐McM",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Q2",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 1183,
      "end": 1185,
      "sentence": "A Forbes preview outlines what to expect from Freeport‐McMoRan's Q2, focusing on copper prices, production guidance and cost control.",
      "context": "w outlines what to expect from Freeport‐McMoRan's Q2, focusing on copper prices, production guidance a",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Freeport-McMoRan",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1272,
      "end": 1288,
      "sentence": "What To Expect From Freeport-McMoRan Stock's Q2?",
      "context": "on guidance and cost control.\nWhat To Expect From Freeport-McMoRan Stock's Q2?\nNegative Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley do",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Q2",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 1297,
      "end": 1299,
      "sentence": "What To Expect From Freeport-McMoRan Stock's Q2?",
      "context": "rol.\nWhat To Expect From Freeport-McMoRan Stock's Q2?\nNegative Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley downgraded FC",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Morgan Stanley",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1321,
      "end": 1335,
      "sentence": "Negative Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley downgraded FCX from Overweight to Equal Weight, though raised its price target to $54, signaling tempered conviction despite bullish pricing.\nMorgan Stanley Downgrades Freeport-McMoRan (FCX)\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "context": "Freeport-McMoRan Stock's Q2?\nNegative Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley downgraded FCX from Overweight to Equal Weight, t",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "FCX",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1347,
      "end": 1350,
      "sentence": "Negative Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley downgraded FCX from Overweight to Equal Weight, though raised its price target to $54, signaling tempered conviction despite bullish pricing.\nMorgan Stanley Downgrades Freeport-McMoRan (FCX)\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "context": "Q2?\nNegative Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley downgraded FCX from Overweight to Equal Weight, though raised it",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "54",
      "label": "MONEY",
      "start": 1419,
      "end": 1421,
      "sentence": "Negative Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley downgraded FCX from Overweight to Equal Weight, though raised its price target to $54, signaling tempered conviction despite bullish pricing.\nMorgan Stanley Downgrades Freeport-McMoRan (FCX)\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "context": "Equal Weight, though raised its price target to $54, signaling tempered conviction despite bullish pr",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": true
    },
    {
      "text": "Morgan Stanley",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1478,
      "end": 1492,
      "sentence": "Negative Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley downgraded FCX from Overweight to Equal Weight, though raised its price target to $54, signaling tempered conviction despite bullish pricing.\nMorgan Stanley Downgrades Freeport-McMoRan (FCX)\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "context": "ling tempered conviction despite bullish pricing.\nMorgan Stanley Downgrades Freeport-McMoRan (FCX)\nNegative Sentim",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Freeport-McMoRan",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1504,
      "end": 1520,
      "sentence": "Negative Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley downgraded FCX from Overweight to Equal Weight, though raised its price target to $54, signaling tempered conviction despite bullish pricing.\nMorgan Stanley Downgrades Freeport-McMoRan (FCX)\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "context": "espite bullish pricing.\nMorgan Stanley Downgrades Freeport-McMoRan (FCX)\nNegative Sentiment:\nBarron's warns that FCX",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Barron's",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1547,
      "end": 1555,
      "sentence": "Barron's warns that FCX's strong copper-driven rally may have peaked, advising investors on exit strategies as momentum slows.\nFreeport-McMoRan Stock Has Been a Copper Winner.",
      "context": "grades Freeport-McMoRan (FCX)\nNegative Sentiment:\nBarron's warns that FCX's strong copper-driven rally may h",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Freeport-McMoRan",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1674,
      "end": 1690,
      "sentence": "Barron's warns that FCX's strong copper-driven rally may have peaked, advising investors on exit strategies as momentum slows.\nFreeport-McMoRan Stock Has Been a Copper Winner.",
      "context": "g investors on exit strategies as momentum slows.\nFreeport-McMoRan Stock Has Been a Copper Winner. How to Know When",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "SchaeffersResearch",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1769,
      "end": 1787,
      "sentence": "SchaeffersResearch warns that the so-called “Dr. Copper” signal may be faltering, suggesting near-term headwinds for copper producers like FCX.",
      "context": "er. How to Know When to Sell.\nNegative Sentiment:\nSchaeffersResearch warns that the so-called “Dr. Copper” signal may",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "FCX",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1908,
      "end": 1911,
      "sentence": "SchaeffersResearch warns that the so-called “Dr. Copper” signal may be faltering, suggesting near-term headwinds for copper producers like FCX.",
      "context": "ing near-term headwinds for copper producers like FCX.\n‘Dr. Copper?' Not So Fast, Says Signal\nNegative",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "CNBC",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1972,
      "end": 1976,
      "sentence": "CNBC's Jim Cramer advised viewers to pause trading FCX, implying caution amid recent volatility.",
      "context": "er?' Not So Fast, Says Signal\nNegative Sentiment:\nCNBC's Jim Cramer advised viewers to pause trading FCX",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Jim Cramer",
      "label": "PERSON",
      "start": 1979,
      "end": 1989,
      "sentence": "CNBC's Jim Cramer advised viewers to pause trading FCX, implying caution amid recent volatility.",
      "context": "t So Fast, Says Signal\nNegative Sentiment:\nCNBC's Jim Cramer advised viewers to pause trading FCX, implying ca",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": true,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Freeport-McMoran",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 2083,
      "end": 2099,
      "sentence": "Freeport-McMoran\nPosted 1h ago\nAI Generated.",
      "context": "ing caution amid recent volatility.\nStop Trading: Freeport-McMoran\nPosted 1h ago\nAI Generated. May Contain Errors.",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "1h ago",
      "label": "TIME",
      "start": 2107,
      "end": 2113,
      "sentence": "Freeport-McMoran\nPosted 1h ago\nAI Generated.",
      "context": "volatility.\nStop Trading: Freeport-McMoran\nPosted 1h ago\nAI Generated. May Contain Errors.",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    }
  ],
  "relationships": [
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Analysts",
      "verb": "forecast",
      "object": "upside",
      "sentence": "Analysts forecast an additional ~15% upside for FCX shares ahead of its Q2 earnings, citing a strong balance sheet (debt-to-equity ~0.30%) and rising copper demand under U.S. tariff and infrastructure tailwinds.",
      "importance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "report",
      "verb": "highlights",
      "object": "FCX",
      "sentence": "A Zacks report highlights FCX as a top long-term growth stock given its scale in copper production and strong style scores.",
      "importance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "FCX",
      "verb": "report",
      "object": "results",
      "sentence": "MarketBeat notes FCX will report Q2 results on July 22, setting the stage for volatility around the release.",
      "importance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "McMoRan",
      "verb": "Release",
      "object": "Earnings",
      "sentence": "Freeport-McMoRan (FCX) to Release Earnings on Tuesday\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "importance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Stanley",
      "verb": "downgraded",
      "object": "FCX",
      "sentence": "Negative Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley downgraded FCX from Overweight to Equal Weight, though raised its price target to $54, signaling tempered conviction despite bullish pricing.\nMorgan Stanley Downgrades Freeport-McMoRan (FCX)\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "importance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Stanley",
      "verb": "Downgrades",
      "object": "McMoRan",
      "sentence": "Negative Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley downgraded FCX from Overweight to Equal Weight, though raised its price target to $54, signaling tempered conviction despite bullish pricing.\nMorgan Stanley Downgrades Freeport-McMoRan (FCX)\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "importance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Cramer",
      "verb": "advised",
      "object": "viewers",
      "sentence": "CNBC's Jim Cramer advised viewers to pause trading FCX, implying caution amid recent volatility.",
      "importance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Freeport",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Freeport-McMoRan Inc. (FCX) stock sentiment today is shaped by a mix of bullish analyst forecasts, upcoming earnings expectations and cautious commentary on copper demand.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Freeport",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "McMoRan",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Freeport-McMoRan Inc. (FCX) stock sentiment today is shaped by a mix of bullish analyst forecasts, upcoming earnings expectations and cautious commentary on copper demand.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Freeport",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Inc.",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Freeport-McMoRan Inc. (FCX) stock sentiment today is shaped by a mix of bullish analyst forecasts, upcoming earnings expectations and cautious commentary on copper demand.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Freeport",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "FCX",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Freeport-McMoRan Inc. (FCX) stock sentiment today is shaped by a mix of bullish analyst forecasts, upcoming earnings expectations and cautious commentary on copper demand.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Freeport",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "today",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Freeport-McMoRan Inc. (FCX) stock sentiment today is shaped by a mix of bullish analyst forecasts, upcoming earnings expectations and cautious commentary on copper demand.",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "McMoRan",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Freeport-McMoRan Inc. (FCX) stock sentiment today is shaped by a mix of bullish analyst forecasts, upcoming earnings expectations and cautious commentary on copper demand.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Inc.",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Freeport-McMoRan Inc. (FCX) stock sentiment today is shaped by a mix of bullish analyst forecasts, upcoming earnings expectations and cautious commentary on copper demand.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "FCX",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Freeport-McMoRan Inc. (FCX) stock sentiment today is shaped by a mix of bullish analyst forecasts, upcoming earnings expectations and cautious commentary on copper demand.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "today",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Freeport-McMoRan Inc. (FCX) stock sentiment today is shaped by a mix of bullish analyst forecasts, upcoming earnings expectations and cautious commentary on copper demand.",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "McMoRan",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Inc.",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Freeport-McMoRan Inc. (FCX) stock sentiment today is shaped by a mix of bullish analyst forecasts, upcoming earnings expectations and cautious commentary on copper demand.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "McMoRan",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "FCX",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Freeport-McMoRan Inc. (FCX) stock sentiment today is shaped by a mix of bullish analyst forecasts, upcoming earnings expectations and cautious commentary on copper demand.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "McMoRan",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "today",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Freeport-McMoRan Inc. (FCX) stock sentiment today is shaped by a mix of bullish analyst forecasts, upcoming earnings expectations and cautious commentary on copper demand.",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Inc.",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "FCX",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Freeport-McMoRan Inc. (FCX) stock sentiment today is shaped by a mix of bullish analyst forecasts, upcoming earnings expectations and cautious commentary on copper demand.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Inc.",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "today",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Freeport-McMoRan Inc. (FCX) stock sentiment today is shaped by a mix of bullish analyst forecasts, upcoming earnings expectations and cautious commentary on copper demand.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "FCX",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "today",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Freeport-McMoRan Inc. (FCX) stock sentiment today is shaped by a mix of bullish analyst forecasts, upcoming earnings expectations and cautious commentary on copper demand.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "~15",
      "entity1_type": "PERCENT",
      "entity2": "%",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "Analysts forecast an additional ~15% upside for FCX shares ahead of its Q2 earnings, citing a strong balance sheet (debt-to-equity ~0.30%) and rising copper demand under U.S. tariff and infrastructure tailwinds.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "~15",
      "entity1_type": "PERCENT",
      "entity2": "FCX",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Analysts forecast an additional ~15% upside for FCX shares ahead of its Q2 earnings, citing a strong balance sheet (debt-to-equity ~0.30%) and rising copper demand under U.S. tariff and infrastructure tailwinds.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "~15",
      "entity1_type": "PERCENT",
      "entity2": "Q2",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Analysts forecast an additional ~15% upside for FCX shares ahead of its Q2 earnings, citing a strong balance sheet (debt-to-equity ~0.30%) and rising copper demand under U.S. tariff and infrastructure tailwinds.",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "~15",
      "entity1_type": "PERCENT",
      "entity2": "~0.30",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "Analysts forecast an additional ~15% upside for FCX shares ahead of its Q2 earnings, citing a strong balance sheet (debt-to-equity ~0.30%) and rising copper demand under U.S. tariff and infrastructure tailwinds.",
      "distance": 23
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "~15",
      "entity1_type": "PERCENT",
      "entity2": "%",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "Analysts forecast an additional ~15% upside for FCX shares ahead of its Q2 earnings, citing a strong balance sheet (debt-to-equity ~0.30%) and rising copper demand under U.S. tariff and infrastructure tailwinds.",
      "distance": 24
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "~15",
      "entity1_type": "PERCENT",
      "entity2": "U.S.",
      "entity2_type": "GPE",
      "sentence": "Analysts forecast an additional ~15% upside for FCX shares ahead of its Q2 earnings, citing a strong balance sheet (debt-to-equity ~0.30%) and rising copper demand under U.S. tariff and infrastructure tailwinds.",
      "distance": 31
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "%",
      "entity1_type": "PERCENT",
      "entity2": "FCX",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Analysts forecast an additional ~15% upside for FCX shares ahead of its Q2 earnings, citing a strong balance sheet (debt-to-equity ~0.30%) and rising copper demand under U.S. tariff and infrastructure tailwinds.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "%",
      "entity1_type": "PERCENT",
      "entity2": "Q2",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Analysts forecast an additional ~15% upside for FCX shares ahead of its Q2 earnings, citing a strong balance sheet (debt-to-equity ~0.30%) and rising copper demand under U.S. tariff and infrastructure tailwinds.",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "%",
      "entity1_type": "PERCENT",
      "entity2": "~0.30",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "Analysts forecast an additional ~15% upside for FCX shares ahead of its Q2 earnings, citing a strong balance sheet (debt-to-equity ~0.30%) and rising copper demand under U.S. tariff and infrastructure tailwinds.",
      "distance": 22
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "%",
      "entity1_type": "PERCENT",
      "entity2": "%",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "Analysts forecast an additional ~15% upside for FCX shares ahead of its Q2 earnings, citing a strong balance sheet (debt-to-equity ~0.30%) and rising copper demand under U.S. tariff and infrastructure tailwinds.",
      "distance": 23
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "%",
      "entity1_type": "PERCENT",
      "entity2": "U.S.",
      "entity2_type": "GPE",
      "sentence": "Analysts forecast an additional ~15% upside for FCX shares ahead of its Q2 earnings, citing a strong balance sheet (debt-to-equity ~0.30%) and rising copper demand under U.S. tariff and infrastructure tailwinds.",
      "distance": 30
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "FCX",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Q2",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Analysts forecast an additional ~15% upside for FCX shares ahead of its Q2 earnings, citing a strong balance sheet (debt-to-equity ~0.30%) and rising copper demand under U.S. tariff and infrastructure tailwinds.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "FCX",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "~0.30",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "Analysts forecast an additional ~15% upside for FCX shares ahead of its Q2 earnings, citing a strong balance sheet (debt-to-equity ~0.30%) and rising copper demand under U.S. tariff and infrastructure tailwinds.",
      "distance": 19
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "FCX",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "%",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "Analysts forecast an additional ~15% upside for FCX shares ahead of its Q2 earnings, citing a strong balance sheet (debt-to-equity ~0.30%) and rising copper demand under U.S. tariff and infrastructure tailwinds.",
      "distance": 20
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "FCX",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "U.S.",
      "entity2_type": "GPE",
      "sentence": "Analysts forecast an additional ~15% upside for FCX shares ahead of its Q2 earnings, citing a strong balance sheet (debt-to-equity ~0.30%) and rising copper demand under U.S. tariff and infrastructure tailwinds.",
      "distance": 27
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Q2",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "~0.30",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "Analysts forecast an additional ~15% upside for FCX shares ahead of its Q2 earnings, citing a strong balance sheet (debt-to-equity ~0.30%) and rising copper demand under U.S. tariff and infrastructure tailwinds.",
      "distance": 14
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Q2",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "%",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "Analysts forecast an additional ~15% upside for FCX shares ahead of its Q2 earnings, citing a strong balance sheet (debt-to-equity ~0.30%) and rising copper demand under U.S. tariff and infrastructure tailwinds.",
      "distance": 15
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Q2",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "U.S.",
      "entity2_type": "GPE",
      "sentence": "Analysts forecast an additional ~15% upside for FCX shares ahead of its Q2 earnings, citing a strong balance sheet (debt-to-equity ~0.30%) and rising copper demand under U.S. tariff and infrastructure tailwinds.",
      "distance": 22
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "~0.30",
      "entity1_type": "PERCENT",
      "entity2": "%",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "Analysts forecast an additional ~15% upside for FCX shares ahead of its Q2 earnings, citing a strong balance sheet (debt-to-equity ~0.30%) and rising copper demand under U.S. tariff and infrastructure tailwinds.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "~0.30",
      "entity1_type": "PERCENT",
      "entity2": "U.S.",
      "entity2_type": "GPE",
      "sentence": "Analysts forecast an additional ~15% upside for FCX shares ahead of its Q2 earnings, citing a strong balance sheet (debt-to-equity ~0.30%) and rising copper demand under U.S. tariff and infrastructure tailwinds.",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "%",
      "entity1_type": "PERCENT",
      "entity2": "U.S.",
      "entity2_type": "GPE",
      "sentence": "Analysts forecast an additional ~15% upside for FCX shares ahead of its Q2 earnings, citing a strong balance sheet (debt-to-equity ~0.30%) and rising copper demand under U.S. tariff and infrastructure tailwinds.",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "3",
      "entity1_type": "CARDINAL",
      "entity2": "Trump",
      "entity2_type": "PERSON",
      "sentence": "3 Stocks Offering Diversification in Trump’s Tariff & Trade Reset\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "FCX",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Q2",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "FCX is positioned to beat Q2 earnings estimates thanks to favorable commodity prices and operational efficiency, potentially supporting further stock gains.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Freeport",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Freeport-McMoRan (FCX) Expected to Beat Earnings Estimates\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Freeport",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "McMoRan",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Freeport-McMoRan (FCX) Expected to Beat Earnings Estimates\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "McMoRan",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Freeport-McMoRan (FCX) Expected to Beat Earnings Estimates\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Zacks",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "FCX",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "A Zacks report highlights FCX as a top long-term growth stock given its scale in copper production and strong style scores.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Freeport",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Why Freeport-McMoRan (FCX) is a Top Growth Stock for the Long-Term\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Freeport",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "McMoRan",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Why Freeport-McMoRan (FCX) is a Top Growth Stock for the Long-Term\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "McMoRan",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Why Freeport-McMoRan (FCX) is a Top Growth Stock for the Long-Term\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "FCX",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Q2",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "MarketBeat notes FCX will report Q2 results on July 22, setting the stage for volatility around the release.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "FCX",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "July",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "MarketBeat notes FCX will report Q2 results on July 22, setting the stage for volatility around the release.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "FCX",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "22",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "MarketBeat notes FCX will report Q2 results on July 22, setting the stage for volatility around the release.",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Q2",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "July",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "MarketBeat notes FCX will report Q2 results on July 22, setting the stage for volatility around the release.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Q2",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "22",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "MarketBeat notes FCX will report Q2 results on July 22, setting the stage for volatility around the release.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "July",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "22",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "MarketBeat notes FCX will report Q2 results on July 22, setting the stage for volatility around the release.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Freeport",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Freeport-McMoRan (FCX) to Release Earnings on Tuesday\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Freeport",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "McMoRan",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Freeport-McMoRan (FCX) to Release Earnings on Tuesday\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Freeport",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "FCX",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Freeport-McMoRan (FCX) to Release Earnings on Tuesday\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Freeport",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Tuesday",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Freeport-McMoRan (FCX) to Release Earnings on Tuesday\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "McMoRan",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Freeport-McMoRan (FCX) to Release Earnings on Tuesday\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "FCX",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Freeport-McMoRan (FCX) to Release Earnings on Tuesday\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Tuesday",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Freeport-McMoRan (FCX) to Release Earnings on Tuesday\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "McMoRan",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "FCX",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Freeport-McMoRan (FCX) to Release Earnings on Tuesday\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "McMoRan",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Tuesday",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Freeport-McMoRan (FCX) to Release Earnings on Tuesday\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "FCX",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Tuesday",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Freeport-McMoRan (FCX) to Release Earnings on Tuesday\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Forbes",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Q2",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "A Forbes preview outlines what to expect from Freeport‐McMoRan's Q2, focusing on copper prices, production guidance and cost control.",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Freeport",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "What To Expect From Freeport-McMoRan Stock's Q2?",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Freeport",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "McMoRan",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "What To Expect From Freeport-McMoRan Stock's Q2?",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Freeport",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Q2",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "What To Expect From Freeport-McMoRan Stock's Q2?",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "McMoRan",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "What To Expect From Freeport-McMoRan Stock's Q2?",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Q2",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "What To Expect From Freeport-McMoRan Stock's Q2?",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "McMoRan",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Q2",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "What To Expect From Freeport-McMoRan Stock's Q2?",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Morgan",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Stanley",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Negative Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley downgraded FCX from Overweight to Equal Weight, though raised its price target to $54, signaling tempered conviction despite bullish pricing.\nMorgan Stanley Downgrades Freeport-McMoRan (FCX)\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Morgan",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "FCX",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Negative Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley downgraded FCX from Overweight to Equal Weight, though raised its price target to $54, signaling tempered conviction despite bullish pricing.\nMorgan Stanley Downgrades Freeport-McMoRan (FCX)\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Morgan",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "54",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Negative Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley downgraded FCX from Overweight to Equal Weight, though raised its price target to $54, signaling tempered conviction despite bullish pricing.\nMorgan Stanley Downgrades Freeport-McMoRan (FCX)\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "distance": 17
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Morgan",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Morgan",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Negative Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley downgraded FCX from Overweight to Equal Weight, though raised its price target to $54, signaling tempered conviction despite bullish pricing.\nMorgan Stanley Downgrades Freeport-McMoRan (FCX)\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "distance": 27
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Morgan",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Stanley",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Negative Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley downgraded FCX from Overweight to Equal Weight, though raised its price target to $54, signaling tempered conviction despite bullish pricing.\nMorgan Stanley Downgrades Freeport-McMoRan (FCX)\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "distance": 28
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Morgan",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Freeport",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Negative Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley downgraded FCX from Overweight to Equal Weight, though raised its price target to $54, signaling tempered conviction despite bullish pricing.\nMorgan Stanley Downgrades Freeport-McMoRan (FCX)\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "distance": 30
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Morgan",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Negative Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley downgraded FCX from Overweight to Equal Weight, though raised its price target to $54, signaling tempered conviction despite bullish pricing.\nMorgan Stanley Downgrades Freeport-McMoRan (FCX)\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "distance": 31
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Morgan",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "McMoRan",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Negative Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley downgraded FCX from Overweight to Equal Weight, though raised its price target to $54, signaling tempered conviction despite bullish pricing.\nMorgan Stanley Downgrades Freeport-McMoRan (FCX)\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "distance": 32
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Stanley",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "FCX",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Negative Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley downgraded FCX from Overweight to Equal Weight, though raised its price target to $54, signaling tempered conviction despite bullish pricing.\nMorgan Stanley Downgrades Freeport-McMoRan (FCX)\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Stanley",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "54",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Negative Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley downgraded FCX from Overweight to Equal Weight, though raised its price target to $54, signaling tempered conviction despite bullish pricing.\nMorgan Stanley Downgrades Freeport-McMoRan (FCX)\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "distance": 16
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Stanley",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Morgan",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Negative Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley downgraded FCX from Overweight to Equal Weight, though raised its price target to $54, signaling tempered conviction despite bullish pricing.\nMorgan Stanley Downgrades Freeport-McMoRan (FCX)\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "distance": 26
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Stanley",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Stanley",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Negative Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley downgraded FCX from Overweight to Equal Weight, though raised its price target to $54, signaling tempered conviction despite bullish pricing.\nMorgan Stanley Downgrades Freeport-McMoRan (FCX)\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "distance": 27
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Stanley",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Freeport",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Negative Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley downgraded FCX from Overweight to Equal Weight, though raised its price target to $54, signaling tempered conviction despite bullish pricing.\nMorgan Stanley Downgrades Freeport-McMoRan (FCX)\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "distance": 29
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Stanley",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Negative Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley downgraded FCX from Overweight to Equal Weight, though raised its price target to $54, signaling tempered conviction despite bullish pricing.\nMorgan Stanley Downgrades Freeport-McMoRan (FCX)\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "distance": 30
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Stanley",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "McMoRan",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Negative Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley downgraded FCX from Overweight to Equal Weight, though raised its price target to $54, signaling tempered conviction despite bullish pricing.\nMorgan Stanley Downgrades Freeport-McMoRan (FCX)\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "distance": 31
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "FCX",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "54",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Negative Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley downgraded FCX from Overweight to Equal Weight, though raised its price target to $54, signaling tempered conviction despite bullish pricing.\nMorgan Stanley Downgrades Freeport-McMoRan (FCX)\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "distance": 14
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "FCX",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Morgan",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Negative Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley downgraded FCX from Overweight to Equal Weight, though raised its price target to $54, signaling tempered conviction despite bullish pricing.\nMorgan Stanley Downgrades Freeport-McMoRan (FCX)\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "distance": 24
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "FCX",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Stanley",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Negative Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley downgraded FCX from Overweight to Equal Weight, though raised its price target to $54, signaling tempered conviction despite bullish pricing.\nMorgan Stanley Downgrades Freeport-McMoRan (FCX)\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "distance": 25
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "FCX",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Freeport",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Negative Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley downgraded FCX from Overweight to Equal Weight, though raised its price target to $54, signaling tempered conviction despite bullish pricing.\nMorgan Stanley Downgrades Freeport-McMoRan (FCX)\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "distance": 27
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "FCX",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Negative Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley downgraded FCX from Overweight to Equal Weight, though raised its price target to $54, signaling tempered conviction despite bullish pricing.\nMorgan Stanley Downgrades Freeport-McMoRan (FCX)\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "distance": 28
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "FCX",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "McMoRan",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Negative Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley downgraded FCX from Overweight to Equal Weight, though raised its price target to $54, signaling tempered conviction despite bullish pricing.\nMorgan Stanley Downgrades Freeport-McMoRan (FCX)\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "distance": 29
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "54",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "Morgan",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Negative Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley downgraded FCX from Overweight to Equal Weight, though raised its price target to $54, signaling tempered conviction despite bullish pricing.\nMorgan Stanley Downgrades Freeport-McMoRan (FCX)\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "54",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "Stanley",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Negative Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley downgraded FCX from Overweight to Equal Weight, though raised its price target to $54, signaling tempered conviction despite bullish pricing.\nMorgan Stanley Downgrades Freeport-McMoRan (FCX)\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "54",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "Freeport",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Negative Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley downgraded FCX from Overweight to Equal Weight, though raised its price target to $54, signaling tempered conviction despite bullish pricing.\nMorgan Stanley Downgrades Freeport-McMoRan (FCX)\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "distance": 13
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "54",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Negative Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley downgraded FCX from Overweight to Equal Weight, though raised its price target to $54, signaling tempered conviction despite bullish pricing.\nMorgan Stanley Downgrades Freeport-McMoRan (FCX)\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "distance": 14
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "54",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "McMoRan",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Negative Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley downgraded FCX from Overweight to Equal Weight, though raised its price target to $54, signaling tempered conviction despite bullish pricing.\nMorgan Stanley Downgrades Freeport-McMoRan (FCX)\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "distance": 15
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Morgan",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Stanley",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Negative Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley downgraded FCX from Overweight to Equal Weight, though raised its price target to $54, signaling tempered conviction despite bullish pricing.\nMorgan Stanley Downgrades Freeport-McMoRan (FCX)\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Morgan",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Freeport",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Negative Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley downgraded FCX from Overweight to Equal Weight, though raised its price target to $54, signaling tempered conviction despite bullish pricing.\nMorgan Stanley Downgrades Freeport-McMoRan (FCX)\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Morgan",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Negative Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley downgraded FCX from Overweight to Equal Weight, though raised its price target to $54, signaling tempered conviction despite bullish pricing.\nMorgan Stanley Downgrades Freeport-McMoRan (FCX)\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Morgan",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "McMoRan",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Negative Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley downgraded FCX from Overweight to Equal Weight, though raised its price target to $54, signaling tempered conviction despite bullish pricing.\nMorgan Stanley Downgrades Freeport-McMoRan (FCX)\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Stanley",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Freeport",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Negative Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley downgraded FCX from Overweight to Equal Weight, though raised its price target to $54, signaling tempered conviction despite bullish pricing.\nMorgan Stanley Downgrades Freeport-McMoRan (FCX)\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Stanley",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Negative Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley downgraded FCX from Overweight to Equal Weight, though raised its price target to $54, signaling tempered conviction despite bullish pricing.\nMorgan Stanley Downgrades Freeport-McMoRan (FCX)\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Stanley",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "McMoRan",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Negative Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley downgraded FCX from Overweight to Equal Weight, though raised its price target to $54, signaling tempered conviction despite bullish pricing.\nMorgan Stanley Downgrades Freeport-McMoRan (FCX)\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Freeport",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Negative Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley downgraded FCX from Overweight to Equal Weight, though raised its price target to $54, signaling tempered conviction despite bullish pricing.\nMorgan Stanley Downgrades Freeport-McMoRan (FCX)\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Freeport",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "McMoRan",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Negative Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley downgraded FCX from Overweight to Equal Weight, though raised its price target to $54, signaling tempered conviction despite bullish pricing.\nMorgan Stanley Downgrades Freeport-McMoRan (FCX)\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "McMoRan",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Negative Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley downgraded FCX from Overweight to Equal Weight, though raised its price target to $54, signaling tempered conviction despite bullish pricing.\nMorgan Stanley Downgrades Freeport-McMoRan (FCX)\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Barron",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "'s",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Barron's warns that FCX's strong copper-driven rally may have peaked, advising investors on exit strategies as momentum slows.\nFreeport-McMoRan Stock Has Been a Copper Winner.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Barron",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Freeport",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Barron's warns that FCX's strong copper-driven rally may have peaked, advising investors on exit strategies as momentum slows.\nFreeport-McMoRan Stock Has Been a Copper Winner.",
      "distance": 25
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Barron",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Barron's warns that FCX's strong copper-driven rally may have peaked, advising investors on exit strategies as momentum slows.\nFreeport-McMoRan Stock Has Been a Copper Winner.",
      "distance": 26
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Barron",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "McMoRan",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Barron's warns that FCX's strong copper-driven rally may have peaked, advising investors on exit strategies as momentum slows.\nFreeport-McMoRan Stock Has Been a Copper Winner.",
      "distance": 27
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "'s",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Freeport",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Barron's warns that FCX's strong copper-driven rally may have peaked, advising investors on exit strategies as momentum slows.\nFreeport-McMoRan Stock Has Been a Copper Winner.",
      "distance": 24
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "'s",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Barron's warns that FCX's strong copper-driven rally may have peaked, advising investors on exit strategies as momentum slows.\nFreeport-McMoRan Stock Has Been a Copper Winner.",
      "distance": 25
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "'s",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "McMoRan",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Barron's warns that FCX's strong copper-driven rally may have peaked, advising investors on exit strategies as momentum slows.\nFreeport-McMoRan Stock Has Been a Copper Winner.",
      "distance": 26
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Freeport",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Barron's warns that FCX's strong copper-driven rally may have peaked, advising investors on exit strategies as momentum slows.\nFreeport-McMoRan Stock Has Been a Copper Winner.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Freeport",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "McMoRan",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Barron's warns that FCX's strong copper-driven rally may have peaked, advising investors on exit strategies as momentum slows.\nFreeport-McMoRan Stock Has Been a Copper Winner.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "McMoRan",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Barron's warns that FCX's strong copper-driven rally may have peaked, advising investors on exit strategies as momentum slows.\nFreeport-McMoRan Stock Has Been a Copper Winner.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "SchaeffersResearch",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "FCX",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "SchaeffersResearch warns that the so-called “Dr. Copper” signal may be faltering, suggesting near-term headwinds for copper producers like FCX.",
      "distance": 25
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "CNBC",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Jim",
      "entity2_type": "PERSON",
      "sentence": "CNBC's Jim Cramer advised viewers to pause trading FCX, implying caution amid recent volatility.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "CNBC",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Cramer",
      "entity2_type": "PERSON",
      "sentence": "CNBC's Jim Cramer advised viewers to pause trading FCX, implying caution amid recent volatility.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Jim",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "Cramer",
      "entity2_type": "PERSON",
      "sentence": "CNBC's Jim Cramer advised viewers to pause trading FCX, implying caution amid recent volatility.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Freeport",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Freeport-McMoran\nPosted 1h ago\nAI Generated.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Freeport",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "McMoran",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Freeport-McMoran\nPosted 1h ago\nAI Generated.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Freeport",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "1h",
      "entity2_type": "TIME",
      "sentence": "Freeport-McMoran\nPosted 1h ago\nAI Generated.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Freeport",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "ago",
      "entity2_type": "TIME",
      "sentence": "Freeport-McMoran\nPosted 1h ago\nAI Generated.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "McMoran",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Freeport-McMoran\nPosted 1h ago\nAI Generated.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "1h",
      "entity2_type": "TIME",
      "sentence": "Freeport-McMoran\nPosted 1h ago\nAI Generated.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "ago",
      "entity2_type": "TIME",
      "sentence": "Freeport-McMoran\nPosted 1h ago\nAI Generated.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "McMoran",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "1h",
      "entity2_type": "TIME",
      "sentence": "Freeport-McMoran\nPosted 1h ago\nAI Generated.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "McMoran",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "ago",
      "entity2_type": "TIME",
      "sentence": "Freeport-McMoran\nPosted 1h ago\nAI Generated.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "1h",
      "entity1_type": "TIME",
      "entity2": "ago",
      "entity2_type": "TIME",
      "sentence": "Freeport-McMoran\nPosted 1h ago\nAI Generated.",
      "distance": 1
    }
  ],
  "key_phrases": [
    {
      "text": "a mix",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "bullish analyst forecasts",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "upcoming earnings expectations",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "financial_metric"
    },
    {
      "text": "cautious commentary",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "copper demand",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "Positive Sentiment",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "an additional ~15% upside",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "FCX shares",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "market_term"
    },
    {
      "text": "its Q2 earnings",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "financial_metric"
    },
    {
      "text": "a strong balance sheet",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "rising copper demand",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "U.S. tariff and infrastructure tailwinds",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "3 Stocks",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "market_term"
    },
    {
      "text": "Trump’s Tariff & Trade Reset",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "Positive Sentiment",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "Q2 earnings estimates",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "financial_metric"
    },
    {
      "text": "favorable commodity prices",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "operational efficiency",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "further stock gains",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "market_term"
    },
    {
      "text": "Earnings Estimates",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "financial_metric"
    },
    {
      "text": "A Zacks report",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "a top long-term growth stock",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "market_term"
    },
    {
      "text": "its scale",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "copper production",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "strong style scores",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "a Top Growth Stock",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "market_term"
    },
    {
      "text": "the Long-Term",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "Neutral Sentiment",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "Q2 results",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "the stage",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "the release",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "Neutral Sentiment",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "A Forbes preview",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "Freeport‐McMoRan's Q2",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "copper prices",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "production guidance",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "cost control",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "Freeport-McMoRan Stock's Q2",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "market_term"
    },
    {
      "text": "Negative Sentiment",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "Morgan Stanley",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "Equal Weight",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "its price target",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "tempered conviction",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "bullish pricing",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "Morgan Stanley",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "Negative Sentiment",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "FCX's strong copper-driven rally",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "exit strategies",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "Freeport-McMoRan Stock",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "market_term"
    },
    {
      "text": "a Copper Winner",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "Negative Sentiment",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "the so-called “Dr. Copper” signal",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "near-term headwinds",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "copper producers",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "Negative Sentiment",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "CNBC's Jim Cramer",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "recent volatility",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "$54,",
      "type": "pattern",
      "category": "money"
    },
    {
      "text": "15%",
      "type": "pattern",
      "category": "percentage"
    },
    {
      "text": "0.30%",
      "type": "pattern",
      "category": "percentage"
    },
    {
      "text": "earnings",
      "type": "pattern",
      "category": "financial_metric"
    },
    {
      "text": "earnings",
      "type": "pattern",
      "category": "financial_metric"
    },
    {
      "text": "earnings",
      "type": "pattern",
      "category": "financial_metric"
    },
    {
      "text": "Earnings",
      "type": "pattern",
      "category": "financial_metric"
    },
    {
      "text": "growth",
      "type": "pattern",
      "category": "financial_metric"
    },
    {
      "text": "Growth",
      "type": "pattern",
      "category": "financial_metric"
    },
    {
      "text": "Earnings",
      "type": "pattern",
      "category": "financial_metric"
    },
    {
      "text": "stock",
      "type": "pattern",
      "category": "market_term"
    },
    {
      "text": "stock",
      "type": "pattern",
      "category": "market_term"
    },
    {
      "text": "stock",
      "type": "pattern",
      "category": "market_term"
    },
    {
      "text": "Stock",
      "type": "pattern",
      "category": "market_term"
    },
    {
      "text": "Stock",
      "type": "pattern",
      "category": "market_term"
    },
    {
      "text": "Stock",
      "type": "pattern",
      "category": "market_term"
    },
    {
      "text": "trading",
      "type": "pattern",
      "category": "market_term"
    },
    {
      "text": "Trading",
      "type": "pattern",
      "category": "market_term"
    }
  ],
  "important_sentences": [
    {
      "text": "Negative Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley downgraded FCX from Overweight to Equal Weight, though raised its price target to $54, signaling tempered conviction despite bullish pricing.\nMorgan Stanley Downgrades Freeport-McMoRan (FCX)\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "importance_score": 42,
      "entity_count": 9,
      "financial_keyword_count": 1,
      "money_count": 1,
      "company_count": 4,
      "sentiment": "negative"
    },
    {
      "text": "Analysts forecast an additional ~15% upside for FCX shares ahead of its Q2 earnings, citing a strong balance sheet (debt-to-equity ~0.30%) and rising copper demand under U.S. tariff and infrastructure tailwinds.",
      "importance_score": 33,
      "entity_count": 7,
      "financial_keyword_count": 5,
      "money_count": 0,
      "company_count": 1,
      "sentiment": "positive"
    },
    {
      "text": "Freeport-McMoRan Inc. (FCX) stock sentiment today is shaped by a mix of bullish analyst forecasts, upcoming earnings expectations and cautious commentary on copper demand.",
      "importance_score": 29,
      "entity_count": 6,
      "financial_keyword_count": 3,
      "money_count": 0,
      "company_count": 2,
      "sentiment": "neutral"
    },
    {
      "text": "Barron's warns that FCX's strong copper-driven rally may have peaked, advising investors on exit strategies as momentum slows.\nFreeport-McMoRan Stock Has Been a Copper Winner.",
      "importance_score": 27,
      "entity_count": 5,
      "financial_keyword_count": 3,
      "money_count": 0,
      "company_count": 2,
      "sentiment": "positive"
    },
    {
      "text": "A Zacks report highlights FCX as a top long-term growth stock given its scale in copper production and strong style scores.",
      "importance_score": 24,
      "entity_count": 2,
      "financial_keyword_count": 4,
      "money_count": 0,
      "company_count": 2,
      "sentiment": "positive"
    },
    {
      "text": "Freeport-McMoRan (FCX) to Release Earnings on Tuesday\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "importance_score": 21,
      "entity_count": 5,
      "financial_keyword_count": 1,
      "money_count": 0,
      "company_count": 2,
      "sentiment": "neutral"
    },
    {
      "text": "Why Freeport-McMoRan (FCX) is a Top Growth Stock for the Long-Term\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "importance_score": 19,
      "entity_count": 3,
      "financial_keyword_count": 3,
      "money_count": 0,
      "company_count": 1,
      "sentiment": "positive"
    },
    {
      "text": "MarketBeat notes FCX will report Q2 results on July 22, setting the stage for volatility around the release.",
      "importance_score": 18,
      "entity_count": 4,
      "financial_keyword_count": 2,
      "money_count": 0,
      "company_count": 1,
      "sentiment": "neutral"
    },
    {
      "text": "FCX is positioned to beat Q2 earnings estimates thanks to favorable commodity prices and operational efficiency, potentially supporting further stock gains.",
      "importance_score": 17,
      "entity_count": 2,
      "financial_keyword_count": 3,
      "money_count": 0,
      "company_count": 1,
      "sentiment": "neutral"
    },
    {
      "text": "Freeport-McMoran\nPosted 1h ago\nAI Generated.",
      "importance_score": 17,
      "entity_count": 5,
      "financial_keyword_count": 1,
      "money_count": 0,
      "company_count": 1,
      "sentiment": "neutral"
    }
  ],
  "entity_statistics": {
    "total_entities": 39,
    "unique_entities": 22,
    "type_counts": {
      "ORG": 23,
      "DATE": 8,
      "PERCENT": 2,
      "GPE": 1,
      "CARDINAL": 1,
      "PERSON": 2,
      "MONEY": 1,
      "TIME": 1
    },
    "type_distribution": {
      "ORG": 0.5897435897435898,
      "DATE": 0.20512820512820512,
      "PERCENT": 0.05128205128205128,
      "GPE": 0.02564102564102564,
      "CARDINAL": 0.02564102564102564,
      "PERSON": 0.05128205128205128,
      "MONEY": 0.02564102564102564,
      "TIME": 0.02564102564102564
    },
    "most_common_entities": [
      [
        "FCX",
        8
      ],
      [
        "Freeport-McMoRan",
        6
      ],
      [
        "Q2",
        5
      ],
      [
        "Morgan Stanley",
        2
      ],
      [
        "Freeport-McMoRan Inc.",
        1
      ],
      [
        "today",
        1
      ],
      [
        "~15%",
        1
      ],
      [
        "~0.30%",
        1
      ],
      [
        "U.S.",
        1
      ],
      [
        "3",
        1
      ]
    ],
    "entity_types_found": [
      "ORG",
      "DATE",
      "PERCENT",
      "GPE",
      "CARDINAL",
      "PERSON",
      "MONEY",
      "TIME"
    ],
    "company_entities": 23,
    "person_entities": 2,
    "financial_entities": 3,
    "entity_density": 0.12956810631229235
  },
  "financial_analysis": {
    "money_amounts": [
      "54"
    ],
    "percentages": [
      "~15%",
      "~0.30%"
    ],
    "companies": [
      "Freeport-McMoRan Inc.",
      "FCX",
      "FCX",
      "FCX",
      "Freeport-McMoRan",
      "Zacks",
      "FCX",
      "Freeport-McMoRan",
      "FCX",
      "Freeport-McMoRan",
      "FCX",
      "Forbes",
      "Freeport-McMoRan",
      "Morgan Stanley",
      "FCX",
      "Morgan Stanley",
      "Freeport-McMoRan",
      "Barron's",
      "Freeport-McMoRan",
      "SchaeffersResearch",
      "FCX",
      "CNBC",
      "Freeport-McMoran"
    ],
    "people": [
      "Trump",
      "Jim Cramer"
    ],
    "dates": [
      "today",
      "Q2",
      "Q2",
      "Q2",
      "July 22",
      "Tuesday",
      "Q2",
      "Q2"
    ],
    "financial_terms": [
      "Stock",
      "Growth",
      "Earnings",
      "earnings",
      "stock",
      "growth",
      "trading",
      "Trading"
    ],
    "financial_metrics": [],
    "market_indicators": [
      "rally",
      "price",
      "target",
      "volatility"
    ]
  },
  "temporal_analysis": {
    "dates": [
      "today",
      "Q2",
      "Q2",
      "Q2",
      "July 22",
      "Tuesday",
      "Q2",
      "Q2"
    ],
    "time_expressions": [
      "1h ago"
    ],
    "temporal_relationships": [
      "upcoming",
      "today",
      "recent"
    ],
    "quarters": [
      "Q2",
      "Q2",
      "Q2",
      "Q2",
      "Q2"
    ],
    "years": [],
    "time_periods": []
  },
  "sentiment_analysis": {
    "positive_words": 11,
    "negative_words": 4,
    "positive_ratio": 0.036544850498338874,
    "negative_ratio": 0.013289036544850499,
    "sentiment_score": 0.023255813953488375,
    "sentiment_label": "positive",
    "sentiment_strength": 0.023255813953488375,
    "confidence": 0.23255813953488375
  },
  "industry_analysis": {
    "dominant_industry": "mining",
    "industry_scores": {
      "tech": 1,
      "finance": 2,
      "healthcare": 0,
      "energy": 0,
      "retail": 0,
      "automotive": 0,
      "media": 0,
      "industrial": 0,
      "real_estate": 0,
      "telecom": 0,
      "food_beverage": 0,
      "travel": 0,
      "education": 0,
      "professional": 0,
      "mining": 9,
      "aerospace": 0,
      "environmental": 0,
      "cannabis": 0
    },
    "confidence": 0.75
  },
  "market_analysis": {
    "market_sentiment": "bullish",
    "bullish_indicators": 3,
    "bearish_indicators": 0,
    "market_conditions": {
      "volatility": "high",
      "volume": "normal",
      "trend": "bullish"
    },
    "trading_activity": "normal"
  },
  "competitor_analysis": {
    "companies_mentioned": [
      "Freeport-McMoRan Inc.",
      "FCX",
      "FCX",
      "FCX",
      "Freeport-McMoRan",
      "Zacks",
      "FCX",
      "Freeport-McMoRan",
      "FCX",
      "Freeport-McMoRan",
      "FCX",
      "Forbes",
      "Freeport-McMoRan",
      "Morgan Stanley",
      "FCX",
      "Morgan Stanley",
      "Freeport-McMoRan",
      "Barron's",
      "Freeport-McMoRan",
      "SchaeffersResearch",
      "FCX",
      "CNBC",
      "Freeport-McMoran"
    ],
    "competitive_context": [],
    "competitor_count": 23,
    "has_competitive_language": false
  },
  "risk_analysis": {
    "risk_sentences": [
      "MarketBeat notes FCX will report Q2 results on July 22, setting the stage for volatility around the release.",
      "CNBC's Jim Cramer advised viewers to pause trading FCX, implying caution amid recent volatility."
    ],
    "risk_count": 2,
    "risk_level": "medium"
  },
  "opportunity_analysis": {
    "opportunity_sentences": [
      "FCX is positioned to beat Q2 earnings estimates thanks to favorable commodity prices and operational efficiency, potentially supporting further stock gains.",
      "A Zacks report highlights FCX as a top long-term growth stock given its scale in copper production and strong style scores.",
      "Why Freeport-McMoRan (FCX) is a Top Growth Stock for the Long-Term\nNeutral Sentiment:"
    ],
    "opportunity_count": 3,
    "opportunity_level": "medium"
  },
  "processing_metadata": {
    "timestamp": "2025-07-17T02:45:37.781937",
    "model_used": "en_core_web_trf",
    "text_length": 2147
  }
}