{
  "ticker": "FOX",
  "entities": [
    {
      "text": "Fox Corporation",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 0,
      "end": 15,
      "sentence": "Fox Corporation (FOX) shares have moved higher as its news division continues to deliver strong viewership, underpinned by Fox News Channel’s recent primetime success.",
      "context": "Fox Corporation (FOX) shares have moved higher as its news divisi",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "FOX",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 17,
      "end": 20,
      "sentence": "Fox Corporation (FOX) shares have moved higher as its news division continues to deliver strong viewership, underpinned by Fox News Channel’s recent primetime success.",
      "context": "Fox Corporation (FOX) shares have moved higher as its news division co",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Fox News Channel’s",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 123,
      "end": 141,
      "sentence": "Fox Corporation (FOX) shares have moved higher as its news division continues to deliver strong viewership, underpinned by Fox News Channel’s recent primetime success.",
      "context": "nues to deliver strong viewership, underpinned by Fox News Channel’s recent primetime success. Below is a summary of r",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Fox News Channel",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 288,
      "end": 304,
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "context": "influence investor sentiment:\nPositive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "NBC",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 313,
      "end": 316,
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "context": "ent:\nPositive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third conse",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "CBS",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 318,
      "end": 321,
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "context": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutiv",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "ABC",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 326,
      "end": 329,
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "context": "Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week,",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "the third consecutive week",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 351,
      "end": 377,
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "context": "nel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Fox News Channel",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 477,
      "end": 493,
      "sentence": "Fox News Channel Ratings Report",
      "context": "supporting higher advertising revenue potential.\nFox News Channel Ratings Report\nNeutral Sentiment:\nFoxtons Group P",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Foxtons Group PLC",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 528,
      "end": 545,
      "sentence": "Neutral Sentiment:\nFoxtons Group PLC announced a shift in its major shareholder holdings, an update relevant to UK real estate investors but not directly tied to Fox Corporation.",
      "context": "ox News Channel Ratings Report\nNeutral Sentiment:\nFoxtons Group PLC announced a shift in its major shareholder holdin",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "UK",
      "label": "GPE",
      "start": 621,
      "end": 623,
      "sentence": "Neutral Sentiment:\nFoxtons Group PLC announced a shift in its major shareholder holdings, an update relevant to UK real estate investors but not directly tied to Fox Corporation.",
      "context": "major shareholder holdings, an update relevant to UK real estate investors but not directly tied to Fo",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": true,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Fox Corporation",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 671,
      "end": 686,
      "sentence": "Neutral Sentiment:\nFoxtons Group PLC announced a shift in its major shareholder holdings, an update relevant to UK real estate investors but not directly tied to Fox Corporation.",
      "context": "UK real estate investors but not directly tied to Fox Corporation.\nFoxtons Shareholder Update\nNeutral Sentiment:\nCa",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Foxtons",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 688,
      "end": 695,
      "sentence": "Foxtons Shareholder Update\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "context": "vestors but not directly tied to Fox Corporation.\nFoxtons Shareholder Update\nNeutral Sentiment:\nCaitlin Cla",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Caitlin Clark’s",
      "label": "PERSON",
      "start": 734,
      "end": 749,
      "sentence": "Caitlin Clark’s heated exchange with a WNBA referee has generated buzz around Fox Sports’ live coverage, though it’s unclear if this will drive significant ad revenue gains.",
      "context": "on.\nFoxtons Shareholder Update\nNeutral Sentiment:\nCaitlin Clark’s heated exchange with a WNBA referee has generated",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": true,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "WNBA",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 773,
      "end": 777,
      "sentence": "Caitlin Clark’s heated exchange with a WNBA referee has generated buzz around Fox Sports’ live coverage, though it’s unclear if this will drive significant ad revenue gains.",
      "context": "Sentiment:\nCaitlin Clark’s heated exchange with a WNBA referee has generated buzz around Fox Sports’ liv",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Fox Sports’",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 812,
      "end": 823,
      "sentence": "Caitlin Clark’s heated exchange with a WNBA referee has generated buzz around Fox Sports’ live coverage, though it’s unclear if this will drive significant ad revenue gains.",
      "context": "nge with a WNBA referee has generated buzz around Fox Sports’ live coverage, though it’s unclear if this will d",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Caitlin Clark",
      "label": "PERSON",
      "start": 908,
      "end": 921,
      "sentence": "Caitlin Clark Confrontation\nNeutral Sentiment:\nA tragic workplace accident at a frozen burrito factory highlights general industrial safety concerns but does not directly involve Fox Corporation.\nFactory Accident Report\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "context": "if this will drive significant ad revenue gains.\nCaitlin Clark Confrontation\nNeutral Sentiment:\nA tragic workpla",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": true,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Fox Corporation",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1087,
      "end": 1102,
      "sentence": "Caitlin Clark Confrontation\nNeutral Sentiment:\nA tragic workplace accident at a frozen burrito factory highlights general industrial safety concerns but does not directly involve Fox Corporation.\nFactory Accident Report\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "context": "ial safety concerns but does not directly involve Fox Corporation.\nFactory Accident Report\nNeutral Sentiment:\nNewt",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Newt Gingrich’s",
      "label": "PERSON",
      "start": 1147,
      "end": 1162,
      "sentence": "Newt Gingrich’s comment on the shrinking role for moderates in the Democratic Party is political analysis content with limited impact on Fox’s core advertising base.",
      "context": "ation.\nFactory Accident Report\nNeutral Sentiment:\nNewt Gingrich’s comment on the shrinking role for moderates in th",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": true,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "the Democratic Party",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1210,
      "end": 1230,
      "sentence": "Newt Gingrich’s comment on the shrinking role for moderates in the Democratic Party is political analysis content with limited impact on Fox’s core advertising base.",
      "context": "’s comment on the shrinking role for moderates in the Democratic Party is political analysis content with limited impact",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Fox",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1284,
      "end": 1287,
      "sentence": "Newt Gingrich’s comment on the shrinking role for moderates in the Democratic Party is political analysis content with limited impact on Fox’s core advertising base.",
      "context": "political analysis content with limited impact on Fox’s core advertising base.\nGingrich on Moderates\nNe",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Gingrich",
      "label": "PERSON",
      "start": 1313,
      "end": 1321,
      "sentence": "Gingrich on Moderates\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "context": "th limited impact on Fox’s core advertising base.\nGingrich on Moderates\nNeutral Sentiment:\nDonald Trump chal",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": true,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Donald Trump",
      "label": "PERSON",
      "start": 1354,
      "end": 1366,
      "sentence": "Donald Trump challenged Representatives Ocasio-Cortez and Crockett to an intelligence test, a political headline likely to drive short‐term traffic but not affect Fox Corporation’s fundamentals.",
      "context": "ng base.\nGingrich on Moderates\nNeutral Sentiment:\nDonald Trump challenged Representatives Ocasio-Cortez and Croc",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": true,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Ocasio-Cortez",
      "label": "PERSON",
      "start": 1394,
      "end": 1407,
      "sentence": "Donald Trump challenged Representatives Ocasio-Cortez and Crockett to an intelligence test, a political headline likely to drive short‐term traffic but not affect Fox Corporation’s fundamentals.",
      "context": "entiment:\nDonald Trump challenged Representatives Ocasio-Cortez and Crockett to an intelligence test, a political",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": true,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Crockett",
      "label": "PERSON",
      "start": 1412,
      "end": 1420,
      "sentence": "Donald Trump challenged Representatives Ocasio-Cortez and Crockett to an intelligence test, a political headline likely to drive short‐term traffic but not affect Fox Corporation’s fundamentals.",
      "context": "rump challenged Representatives Ocasio-Cortez and Crockett to an intelligence test, a political headline lik",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": true,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Fox Corporation’s",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1517,
      "end": 1534,
      "sentence": "Donald Trump challenged Representatives Ocasio-Cortez and Crockett to an intelligence test, a political headline likely to drive short‐term traffic but not affect Fox Corporation’s fundamentals.",
      "context": "likely to drive short‐term traffic but not affect Fox Corporation’s fundamentals.\nTrump IQ Challenge\nNeutral Sentimen",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Trump",
      "label": "PERSON",
      "start": 1631,
      "end": 1636,
      "sentence": "An analysis of state-by-state savings under Trump’s proposed “big beautiful bill” may attract policy-minded viewers but has no direct bearing on Fox Corporation’s operations.",
      "context": "ment:\nAn analysis of state-by-state savings under Trump’s proposed “big beautiful bill” may attract polic",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": true,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Fox Corporation’s",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1732,
      "end": 1749,
      "sentence": "An analysis of state-by-state savings under Trump’s proposed “big beautiful bill” may attract policy-minded viewers but has no direct bearing on Fox Corporation’s operations.",
      "context": "olicy-minded viewers but has no direct bearing on Fox Corporation’s operations.\nTrump Bill Savings Breakdown\nNeutral",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Trump Bill",
      "label": "LAW",
      "start": 1762,
      "end": 1772,
      "sentence": "Trump Bill Savings Breakdown\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "context": "o direct bearing on Fox Corporation’s operations.\nTrump Bill Savings Breakdown\nNeutral Sentiment:\nAn illegal-m",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Fox",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1903,
      "end": 1906,
      "sentence": "An illegal-migrant plea in a fatal crash case is coverage of national news, unlikely to move Fox’s ad revenues beyond regular traffic.",
      "context": "se is coverage of national news, unlikely to move Fox’s ad revenues beyond regular traffic.\nCrime Plea",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Trump",
      "label": "PERSON",
      "start": 1984,
      "end": 1989,
      "sentence": "Trump’s $9 billion clawback bill passed its first Senate hurdle, a political development that may boost Fox News viewership but won’t immediately impact Fox Corporation’s top line.",
      "context": "r traffic.\nCrime Plea Coverage\nNeutral Sentiment:\nTrump’s $9 billion clawback bill passed its first Senat",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": true,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "$9 billion",
      "label": "MONEY",
      "start": 1992,
      "end": 2002,
      "sentence": "Trump’s $9 billion clawback bill passed its first Senate hurdle, a political development that may boost Fox News viewership but won’t immediately impact Fox Corporation’s top line.",
      "context": "c.\nCrime Plea Coverage\nNeutral Sentiment:\nTrump’s $9 billion clawback bill passed its first Senate hurdle, a p",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": true
    },
    {
      "text": "first",
      "label": "ORDINAL",
      "start": 2028,
      "end": 2033,
      "sentence": "Trump’s $9 billion clawback bill passed its first Senate hurdle, a political development that may boost Fox News viewership but won’t immediately impact Fox Corporation’s top line.",
      "context": "ment:\nTrump’s $9 billion clawback bill passed its first Senate hurdle, a political development that may b",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Senate",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 2034,
      "end": 2040,
      "sentence": "Trump’s $9 billion clawback bill passed its first Senate hurdle, a political development that may boost Fox News viewership but won’t immediately impact Fox Corporation’s top line.",
      "context": "Trump’s $9 billion clawback bill passed its first Senate hurdle, a political development that may boost Fo",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Fox News",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 2088,
      "end": 2096,
      "sentence": "Trump’s $9 billion clawback bill passed its first Senate hurdle, a political development that may boost Fox News viewership but won’t immediately impact Fox Corporation’s top line.",
      "context": "te hurdle, a political development that may boost Fox News viewership but won’t immediately impact Fox Corpo",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Fox Corporation’s",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 2137,
      "end": 2154,
      "sentence": "Trump’s $9 billion clawback bill passed its first Senate hurdle, a political development that may boost Fox News viewership but won’t immediately impact Fox Corporation’s top line.",
      "context": "Fox News viewership but won’t immediately impact Fox Corporation’s top line.\nClawback Bill Update\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Clawback Bill",
      "label": "LAW",
      "start": 2165,
      "end": 2178,
      "sentence": "Clawback Bill Update\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "context": "’t immediately impact Fox Corporation’s top line.\nClawback Bill Update\nNeutral Sentiment:\nA NATO ambassador’s cal",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "NATO",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 2207,
      "end": 2211,
      "sentence": "A NATO ambassador’s call for presidential flexibility on foreign policy funding could drive international affairs coverage, with limited direct impact on Fox Corporation.",
      "context": "p line.\nClawback Bill Update\nNeutral Sentiment:\nA NATO ambassador’s call for presidential flexibility on",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Fox Corporation",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 2359,
      "end": 2374,
      "sentence": "A NATO ambassador’s call for presidential flexibility on foreign policy funding could drive international affairs coverage, with limited direct impact on Fox Corporation.",
      "context": "l affairs coverage, with limited direct impact on Fox Corporation.\nNATO Ambassador Interview\nNeutral Sentiment:\nSen",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "NATO",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 2376,
      "end": 2380,
      "sentence": "NATO Ambassador Interview\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "context": "e, with limited direct impact on Fox Corporation.\nNATO Ambassador Interview\nNeutral Sentiment:\nSenate GO",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Senate",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 2421,
      "end": 2427,
      "sentence": "Senate GOP agreement to restore HIV/AIDS prevention funding is significant policy news but not specific to Fox Corporation’s business.",
      "context": "ion.\nNATO Ambassador Interview\nNeutral Sentiment:\nSenate GOP agreement to restore HIV/AIDS prevention fund",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "GOP",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 2428,
      "end": 2431,
      "sentence": "Senate GOP agreement to restore HIV/AIDS prevention funding is significant policy news but not specific to Fox Corporation’s business.",
      "context": "TO Ambassador Interview\nNeutral Sentiment:\nSenate GOP agreement to restore HIV/AIDS prevention funding",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Fox Corporation’s",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 2528,
      "end": 2545,
      "sentence": "Senate GOP agreement to restore HIV/AIDS prevention funding is significant policy news but not specific to Fox Corporation’s business.",
      "context": "ng is significant policy news but not specific to Fox Corporation’s business.\nSenate GOP Funding Deal\nNeutral Sentime",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Senate GOP Funding",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 2556,
      "end": 2574,
      "sentence": "Senate GOP Funding Deal\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "context": "s but not specific to Fox Corporation’s business.\nSenate GOP Funding Deal\nNeutral Sentiment:\nUnited Cajun Navy and vol",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "United Cajun Navy",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 2599,
      "end": 2616,
      "sentence": "United Cajun Navy and volunteers conducting flood rescues in Texas is human-interest reporting, unlikely to sway Fox’s advertising outlook.",
      "context": "iness.\nSenate GOP Funding Deal\nNeutral Sentiment:\nUnited Cajun Navy and volunteers conducting flood rescues in Texas",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Texas",
      "label": "GPE",
      "start": 2660,
      "end": 2665,
      "sentence": "United Cajun Navy and volunteers conducting flood rescues in Texas is human-interest reporting, unlikely to sway Fox’s advertising outlook.",
      "context": "n Navy and volunteers conducting flood rescues in Texas is human-interest reporting, unlikely to sway Fox",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": true,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Fox",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 2712,
      "end": 2715,
      "sentence": "United Cajun Navy and volunteers conducting flood rescues in Texas is human-interest reporting, unlikely to sway Fox’s advertising outlook.",
      "context": "xas is human-interest reporting, unlikely to sway Fox’s advertising outlook.\nTexas Flood Rescue\nNeutral",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Texas Flood Rescue",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 2739,
      "end": 2758,
      "sentence": "Texas Flood Rescue\nNeutral Sentiment:\nFlood devastation in New Jersey is major breaking news but does not specifically affect Fox Corporation’s content strategy.",
      "context": "ting, unlikely to sway Fox’s advertising outlook.\nTexas Flood Rescue\nNeutral Sentiment:\nFlood devastation in New Jersey",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "New Jersey",
      "label": "GPE",
      "start": 2798,
      "end": 2808,
      "sentence": "Texas Flood Rescue\nNeutral Sentiment:\nFlood devastation in New Jersey is major breaking news but does not specifically affect Fox Corporation’s content strategy.",
      "context": "od Rescue\nNeutral Sentiment:\nFlood devastation in New Jersey is major breaking news but does not specifically",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": true,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Fox Corporation’s",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 2865,
      "end": 2882,
      "sentence": "Texas Flood Rescue\nNeutral Sentiment:\nFlood devastation in New Jersey is major breaking news but does not specifically affect Fox Corporation’s content strategy.",
      "context": "or breaking news but does not specifically affect Fox Corporation’s content strategy.\nNJ Flood Coverage\nNeutral Senti",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Trump",
      "label": "PERSON",
      "start": 2955,
      "end": 2960,
      "sentence": "Live coverage of Trump promoting an industrial agenda from Pittsburgh may drive temporary traffic peaks but has limited revenue impact.",
      "context": "lood Coverage\nNeutral Sentiment:\nLive coverage of Trump promoting an industrial agenda from Pittsburgh ma",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": true,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Pittsburgh",
      "label": "GPE",
      "start": 2997,
      "end": 3007,
      "sentence": "Live coverage of Trump promoting an industrial agenda from Pittsburgh may drive temporary traffic peaks but has limited revenue impact.",
      "context": "rage of Trump promoting an industrial agenda from Pittsburgh may drive temporary traffic peaks but has limited",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": true,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Trump Pittsburgh Event",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 3074,
      "end": 3097,
      "sentence": "Trump Pittsburgh Event\nNeutral Sentiment:\nWhite House probing use of autopen in post-presidential correspondence is political news unlikely to change Fox Corporation’s advertising fundamentals.",
      "context": "ary traffic peaks but has limited revenue impact.\nTrump Pittsburgh Event\nNeutral Sentiment:\nWhite House probing use of auto",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "White House",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 3116,
      "end": 3127,
      "sentence": "Trump Pittsburgh Event\nNeutral Sentiment:\nWhite House probing use of autopen in post-presidential correspondence is political news unlikely to change Fox Corporation’s advertising fundamentals.",
      "context": "impact.\nTrump Pittsburgh Event\nNeutral Sentiment:\nWhite House probing use of autopen in post-presidential corre",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Fox Corporation’s",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 3224,
      "end": 3241,
      "sentence": "Trump Pittsburgh Event\nNeutral Sentiment:\nWhite House probing use of autopen in post-presidential correspondence is political news unlikely to change Fox Corporation’s advertising fundamentals.",
      "context": "rrespondence is political news unlikely to change Fox Corporation’s advertising fundamentals.\nAutopen Investigation\nN",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "weekly",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 3326,
      "end": 3332,
      "sentence": "Autopen Investigation\nNeutral Sentiment:\nA study on a new weekly Parkinson’s injection may drive health-segment viewership, but its direct impact on Fox Corporation is limited.",
      "context": "Investigation\nNeutral Sentiment:\nA study on a new weekly Parkinson’s injection may drive health-segment vi",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Fox Corporation",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 3417,
      "end": 3432,
      "sentence": "Autopen Investigation\nNeutral Sentiment:\nA study on a new weekly Parkinson’s injection may drive health-segment viewership, but its direct impact on Fox Corporation is limited.",
      "context": "alth-segment viewership, but its direct impact on Fox Corporation is limited.\nParkinson’s Study Coverage\nNeutral Se",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Dodgers",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 3507,
      "end": 3514,
      "sentence": "Coverage of the Dodgers manager’s All-Star Game remarks represents routine sports reporting with minimal influence on Fox Corporation’s bottom line.",
      "context": "Study Coverage\nNeutral Sentiment:\nCoverage of the Dodgers manager’s All-Star Game remarks represents routin",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "All-Star Game",
      "label": "EVENT",
      "start": 3525,
      "end": 3538,
      "sentence": "Coverage of the Dodgers manager’s All-Star Game remarks represents routine sports reporting with minimal influence on Fox Corporation’s bottom line.",
      "context": "tral Sentiment:\nCoverage of the Dodgers manager’s All-Star Game remarks represents routine sports reporting with",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Fox Corporation’s",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 3609,
      "end": 3626,
      "sentence": "Coverage of the Dodgers manager’s All-Star Game remarks represents routine sports reporting with minimal influence on Fox Corporation’s bottom line.",
      "context": "outine sports reporting with minimal influence on Fox Corporation’s bottom line.\nDodgers Manager Interview\nNeutral Se",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Dodgers",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 3640,
      "end": 3647,
      "sentence": "Dodgers Manager Interview\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "context": "nimal influence on Fox Corporation’s bottom line.\nDodgers Manager Interview\nNeutral Sentiment:\nProfile of J",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Jill Biden’s",
      "label": "PERSON",
      "start": 3696,
      "end": 3708,
      "sentence": "Profile of Jill Biden’s aide Anthony Bernal is editorial content unlikely to move Fox’s ad revenues.",
      "context": "s Manager Interview\nNeutral Sentiment:\nProfile of Jill Biden’s aide Anthony Bernal is editorial content unlikely",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": true,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Anthony Bernal",
      "label": "PERSON",
      "start": 3714,
      "end": 3728,
      "sentence": "Profile of Jill Biden’s aide Anthony Bernal is editorial content unlikely to move Fox’s ad revenues.",
      "context": "w\nNeutral Sentiment:\nProfile of Jill Biden’s aide Anthony Bernal is editorial content unlikely to move Fox’s ad re",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": true,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Fox",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 3767,
      "end": 3770,
      "sentence": "Profile of Jill Biden’s aide Anthony Bernal is editorial content unlikely to move Fox’s ad revenues.",
      "context": "hony Bernal is editorial content unlikely to move Fox’s ad revenues.\nBernal Profile\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Bernal",
      "label": "PERSON",
      "start": 3786,
      "end": 3792,
      "sentence": "Bernal Profile\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "context": "orial content unlikely to move Fox’s ad revenues.\nBernal Profile\nNeutral Sentiment:\nThe Senate GOP’s upcom",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": true,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "The Senate GOP’s",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 3820,
      "end": 3836,
      "sentence": "The Senate GOP’s upcoming test vote on a $9.4 billion clawback package is political news that may lift Fox News viewership but has no direct corporate impact.",
      "context": "’s ad revenues.\nBernal Profile\nNeutral Sentiment:\nThe Senate GOP’s upcoming test vote on a $9.4 billion clawback pac",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "$9.4 billion",
      "label": "MONEY",
      "start": 3861,
      "end": 3873,
      "sentence": "The Senate GOP’s upcoming test vote on a $9.4 billion clawback package is political news that may lift Fox News viewership but has no direct corporate impact.",
      "context": "ntiment:\nThe Senate GOP’s upcoming test vote on a $9.4 billion clawback package is political news that may lift",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": true
    },
    {
      "text": "Fox News",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 3923,
      "end": 3931,
      "sentence": "The Senate GOP’s upcoming test vote on a $9.4 billion clawback package is political news that may lift Fox News viewership but has no direct corporate impact.",
      "context": "clawback package is political news that may lift Fox News viewership but has no direct corporate impact.\nCl",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Cotton",
      "label": "PERSON",
      "start": 4025,
      "end": 4031,
      "sentence": "Sen. Cotton’s remarks on ICE resistance are part of routine political coverage with limited implications for Fox’s financials.",
      "context": "ct.\nClawback Vote Preview\nNeutral Sentiment:\nSen. Cotton’s remarks on ICE resistance are part of routine p",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": true,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "ICE",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 4045,
      "end": 4048,
      "sentence": "Sen. Cotton’s remarks on ICE resistance are part of routine political coverage with limited implications for Fox’s financials.",
      "context": "eview\nNeutral Sentiment:\nSen. Cotton’s remarks on ICE resistance are part of routine political coverage",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Fox",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 4129,
      "end": 4132,
      "sentence": "Sen. Cotton’s remarks on ICE resistance are part of routine political coverage with limited implications for Fox’s financials.",
      "context": "political coverage with limited implications for Fox’s financials.\nSen. Cotton Interview\nNeutral Senti",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Cotton",
      "label": "PERSON",
      "start": 4152,
      "end": 4158,
      "sentence": "Sen. Cotton Interview",
      "context": "h limited implications for Fox’s financials.\nSen. Cotton Interview\nNeutral Sentiment:\nPutin’s reaction to",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": true,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Putin",
      "label": "PERSON",
      "start": 4188,
      "end": 4193,
      "sentence": "Putin’s reaction to Trump’s 50-day ultimatum is global affairs news, unlikely to affect Fox Corporation’s ad sales directly.",
      "context": "ancials.\nSen. Cotton Interview\nNeutral Sentiment:\nPutin’s reaction to Trump’s 50-day ultimatum is global",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": true,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Trump",
      "label": "PERSON",
      "start": 4208,
      "end": 4213,
      "sentence": "Putin’s reaction to Trump’s 50-day ultimatum is global affairs news, unlikely to affect Fox Corporation’s ad sales directly.",
      "context": "Interview\nNeutral Sentiment:\nPutin’s reaction to Trump’s 50-day ultimatum is global affairs news, unlike",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": true,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "50-day",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 4216,
      "end": 4222,
      "sentence": "Putin’s reaction to Trump’s 50-day ultimatum is global affairs news, unlikely to affect Fox Corporation’s ad sales directly.",
      "context": "ew\nNeutral Sentiment:\nPutin’s reaction to Trump’s 50-day ultimatum is global affairs news, unlikely to aff",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Fox Corporation’s",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 4276,
      "end": 4293,
      "sentence": "Putin’s reaction to Trump’s 50-day ultimatum is global affairs news, unlikely to affect Fox Corporation’s ad sales directly.",
      "context": "imatum is global affairs news, unlikely to affect Fox Corporation’s ad sales directly.\nPutin Ultimatum Coverage\nNeutr",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Putin",
      "label": "PERSON",
      "start": 4313,
      "end": 4318,
      "sentence": "Putin Ultimatum Coverage\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "context": "ly to affect Fox Corporation’s ad sales directly.\nPutin Ultimatum Coverage\nNeutral Sentiment:\nA lawmaker’",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": true,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "America",
      "label": "GPE",
      "start": 4425,
      "end": 4432,
      "sentence": "A lawmaker’s warning about a supermarket plan targeting blue-collar America is policy commentary with minimal impact on Fox’s ad revenues.",
      "context": "ng about a supermarket plan targeting blue-collar America is policy commentary with minimal impact on Fox’s",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": true,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Fox",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 4477,
      "end": 4480,
      "sentence": "A lawmaker’s warning about a supermarket plan targeting blue-collar America is policy commentary with minimal impact on Fox’s ad revenues.",
      "context": "erica is policy commentary with minimal impact on Fox’s ad revenues.\nSupermarket Plan Analysis\nNeutral",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Arizona",
      "label": "GPE",
      "start": 4544,
      "end": 4551,
      "sentence": "Supermarket Plan Analysis\nNeutral Sentiment:\nAn Arizona pneumonic plague death report is breaking health news but not related to Fox Corporation’s business.",
      "context": ".\nSupermarket Plan Analysis\nNeutral Sentiment:\nAn Arizona pneumonic plague death report is breaking health",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": true,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Fox Corporation’s",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 4625,
      "end": 4642,
      "sentence": "Supermarket Plan Analysis\nNeutral Sentiment:\nAn Arizona pneumonic plague death report is breaking health news but not related to Fox Corporation’s business.",
      "context": "report is breaking health news but not related to Fox Corporation’s business.\nPlague Death Report\nPosted 26m ago\nAI G",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "26m ago",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 4680,
      "end": 4687,
      "sentence": "Plague Death Report\nPosted 26m ago\nAI Generated.",
      "context": "orporation’s business.\nPlague Death Report\nPosted 26m ago\nAI Generated. May Contain Errors.",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "AI Generated",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 4688,
      "end": 4700,
      "sentence": "Plague Death Report\nPosted 26m ago\nAI Generated.",
      "context": "on’s business.\nPlague Death Report\nPosted 26m ago\nAI Generated. May Contain Errors.",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    }
  ],
  "relationships": [
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "that",
      "verb": "influence",
      "object": "sentiment",
      "sentence": "Below is a summary of recent media and market‐related events that may influence investor sentiment:",
      "importance": 0
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Channel",
      "verb": "outdrew",
      "object": "NBC",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "importance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "PLC",
      "verb": "announced",
      "object": "shift",
      "sentence": "Neutral Sentiment:\nFoxtons Group PLC announced a shift in its major shareholder holdings, an update relevant to UK real estate investors but not directly tied to Fox Corporation.",
      "importance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "exchange",
      "verb": "generated",
      "object": "buzz",
      "sentence": "Caitlin Clark’s heated exchange with a WNBA referee has generated buzz around Fox Sports’ live coverage, though it’s unclear if this will drive significant ad revenue gains.",
      "importance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "this",
      "verb": "drive",
      "object": "gains",
      "sentence": "Caitlin Clark’s heated exchange with a WNBA referee has generated buzz around Fox Sports’ live coverage, though it’s unclear if this will drive significant ad revenue gains.",
      "importance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "accident",
      "verb": "highlights",
      "object": "concerns",
      "sentence": "Caitlin Clark Confrontation\nNeutral Sentiment:\nA tragic workplace accident at a frozen burrito factory highlights general industrial safety concerns but does not directly involve Fox Corporation.\nFactory Accident Report\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "importance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Trump",
      "verb": "challenged",
      "object": "Cortez",
      "sentence": "Donald Trump challenged Representatives Ocasio-Cortez and Crockett to an intelligence test, a political headline likely to drive short‐term traffic but not affect Fox Corporation’s fundamentals.",
      "importance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "analysis",
      "verb": "attract",
      "object": "viewers",
      "sentence": "An analysis of state-by-state savings under Trump’s proposed “big beautiful bill” may attract policy-minded viewers but has no direct bearing on Fox Corporation’s operations.",
      "importance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "bill",
      "verb": "passed",
      "object": "hurdle",
      "sentence": "Trump’s $9 billion clawback bill passed its first Senate hurdle, a political development that may boost Fox News viewership but won’t immediately impact Fox Corporation’s top line.",
      "importance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "that",
      "verb": "boost",
      "object": "viewership",
      "sentence": "Trump’s $9 billion clawback bill passed its first Senate hurdle, a political development that may boost Fox News viewership but won’t immediately impact Fox Corporation’s top line.",
      "importance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "call",
      "verb": "drive",
      "object": "coverage",
      "sentence": "A NATO ambassador’s call for presidential flexibility on foreign policy funding could drive international affairs coverage, with limited direct impact on Fox Corporation.",
      "importance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "coverage",
      "verb": "drive",
      "object": "peaks",
      "sentence": "Live coverage of Trump promoting an industrial agenda from Pittsburgh may drive temporary traffic peaks but has limited revenue impact.",
      "importance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "study",
      "verb": "drive",
      "object": "viewership",
      "sentence": "Autopen Investigation\nNeutral Sentiment:\nA study on a new weekly Parkinson’s injection may drive health-segment viewership, but its direct impact on Fox Corporation is limited.",
      "importance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Coverage",
      "verb": "represents",
      "object": "reporting",
      "sentence": "Coverage of the Dodgers manager’s All-Star Game remarks represents routine sports reporting with minimal influence on Fox Corporation’s bottom line.",
      "importance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "that",
      "verb": "lift",
      "object": "viewership",
      "sentence": "The Senate GOP’s upcoming test vote on a $9.4 billion clawback package is political news that may lift Fox News viewership but has no direct corporate impact.",
      "importance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Fox",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Corporation",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Fox Corporation (FOX) shares have moved higher as its news division continues to deliver strong viewership, underpinned by Fox News Channel’s recent primetime success.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Fox",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "FOX",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Fox Corporation (FOX) shares have moved higher as its news division continues to deliver strong viewership, underpinned by Fox News Channel’s recent primetime success.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Fox",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Fox",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Fox Corporation (FOX) shares have moved higher as its news division continues to deliver strong viewership, underpinned by Fox News Channel’s recent primetime success.",
      "distance": 21
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Fox",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "News",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Fox Corporation (FOX) shares have moved higher as its news division continues to deliver strong viewership, underpinned by Fox News Channel’s recent primetime success.",
      "distance": 22
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Fox",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Channel",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Fox Corporation (FOX) shares have moved higher as its news division continues to deliver strong viewership, underpinned by Fox News Channel’s recent primetime success.",
      "distance": 23
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Fox",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "’s",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Fox Corporation (FOX) shares have moved higher as its news division continues to deliver strong viewership, underpinned by Fox News Channel’s recent primetime success.",
      "distance": 24
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Corporation",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "FOX",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Fox Corporation (FOX) shares have moved higher as its news division continues to deliver strong viewership, underpinned by Fox News Channel’s recent primetime success.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Corporation",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Fox",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Fox Corporation (FOX) shares have moved higher as its news division continues to deliver strong viewership, underpinned by Fox News Channel’s recent primetime success.",
      "distance": 20
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Corporation",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "News",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Fox Corporation (FOX) shares have moved higher as its news division continues to deliver strong viewership, underpinned by Fox News Channel’s recent primetime success.",
      "distance": 21
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Corporation",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Channel",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Fox Corporation (FOX) shares have moved higher as its news division continues to deliver strong viewership, underpinned by Fox News Channel’s recent primetime success.",
      "distance": 22
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Corporation",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "’s",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Fox Corporation (FOX) shares have moved higher as its news division continues to deliver strong viewership, underpinned by Fox News Channel’s recent primetime success.",
      "distance": 23
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "FOX",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Fox",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Fox Corporation (FOX) shares have moved higher as its news division continues to deliver strong viewership, underpinned by Fox News Channel’s recent primetime success.",
      "distance": 18
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "FOX",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "News",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Fox Corporation (FOX) shares have moved higher as its news division continues to deliver strong viewership, underpinned by Fox News Channel’s recent primetime success.",
      "distance": 19
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "FOX",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Channel",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Fox Corporation (FOX) shares have moved higher as its news division continues to deliver strong viewership, underpinned by Fox News Channel’s recent primetime success.",
      "distance": 20
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "FOX",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "’s",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Fox Corporation (FOX) shares have moved higher as its news division continues to deliver strong viewership, underpinned by Fox News Channel’s recent primetime success.",
      "distance": 21
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Fox",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "News",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Fox Corporation (FOX) shares have moved higher as its news division continues to deliver strong viewership, underpinned by Fox News Channel’s recent primetime success.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Fox",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Channel",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Fox Corporation (FOX) shares have moved higher as its news division continues to deliver strong viewership, underpinned by Fox News Channel’s recent primetime success.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Fox",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "’s",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Fox Corporation (FOX) shares have moved higher as its news division continues to deliver strong viewership, underpinned by Fox News Channel’s recent primetime success.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "News",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Channel",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Fox Corporation (FOX) shares have moved higher as its news division continues to deliver strong viewership, underpinned by Fox News Channel’s recent primetime success.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "News",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "’s",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Fox Corporation (FOX) shares have moved higher as its news division continues to deliver strong viewership, underpinned by Fox News Channel’s recent primetime success.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Channel",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "’s",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Fox Corporation (FOX) shares have moved higher as its news division continues to deliver strong viewership, underpinned by Fox News Channel’s recent primetime success.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Fox",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "News",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Fox",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Channel",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Fox",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "NBC",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Fox",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "CBS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Fox",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "ABC",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Fox",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "the",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "distance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Fox",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "third",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "distance": 13
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Fox",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "consecutive",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "distance": 14
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Fox",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "week",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "distance": 15
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "News",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Channel",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "News",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "NBC",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "News",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "CBS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "News",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "ABC",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "News",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "the",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "News",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "third",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "distance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "News",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "consecutive",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "distance": 13
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "News",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "week",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "distance": 14
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Channel",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "NBC",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Channel",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "CBS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Channel",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "ABC",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Channel",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "the",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Channel",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "third",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Channel",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "consecutive",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "distance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Channel",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "week",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "distance": 13
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "NBC",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "CBS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "NBC",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "ABC",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "NBC",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "the",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "NBC",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "third",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "NBC",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "consecutive",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "NBC",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "week",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "CBS",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "ABC",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "CBS",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "the",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "CBS",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "third",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "CBS",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "consecutive",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "CBS",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "week",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "ABC",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "the",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "ABC",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "third",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "ABC",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "consecutive",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "ABC",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "week",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "the",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "third",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "the",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "consecutive",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "the",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "week",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "third",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "consecutive",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "third",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "week",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "consecutive",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "week",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nFox News Channel outdrew NBC, CBS and ABC during primetime for the third consecutive week, reinforcing its leadership in audience share and supporting higher advertising revenue potential.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Fox",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "News",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Fox News Channel Ratings Report",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Fox",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Channel",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Fox News Channel Ratings Report",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "News",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Channel",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Fox News Channel Ratings Report",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Foxtons",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Group",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Neutral Sentiment:\nFoxtons Group PLC announced a shift in its major shareholder holdings, an update relevant to UK real estate investors but not directly tied to Fox Corporation.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Foxtons",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "PLC",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Neutral Sentiment:\nFoxtons Group PLC announced a shift in its major shareholder holdings, an update relevant to UK real estate investors but not directly tied to Fox Corporation.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Foxtons",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "UK",
      "entity2_type": "GPE",
      "sentence": "Neutral Sentiment:\nFoxtons Group PLC announced a shift in its major shareholder holdings, an update relevant to UK real estate investors but not directly tied to Fox Corporation.",
      "distance": 16
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Foxtons",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Fox",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Neutral Sentiment:\nFoxtons Group PLC announced a shift in its major shareholder holdings, an update relevant to UK real estate investors but not directly tied to Fox Corporation.",
      "distance": 25
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Foxtons",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Corporation",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Neutral Sentiment:\nFoxtons Group PLC announced a shift in its major shareholder holdings, an update relevant to UK real estate investors but not directly tied to Fox Corporation.",
      "distance": 26
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Group",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "PLC",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Neutral Sentiment:\nFoxtons Group PLC announced a shift in its major shareholder holdings, an update relevant to UK real estate investors but not directly tied to Fox Corporation.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Group",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "UK",
      "entity2_type": "GPE",
      "sentence": "Neutral Sentiment:\nFoxtons Group PLC announced a shift in its major shareholder holdings, an update relevant to UK real estate investors but not directly tied to Fox Corporation.",
      "distance": 15
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Group",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Fox",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Neutral Sentiment:\nFoxtons Group PLC announced a shift in its major shareholder holdings, an update relevant to UK real estate investors but not directly tied to Fox Corporation.",
      "distance": 24
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Group",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Corporation",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Neutral Sentiment:\nFoxtons Group PLC announced a shift in its major shareholder holdings, an update relevant to UK real estate investors but not directly tied to Fox Corporation.",
      "distance": 25
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "PLC",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "UK",
      "entity2_type": "GPE",
      "sentence": "Neutral Sentiment:\nFoxtons Group PLC announced a shift in its major shareholder holdings, an update relevant to UK real estate investors but not directly tied to Fox Corporation.",
      "distance": 14
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "PLC",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Fox",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Neutral Sentiment:\nFoxtons Group PLC announced a shift in its major shareholder holdings, an update relevant to UK real estate investors but not directly tied to Fox Corporation.",
      "distance": 23
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "PLC",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Corporation",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Neutral Sentiment:\nFoxtons Group PLC announced a shift in its major shareholder holdings, an update relevant to UK real estate investors but not directly tied to Fox Corporation.",
      "distance": 24
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "UK",
      "entity1_type": "GPE",
      "entity2": "Fox",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Neutral Sentiment:\nFoxtons Group PLC announced a shift in its major shareholder holdings, an update relevant to UK real estate investors but not directly tied to Fox Corporation.",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "UK",
      "entity1_type": "GPE",
      "entity2": "Corporation",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Neutral Sentiment:\nFoxtons Group PLC announced a shift in its major shareholder holdings, an update relevant to UK real estate investors but not directly tied to Fox Corporation.",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Fox",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Corporation",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Neutral Sentiment:\nFoxtons Group PLC announced a shift in its major shareholder holdings, an update relevant to UK real estate investors but not directly tied to Fox Corporation.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Caitlin",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "Clark",
      "entity2_type": "PERSON",
      "sentence": "Caitlin Clark’s heated exchange with a WNBA referee has generated buzz around Fox Sports’ live coverage, though it’s unclear if this will drive significant ad revenue gains.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Caitlin",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "’s",
      "entity2_type": "PERSON",
      "sentence": "Caitlin Clark’s heated exchange with a WNBA referee has generated buzz around Fox Sports’ live coverage, though it’s unclear if this will drive significant ad revenue gains.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Caitlin",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "WNBA",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Caitlin Clark’s heated exchange with a WNBA referee has generated buzz around Fox Sports’ live coverage, though it’s unclear if this will drive significant ad revenue gains.",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Caitlin",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "Fox",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Caitlin Clark’s heated exchange with a WNBA referee has generated buzz around Fox Sports’ live coverage, though it’s unclear if this will drive significant ad revenue gains.",
      "distance": 13
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Caitlin",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "Sports",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Caitlin Clark’s heated exchange with a WNBA referee has generated buzz around Fox Sports’ live coverage, though it’s unclear if this will drive significant ad revenue gains.",
      "distance": 14
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Caitlin",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "’",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Caitlin Clark’s heated exchange with a WNBA referee has generated buzz around Fox Sports’ live coverage, though it’s unclear if this will drive significant ad revenue gains.",
      "distance": 15
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Clark",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "’s",
      "entity2_type": "PERSON",
      "sentence": "Caitlin Clark’s heated exchange with a WNBA referee has generated buzz around Fox Sports’ live coverage, though it’s unclear if this will drive significant ad revenue gains.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Clark",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "WNBA",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Caitlin Clark’s heated exchange with a WNBA referee has generated buzz around Fox Sports’ live coverage, though it’s unclear if this will drive significant ad revenue gains.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Clark",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "Fox",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Caitlin Clark’s heated exchange with a WNBA referee has generated buzz around Fox Sports’ live coverage, though it’s unclear if this will drive significant ad revenue gains.",
      "distance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Clark",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "Sports",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Caitlin Clark’s heated exchange with a WNBA referee has generated buzz around Fox Sports’ live coverage, though it’s unclear if this will drive significant ad revenue gains.",
      "distance": 13
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Clark",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "’",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Caitlin Clark’s heated exchange with a WNBA referee has generated buzz around Fox Sports’ live coverage, though it’s unclear if this will drive significant ad revenue gains.",
      "distance": 14
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "’s",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "WNBA",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Caitlin Clark’s heated exchange with a WNBA referee has generated buzz around Fox Sports’ live coverage, though it’s unclear if this will drive significant ad revenue gains.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "’s",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "Fox",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Caitlin Clark’s heated exchange with a WNBA referee has generated buzz around Fox Sports’ live coverage, though it’s unclear if this will drive significant ad revenue gains.",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "’s",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "Sports",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Caitlin Clark’s heated exchange with a WNBA referee has generated buzz around Fox Sports’ live coverage, though it’s unclear if this will drive significant ad revenue gains.",
      "distance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "’s",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "’",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Caitlin Clark’s heated exchange with a WNBA referee has generated buzz around Fox Sports’ live coverage, though it’s unclear if this will drive significant ad revenue gains.",
      "distance": 13
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "WNBA",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Fox",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Caitlin Clark’s heated exchange with a WNBA referee has generated buzz around Fox Sports’ live coverage, though it’s unclear if this will drive significant ad revenue gains.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "WNBA",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Sports",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Caitlin Clark’s heated exchange with a WNBA referee has generated buzz around Fox Sports’ live coverage, though it’s unclear if this will drive significant ad revenue gains.",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "WNBA",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "’",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Caitlin Clark’s heated exchange with a WNBA referee has generated buzz around Fox Sports’ live coverage, though it’s unclear if this will drive significant ad revenue gains.",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Fox",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Sports",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Caitlin Clark’s heated exchange with a WNBA referee has generated buzz around Fox Sports’ live coverage, though it’s unclear if this will drive significant ad revenue gains.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Fox",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "’",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Caitlin Clark’s heated exchange with a WNBA referee has generated buzz around Fox Sports’ live coverage, though it’s unclear if this will drive significant ad revenue gains.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Sports",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "’",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Caitlin Clark’s heated exchange with a WNBA referee has generated buzz around Fox Sports’ live coverage, though it’s unclear if this will drive significant ad revenue gains.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Caitlin",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "Clark",
      "entity2_type": "PERSON",
      "sentence": "Caitlin Clark Confrontation\nNeutral Sentiment:\nA tragic workplace accident at a frozen burrito factory highlights general industrial safety concerns but does not directly involve Fox Corporation.\nFactory Accident Report\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Caitlin",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "Fox",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Caitlin Clark Confrontation\nNeutral Sentiment:\nA tragic workplace accident at a frozen burrito factory highlights general industrial safety concerns but does not directly involve Fox Corporation.\nFactory Accident Report\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 27
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Caitlin",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "Corporation",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Caitlin Clark Confrontation\nNeutral Sentiment:\nA tragic workplace accident at a frozen burrito factory highlights general industrial safety concerns but does not directly involve Fox Corporation.\nFactory Accident Report\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 28
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Clark",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "Fox",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Caitlin Clark Confrontation\nNeutral Sentiment:\nA tragic workplace accident at a frozen burrito factory highlights general industrial safety concerns but does not directly involve Fox Corporation.\nFactory Accident Report\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 26
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Clark",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "Corporation",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Caitlin Clark Confrontation\nNeutral Sentiment:\nA tragic workplace accident at a frozen burrito factory highlights general industrial safety concerns but does not directly involve Fox Corporation.\nFactory Accident Report\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 27
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Fox",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Corporation",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Caitlin Clark Confrontation\nNeutral Sentiment:\nA tragic workplace accident at a frozen burrito factory highlights general industrial safety concerns but does not directly involve Fox Corporation.\nFactory Accident Report\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Newt",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "Gingrich",
      "entity2_type": "PERSON",
      "sentence": "Newt Gingrich’s comment on the shrinking role for moderates in the Democratic Party is political analysis content with limited impact on Fox’s core advertising base.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Newt",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "’s",
      "entity2_type": "PERSON",
      "sentence": "Newt Gingrich’s comment on the shrinking role for moderates in the Democratic Party is political analysis content with limited impact on Fox’s core advertising base.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Newt",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "the",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Newt Gingrich’s comment on the shrinking role for moderates in the Democratic Party is political analysis content with limited impact on Fox’s core advertising base.",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Newt",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "Democratic",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Newt Gingrich’s comment on the shrinking role for moderates in the Democratic Party is political analysis content with limited impact on Fox’s core advertising base.",
      "distance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Newt",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "Party",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Newt Gingrich’s comment on the shrinking role for moderates in the Democratic Party is political analysis content with limited impact on Fox’s core advertising base.",
      "distance": 13
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Newt",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "Fox",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Newt Gingrich’s comment on the shrinking role for moderates in the Democratic Party is political analysis content with limited impact on Fox’s core advertising base.",
      "distance": 22
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Gingrich",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "’s",
      "entity2_type": "PERSON",
      "sentence": "Newt Gingrich’s comment on the shrinking role for moderates in the Democratic Party is political analysis content with limited impact on Fox’s core advertising base.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Gingrich",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "the",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Newt Gingrich’s comment on the shrinking role for moderates in the Democratic Party is political analysis content with limited impact on Fox’s core advertising base.",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Gingrich",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "Democratic",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Newt Gingrich’s comment on the shrinking role for moderates in the Democratic Party is political analysis content with limited impact on Fox’s core advertising base.",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Gingrich",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "Party",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Newt Gingrich’s comment on the shrinking role for moderates in the Democratic Party is political analysis content with limited impact on Fox’s core advertising base.",
      "distance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Gingrich",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "Fox",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Newt Gingrich’s comment on the shrinking role for moderates in the Democratic Party is political analysis content with limited impact on Fox’s core advertising base.",
      "distance": 21
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "’s",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "the",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Newt Gingrich’s comment on the shrinking role for moderates in the Democratic Party is political analysis content with limited impact on Fox’s core advertising base.",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "’s",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "Democratic",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Newt Gingrich’s comment on the shrinking role for moderates in the Democratic Party is political analysis content with limited impact on Fox’s core advertising base.",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "’s",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "Party",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Newt Gingrich’s comment on the shrinking role for moderates in the Democratic Party is political analysis content with limited impact on Fox’s core advertising base.",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "’s",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "Fox",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Newt Gingrich’s comment on the shrinking role for moderates in the Democratic Party is political analysis content with limited impact on Fox’s core advertising base.",
      "distance": 20
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "the",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Democratic",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Newt Gingrich’s comment on the shrinking role for moderates in the Democratic Party is political analysis content with limited impact on Fox’s core advertising base.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "the",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Party",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Newt Gingrich’s comment on the shrinking role for moderates in the Democratic Party is political analysis content with limited impact on Fox’s core advertising base.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "the",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Fox",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Newt Gingrich’s comment on the shrinking role for moderates in the Democratic Party is political analysis content with limited impact on Fox’s core advertising base.",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Democratic",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Party",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Newt Gingrich’s comment on the shrinking role for moderates in the Democratic Party is political analysis content with limited impact on Fox’s core advertising base.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Democratic",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Fox",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Newt Gingrich’s comment on the shrinking role for moderates in the Democratic Party is political analysis content with limited impact on Fox’s core advertising base.",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Party",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Fox",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Newt Gingrich’s comment on the shrinking role for moderates in the Democratic Party is political analysis content with limited impact on Fox’s core advertising base.",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Donald",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "Trump",
      "entity2_type": "PERSON",
      "sentence": "Donald Trump challenged Representatives Ocasio-Cortez and Crockett to an intelligence test, a political headline likely to drive short‐term traffic but not affect Fox Corporation’s fundamentals.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Donald",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "Ocasio",
      "entity2_type": "PERSON",
      "sentence": "Donald Trump challenged Representatives Ocasio-Cortez and Crockett to an intelligence test, a political headline likely to drive short‐term traffic but not affect Fox Corporation’s fundamentals.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Donald",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "PERSON",
      "sentence": "Donald Trump challenged Representatives Ocasio-Cortez and Crockett to an intelligence test, a political headline likely to drive short‐term traffic but not affect Fox Corporation’s fundamentals.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Donald",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "Cortez",
      "entity2_type": "PERSON",
      "sentence": "Donald Trump challenged Representatives Ocasio-Cortez and Crockett to an intelligence test, a political headline likely to drive short‐term traffic but not affect Fox Corporation’s fundamentals.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Donald",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "Crockett",
      "entity2_type": "PERSON",
      "sentence": "Donald Trump challenged Representatives Ocasio-Cortez and Crockett to an intelligence test, a political headline likely to drive short‐term traffic but not affect Fox Corporation’s fundamentals.",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Donald",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "Fox",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Donald Trump challenged Representatives Ocasio-Cortez and Crockett to an intelligence test, a political headline likely to drive short‐term traffic but not affect Fox Corporation’s fundamentals.",
      "distance": 25
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
