{
  "ticker": "NKE",
  "entities": [
    {
      "text": "NIKE, Inc.",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 0,
      "end": 10,
      "sentence": "NIKE, Inc. (NKE) shares are under pressure today after analysts trimmed profit forecasts, even as several bullish themes emerge.",
      "context": "NIKE, Inc. (NKE) shares are under pressure today after analy",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "NKE",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 12,
      "end": 15,
      "sentence": "NIKE, Inc. (NKE) shares are under pressure today after analysts trimmed profit forecasts, even as several bullish themes emerge.",
      "context": "NIKE, Inc. (NKE) shares are under pressure today after analysts t",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "today",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 43,
      "end": 48,
      "sentence": "NIKE, Inc. (NKE) shares are under pressure today after analysts trimmed profit forecasts, even as several bullish themes emerge.",
      "context": "NIKE, Inc. (NKE) shares are under pressure today after analysts trimmed profit forecasts, even as",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Zacks Research",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 129,
      "end": 143,
      "sentence": "Zacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate and a report flagged NKE among S&P 500 names with potentially plunging earnings.",
      "context": "forecasts, even as several bullish themes emerge. Zacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate and a report flagged",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Q1 2026",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 152,
      "end": 159,
      "sentence": "Zacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate and a report flagged NKE among S&P 500 names with potentially plunging earnings.",
      "context": "ral bullish themes emerge. Zacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate and a report flagged NKE among S&P 5",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "NKE",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 194,
      "end": 197,
      "sentence": "Zacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate and a report flagged NKE among S&P 500 names with potentially plunging earnings.",
      "context": "cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate and a report flagged NKE among S&P 500 names with potentially plunging ear",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Europe",
      "label": "LOC",
      "start": 336,
      "end": 342,
      "sentence": "Offsetting this, bulls highlight attractive valuation, expanded trading access in Europe and brand-strengthening initiatives that could support a rebound.",
      "context": "attractive valuation, expanded trading access in Europe and brand-strengthening initiatives that could su",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": true,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "InsiderMonkey",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 429,
      "end": 442,
      "sentence": "InsiderMonkey outlines a bullish thesis on NKE, highlighting valuation potential after the recent share slide.",
      "context": "that could support a rebound.\nPositive Sentiment:\nInsiderMonkey outlines a bullish thesis on NKE, highlighting va",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "NKE",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 472,
      "end": 475,
      "sentence": "InsiderMonkey outlines a bullish thesis on NKE, highlighting valuation potential after the recent share slide.",
      "context": "iment:\nInsiderMonkey outlines a bullish thesis on NKE, highlighting valuation potential after the recen",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "NIKE, Inc.",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 540,
      "end": 550,
      "sentence": "NIKE, Inc. (NKE): A Bull Case Theory\nPositive Sentiment:\nCrypto exchange Gemini adds NKE to its tokenized stock offering in the EU, broadening investor access and liquidity.",
      "context": "valuation potential after the recent share slide.\nNIKE, Inc. (NKE): A Bull Case Theory\nPositive Sentiment:\nCry",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "NKE",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 552,
      "end": 555,
      "sentence": "NIKE, Inc. (NKE): A Bull Case Theory\nPositive Sentiment:\nCrypto exchange Gemini adds NKE to its tokenized stock offering in the EU, broadening investor access and liquidity.",
      "context": "tential after the recent share slide.\nNIKE, Inc. (NKE): A Bull Case Theory\nPositive Sentiment:\nCrypto e",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Gemini",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 613,
      "end": 619,
      "sentence": "NIKE, Inc. (NKE): A Bull Case Theory\nPositive Sentiment:\nCrypto exchange Gemini adds NKE to its tokenized stock offering in the EU, broadening investor access and liquidity.",
      "context": "l Case Theory\nPositive Sentiment:\nCrypto exchange Gemini adds NKE to its tokenized stock offering in the E",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "NKE",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 625,
      "end": 628,
      "sentence": "NIKE, Inc. (NKE): A Bull Case Theory\nPositive Sentiment:\nCrypto exchange Gemini adds NKE to its tokenized stock offering in the EU, broadening investor access and liquidity.",
      "context": "y\nPositive Sentiment:\nCrypto exchange Gemini adds NKE to its tokenized stock offering in the EU, broade",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "EU",
      "label": "GPE",
      "start": 668,
      "end": 670,
      "sentence": "NIKE, Inc. (NKE): A Bull Case Theory\nPositive Sentiment:\nCrypto exchange Gemini adds NKE to its tokenized stock offering in the EU, broadening investor access and liquidity.",
      "context": "i adds NKE to its tokenized stock offering in the EU, broadening investor access and liquidity.\nGemini",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": true,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Gemini",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 714,
      "end": 720,
      "sentence": "Gemini Expands Tokenized Stock Offerings with Nike, McDonald’s, Starbucks for EU Investors\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "context": "the EU, broadening investor access and liquidity.\nGemini Expands Tokenized Stock Offerings with Nike, McDo",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Nike",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 760,
      "end": 764,
      "sentence": "Gemini Expands Tokenized Stock Offerings with Nike, McDonald’s, Starbucks for EU Investors\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "context": "ty.\nGemini Expands Tokenized Stock Offerings with Nike, McDonald’s, Starbucks for EU Investors\nNeutral S",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "McDonald’s",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 766,
      "end": 776,
      "sentence": "Gemini Expands Tokenized Stock Offerings with Nike, McDonald’s, Starbucks for EU Investors\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "context": "mini Expands Tokenized Stock Offerings with Nike, McDonald’s, Starbucks for EU Investors\nNeutral Sentiment:\nNi",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Starbucks",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 778,
      "end": 787,
      "sentence": "Gemini Expands Tokenized Stock Offerings with Nike, McDonald’s, Starbucks for EU Investors\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "context": "Tokenized Stock Offerings with Nike, McDonald’s, Starbucks for EU Investors\nNeutral Sentiment:\nNike has beco",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Nike",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 824,
      "end": 828,
      "sentence": "Nike has become one of the most-watched stocks on Zacks.com, indicating heightened investor interest and trading volume.\nNIKE, Inc. (NKE) is Attracting Investor Attention\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "context": "’s, Starbucks for EU Investors\nNeutral Sentiment:\nNike has become one of the most-watched stocks on Zack",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "NIKE, Inc.",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 945,
      "end": 955,
      "sentence": "Nike has become one of the most-watched stocks on Zacks.com, indicating heightened investor interest and trading volume.\nNIKE, Inc. (NKE) is Attracting Investor Attention\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "context": "heightened investor interest and trading volume.\nNIKE, Inc. (NKE) is Attracting Investor Attention\nNeutral Se",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "NKE",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 957,
      "end": 960,
      "sentence": "Nike has become one of the most-watched stocks on Zacks.com, indicating heightened investor interest and trading volume.\nNIKE, Inc. (NKE) is Attracting Investor Attention\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "context": "investor interest and trading volume.\nNIKE, Inc. (NKE) is Attracting Investor Attention\nNeutral Sentime",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Nike",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1014,
      "end": 1018,
      "sentence": "Nike partners with Special Olympics for a global youth inclusion initiative, reinforcing brand goodwill and community engagement.",
      "context": "Attracting Investor Attention\nNeutral Sentiment:\nNike partners with Special Olympics for a global youth",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Special Olympics",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1033,
      "end": 1049,
      "sentence": "Nike partners with Special Olympics for a global youth inclusion initiative, reinforcing brand goodwill and community engagement.",
      "context": "r Attention\nNeutral Sentiment:\nNike partners with Special Olympics for a global youth inclusion initiative, reinforc",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "NIKE",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1144,
      "end": 1148,
      "sentence": "NIKE (NKE) Teams With Special Olympics For Global Youth Sport Inclusion Initiative\nNeutral Sentiment:\nOakmark’s Q2 investor letter revisits Nike’s valuation amid mixed sector returns, sparking debate on whether this is the right entry point.",
      "context": "nforcing brand goodwill and community engagement.\nNIKE (NKE) Teams With Special Olympics For Global Yout",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "NKE",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1150,
      "end": 1153,
      "sentence": "NIKE (NKE) Teams With Special Olympics For Global Youth Sport Inclusion Initiative\nNeutral Sentiment:\nOakmark’s Q2 investor letter revisits Nike’s valuation amid mixed sector returns, sparking debate on whether this is the right entry point.",
      "context": "ng brand goodwill and community engagement.\nNIKE (NKE) Teams With Special Olympics For Global Youth Spo",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Special Olympics",
      "label": "EVENT",
      "start": 1166,
      "end": 1182,
      "sentence": "NIKE (NKE) Teams With Special Olympics For Global Youth Sport Inclusion Initiative\nNeutral Sentiment:\nOakmark’s Q2 investor letter revisits Nike’s valuation amid mixed sector returns, sparking debate on whether this is the right entry point.",
      "context": "l and community engagement.\nNIKE (NKE) Teams With Special Olympics For Global Youth Sport Inclusion Initiative\nNeutr",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Oakmark",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1246,
      "end": 1253,
      "sentence": "NIKE (NKE) Teams With Special Olympics For Global Youth Sport Inclusion Initiative\nNeutral Sentiment:\nOakmark’s Q2 investor letter revisits Nike’s valuation amid mixed sector returns, sparking debate on whether this is the right entry point.",
      "context": "uth Sport Inclusion Initiative\nNeutral Sentiment:\nOakmark’s Q2 investor letter revisits Nike’s valuation am",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Q2",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 1256,
      "end": 1258,
      "sentence": "NIKE (NKE) Teams With Special Olympics For Global Youth Sport Inclusion Initiative\nNeutral Sentiment:\nOakmark’s Q2 investor letter revisits Nike’s valuation amid mixed sector returns, sparking debate on whether this is the right entry point.",
      "context": "Inclusion Initiative\nNeutral Sentiment:\nOakmark’s Q2 investor letter revisits Nike’s valuation amid mi",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Nike",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1284,
      "end": 1288,
      "sentence": "NIKE (NKE) Teams With Special Olympics For Global Youth Sport Inclusion Initiative\nNeutral Sentiment:\nOakmark’s Q2 investor letter revisits Nike’s valuation amid mixed sector returns, sparking debate on whether this is the right entry point.",
      "context": "Sentiment:\nOakmark’s Q2 investor letter revisits Nike’s valuation amid mixed sector returns, sparking d",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Nike",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1421,
      "end": 1425,
      "sentence": "Is this the Best Time to Invest in Nike (NKE)?",
      "context": "t entry point.\nIs this the Best Time to Invest in Nike (NKE)?\nNeutral Sentiment:\nHypebeast highlights Ni",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "NKE",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1427,
      "end": 1430,
      "sentence": "Is this the Best Time to Invest in Nike (NKE)?",
      "context": "y point.\nIs this the Best Time to Invest in Nike (NKE)?\nNeutral Sentiment:\nHypebeast highlights Nike’s",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Hypebeast",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1452,
      "end": 1461,
      "sentence": "Hypebeast highlights Nike’s new Air Superfly release, showcasing ongoing product innovation that may support brand momentum.",
      "context": "Time to Invest in Nike (NKE)?\nNeutral Sentiment:\nHypebeast highlights Nike’s new Air Superfly release, showc",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Nike",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1473,
      "end": 1477,
      "sentence": "Hypebeast highlights Nike’s new Air Superfly release, showcasing ongoing product innovation that may support brand momentum.",
      "context": "ke (NKE)?\nNeutral Sentiment:\nHypebeast highlights Nike’s new Air Superfly release, showcasing ongoing pr",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Air Superfly",
      "label": "PRODUCT",
      "start": 1484,
      "end": 1496,
      "sentence": "Hypebeast highlights Nike’s new Air Superfly release, showcasing ongoing product innovation that may support brand momentum.",
      "context": "eutral Sentiment:\nHypebeast highlights Nike’s new Air Superfly release, showcasing ongoing product innovation th",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Nike",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1577,
      "end": 1581,
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "context": "oduct innovation that may support brand momentum.\nNike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "the Iconic Air Superfly",
      "label": "PRODUCT",
      "start": 1590,
      "end": 1613,
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "context": "ion that may support brand momentum.\nNike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZ",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Zacks Research",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1662,
      "end": 1676,
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "context": "y with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 fr",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Q1 2026",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 1685,
      "end": 1692,
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "context": "lusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signal",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Nike",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1710,
      "end": 1714,
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "context": ":\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term p",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "0.27",
      "label": "MONEY",
      "start": 1719,
      "end": 1723,
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "context": "esearch cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit exp",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": true
    },
    {
      "text": "0.35",
      "label": "MONEY",
      "start": 1730,
      "end": 1734,
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "context": "its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": true
    },
    {
      "text": "Zacks Research",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1784,
      "end": 1798,
      "sentence": "Zacks Research Has Bearish Estimate for NIKE Q1 Earnings\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "context": ", signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.\nZacks Research Has Bearish Estimate for NIKE Q1 Earnings\nNegativ",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "NIKE",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1824,
      "end": 1828,
      "sentence": "Zacks Research Has Bearish Estimate for NIKE Q1 Earnings\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "context": "ctations.\nZacks Research Has Bearish Estimate for NIKE Q1 Earnings\nNegative Sentiment:\nAn Investors.com",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Q1",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 1829,
      "end": 1831,
      "sentence": "Zacks Research Has Bearish Estimate for NIKE Q1 Earnings\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "context": "ons.\nZacks Research Has Bearish Estimate for NIKE Q1 Earnings\nNegative Sentiment:\nAn Investors.com art",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "NKE",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1892,
      "end": 1895,
      "sentence": "An Investors.com article flags NKE among five S&P 500 stocks whose earnings are poised to plunge in the coming quarter.",
      "context": "egative Sentiment:\nAn Investors.com article flags NKE among five S&P 500 stocks whose earnings are pois",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "five",
      "label": "CARDINAL",
      "start": 1902,
      "end": 1906,
      "sentence": "An Investors.com article flags NKE among five S&P 500 stocks whose earnings are poised to plunge in the coming quarter.",
      "context": "ntiment:\nAn Investors.com article flags NKE among five S&P 500 stocks whose earnings are poised to plung",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "the coming quarter",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 1961,
      "end": 1979,
      "sentence": "An Investors.com article flags NKE among five S&P 500 stocks whose earnings are poised to plunge in the coming quarter.",
      "context": "500 stocks whose earnings are poised to plunge in the coming quarter.\nFive S&P 500 Stocks' Earnings Poised To Plunge A",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Five",
      "label": "CARDINAL",
      "start": 1981,
      "end": 1985,
      "sentence": "Five S&P 500 Stocks' Earnings Poised To Plunge Any Day Now\nPosted 2h ago\nAI Generated.",
      "context": "nings are poised to plunge in the coming quarter.\nFive S&P 500 Stocks' Earnings Poised To Plunge Any Day",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Any Day",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 2028,
      "end": 2035,
      "sentence": "Five S&P 500 Stocks' Earnings Poised To Plunge Any Day Now\nPosted 2h ago\nAI Generated.",
      "context": "r.\nFive S&P 500 Stocks' Earnings Poised To Plunge Any Day Now\nPosted 2h ago\nAI Generated. May Contain Error",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "2h ago",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 2047,
      "end": 2053,
      "sentence": "Five S&P 500 Stocks' Earnings Poised To Plunge Any Day Now\nPosted 2h ago\nAI Generated.",
      "context": "cks' Earnings Poised To Plunge Any Day Now\nPosted 2h ago\nAI Generated. May Contain Errors.",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    }
  ],
  "relationships": [
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "analysts",
      "verb": "trimmed",
      "object": "forecasts",
      "sentence": "NIKE, Inc. (NKE) shares are under pressure today after analysts trimmed profit forecasts, even as several bullish themes emerge.",
      "importance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Research",
      "verb": "cut",
      "object": "estimate",
      "sentence": "Zacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate and a report flagged NKE among S&P 500 names with potentially plunging earnings.",
      "importance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "report",
      "verb": "flagged",
      "object": "NKE",
      "sentence": "Zacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate and a report flagged NKE among S&P 500 names with potentially plunging earnings.",
      "importance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "bulls",
      "verb": "highlight",
      "object": "valuation",
      "sentence": "Offsetting this, bulls highlight attractive valuation, expanded trading access in Europe and brand-strengthening initiatives that could support a rebound.",
      "importance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "that",
      "verb": "support",
      "object": "rebound",
      "sentence": "Offsetting this, bulls highlight attractive valuation, expanded trading access in Europe and brand-strengthening initiatives that could support a rebound.",
      "importance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "InsiderMonkey",
      "verb": "outlines",
      "object": "thesis",
      "sentence": "InsiderMonkey outlines a bullish thesis on NKE, highlighting valuation potential after the recent share slide.",
      "importance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Gemini",
      "verb": "adds",
      "object": "NKE",
      "sentence": "NIKE, Inc. (NKE): A Bull Case Theory\nPositive Sentiment:\nCrypto exchange Gemini adds NKE to its tokenized stock offering in the EU, broadening investor access and liquidity.",
      "importance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Gemini",
      "verb": "Expands",
      "object": "Offerings",
      "sentence": "Gemini Expands Tokenized Stock Offerings with Nike, McDonald’s, Starbucks for EU Investors\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "importance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "NIKE",
      "verb": "Attracting",
      "object": "Attention",
      "sentence": "Nike has become one of the most-watched stocks on Zacks.com, indicating heightened investor interest and trading volume.\nNIKE, Inc. (NKE) is Attracting Investor Attention\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "importance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "letter",
      "verb": "revisits",
      "object": "valuation",
      "sentence": "NIKE (NKE) Teams With Special Olympics For Global Youth Sport Inclusion Initiative\nNeutral Sentiment:\nOakmark’s Q2 investor letter revisits Nike’s valuation amid mixed sector returns, sparking debate on whether this is the right entry point.",
      "importance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Hypebeast",
      "verb": "highlights",
      "object": "release",
      "sentence": "Hypebeast highlights Nike’s new Air Superfly release, showcasing ongoing product innovation that may support brand momentum.",
      "importance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "that",
      "verb": "support",
      "object": "momentum",
      "sentence": "Hypebeast highlights Nike’s new Air Superfly release, showcasing ongoing product innovation that may support brand momentum.",
      "importance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Nike",
      "verb": "Revives",
      "object": "Superfly",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "importance": 14
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Research",
      "verb": "cut",
      "object": "estimate",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "importance": 14
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Research",
      "verb": "Has",
      "object": "Estimate",
      "sentence": "Zacks Research Has Bearish Estimate for NIKE Q1 Earnings\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "importance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "article",
      "verb": "flags",
      "object": "NKE",
      "sentence": "An Investors.com article flags NKE among five S&P 500 stocks whose earnings are poised to plunge in the coming quarter.",
      "importance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "NIKE",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": ",",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "NIKE, Inc. (NKE) shares are under pressure today after analysts trimmed profit forecasts, even as several bullish themes emerge.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "NIKE",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Inc.",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "NIKE, Inc. (NKE) shares are under pressure today after analysts trimmed profit forecasts, even as several bullish themes emerge.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "NIKE",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "NKE",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "NIKE, Inc. (NKE) shares are under pressure today after analysts trimmed profit forecasts, even as several bullish themes emerge.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "NIKE",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "today",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "NIKE, Inc. (NKE) shares are under pressure today after analysts trimmed profit forecasts, even as several bullish themes emerge.",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": ",",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Inc.",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "NIKE, Inc. (NKE) shares are under pressure today after analysts trimmed profit forecasts, even as several bullish themes emerge.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": ",",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "NKE",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "NIKE, Inc. (NKE) shares are under pressure today after analysts trimmed profit forecasts, even as several bullish themes emerge.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": ",",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "today",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "NIKE, Inc. (NKE) shares are under pressure today after analysts trimmed profit forecasts, even as several bullish themes emerge.",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Inc.",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "NKE",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "NIKE, Inc. (NKE) shares are under pressure today after analysts trimmed profit forecasts, even as several bullish themes emerge.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Inc.",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "today",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "NIKE, Inc. (NKE) shares are under pressure today after analysts trimmed profit forecasts, even as several bullish themes emerge.",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "NKE",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "today",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "NIKE, Inc. (NKE) shares are under pressure today after analysts trimmed profit forecasts, even as several bullish themes emerge.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Zacks",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Research",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Zacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate and a report flagged NKE among S&P 500 names with potentially plunging earnings.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Zacks",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Q1",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Zacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate and a report flagged NKE among S&P 500 names with potentially plunging earnings.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Zacks",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "2026",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Zacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate and a report flagged NKE among S&P 500 names with potentially plunging earnings.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Zacks",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "NKE",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Zacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate and a report flagged NKE among S&P 500 names with potentially plunging earnings.",
      "distance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Research",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Q1",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Zacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate and a report flagged NKE among S&P 500 names with potentially plunging earnings.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Research",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "2026",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Zacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate and a report flagged NKE among S&P 500 names with potentially plunging earnings.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Research",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "NKE",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Zacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate and a report flagged NKE among S&P 500 names with potentially plunging earnings.",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Q1",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "2026",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Zacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate and a report flagged NKE among S&P 500 names with potentially plunging earnings.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Q1",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "NKE",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Zacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate and a report flagged NKE among S&P 500 names with potentially plunging earnings.",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "2026",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "NKE",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Zacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate and a report flagged NKE among S&P 500 names with potentially plunging earnings.",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "InsiderMonkey",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "NKE",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "InsiderMonkey outlines a bullish thesis on NKE, highlighting valuation potential after the recent share slide.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "NIKE",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": ",",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "NIKE, Inc. (NKE): A Bull Case Theory\nPositive Sentiment:\nCrypto exchange Gemini adds NKE to its tokenized stock offering in the EU, broadening investor access and liquidity.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "NIKE",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Inc.",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "NIKE, Inc. (NKE): A Bull Case Theory\nPositive Sentiment:\nCrypto exchange Gemini adds NKE to its tokenized stock offering in the EU, broadening investor access and liquidity.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "NIKE",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "NKE",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "NIKE, Inc. (NKE): A Bull Case Theory\nPositive Sentiment:\nCrypto exchange Gemini adds NKE to its tokenized stock offering in the EU, broadening investor access and liquidity.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "NIKE",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Gemini",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "NIKE, Inc. (NKE): A Bull Case Theory\nPositive Sentiment:\nCrypto exchange Gemini adds NKE to its tokenized stock offering in the EU, broadening investor access and liquidity.",
      "distance": 17
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "NIKE",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "NKE",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "NIKE, Inc. (NKE): A Bull Case Theory\nPositive Sentiment:\nCrypto exchange Gemini adds NKE to its tokenized stock offering in the EU, broadening investor access and liquidity.",
      "distance": 19
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "NIKE",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "EU",
      "entity2_type": "GPE",
      "sentence": "NIKE, Inc. (NKE): A Bull Case Theory\nPositive Sentiment:\nCrypto exchange Gemini adds NKE to its tokenized stock offering in the EU, broadening investor access and liquidity.",
      "distance": 27
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": ",",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Inc.",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "NIKE, Inc. (NKE): A Bull Case Theory\nPositive Sentiment:\nCrypto exchange Gemini adds NKE to its tokenized stock offering in the EU, broadening investor access and liquidity.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": ",",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "NKE",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "NIKE, Inc. (NKE): A Bull Case Theory\nPositive Sentiment:\nCrypto exchange Gemini adds NKE to its tokenized stock offering in the EU, broadening investor access and liquidity.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": ",",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Gemini",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "NIKE, Inc. (NKE): A Bull Case Theory\nPositive Sentiment:\nCrypto exchange Gemini adds NKE to its tokenized stock offering in the EU, broadening investor access and liquidity.",
      "distance": 16
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": ",",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "NKE",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "NIKE, Inc. (NKE): A Bull Case Theory\nPositive Sentiment:\nCrypto exchange Gemini adds NKE to its tokenized stock offering in the EU, broadening investor access and liquidity.",
      "distance": 18
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": ",",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "EU",
      "entity2_type": "GPE",
      "sentence": "NIKE, Inc. (NKE): A Bull Case Theory\nPositive Sentiment:\nCrypto exchange Gemini adds NKE to its tokenized stock offering in the EU, broadening investor access and liquidity.",
      "distance": 26
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Inc.",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "NKE",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "NIKE, Inc. (NKE): A Bull Case Theory\nPositive Sentiment:\nCrypto exchange Gemini adds NKE to its tokenized stock offering in the EU, broadening investor access and liquidity.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Inc.",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Gemini",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "NIKE, Inc. (NKE): A Bull Case Theory\nPositive Sentiment:\nCrypto exchange Gemini adds NKE to its tokenized stock offering in the EU, broadening investor access and liquidity.",
      "distance": 15
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Inc.",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "NKE",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "NIKE, Inc. (NKE): A Bull Case Theory\nPositive Sentiment:\nCrypto exchange Gemini adds NKE to its tokenized stock offering in the EU, broadening investor access and liquidity.",
      "distance": 17
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Inc.",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "EU",
      "entity2_type": "GPE",
      "sentence": "NIKE, Inc. (NKE): A Bull Case Theory\nPositive Sentiment:\nCrypto exchange Gemini adds NKE to its tokenized stock offering in the EU, broadening investor access and liquidity.",
      "distance": 25
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "NKE",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Gemini",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "NIKE, Inc. (NKE): A Bull Case Theory\nPositive Sentiment:\nCrypto exchange Gemini adds NKE to its tokenized stock offering in the EU, broadening investor access and liquidity.",
      "distance": 13
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "NKE",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "NKE",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "NIKE, Inc. (NKE): A Bull Case Theory\nPositive Sentiment:\nCrypto exchange Gemini adds NKE to its tokenized stock offering in the EU, broadening investor access and liquidity.",
      "distance": 15
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "NKE",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "EU",
      "entity2_type": "GPE",
      "sentence": "NIKE, Inc. (NKE): A Bull Case Theory\nPositive Sentiment:\nCrypto exchange Gemini adds NKE to its tokenized stock offering in the EU, broadening investor access and liquidity.",
      "distance": 23
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Gemini",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "NKE",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "NIKE, Inc. (NKE): A Bull Case Theory\nPositive Sentiment:\nCrypto exchange Gemini adds NKE to its tokenized stock offering in the EU, broadening investor access and liquidity.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Gemini",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "EU",
      "entity2_type": "GPE",
      "sentence": "NIKE, Inc. (NKE): A Bull Case Theory\nPositive Sentiment:\nCrypto exchange Gemini adds NKE to its tokenized stock offering in the EU, broadening investor access and liquidity.",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "NKE",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "EU",
      "entity2_type": "GPE",
      "sentence": "NIKE, Inc. (NKE): A Bull Case Theory\nPositive Sentiment:\nCrypto exchange Gemini adds NKE to its tokenized stock offering in the EU, broadening investor access and liquidity.",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Gemini",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Nike",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Gemini Expands Tokenized Stock Offerings with Nike, McDonald’s, Starbucks for EU Investors\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Gemini",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "McDonald",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Gemini Expands Tokenized Stock Offerings with Nike, McDonald’s, Starbucks for EU Investors\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Gemini",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "’s",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Gemini Expands Tokenized Stock Offerings with Nike, McDonald’s, Starbucks for EU Investors\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Gemini",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Starbucks",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Gemini Expands Tokenized Stock Offerings with Nike, McDonald’s, Starbucks for EU Investors\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Nike",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "McDonald",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Gemini Expands Tokenized Stock Offerings with Nike, McDonald’s, Starbucks for EU Investors\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Nike",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "’s",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Gemini Expands Tokenized Stock Offerings with Nike, McDonald’s, Starbucks for EU Investors\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Nike",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Starbucks",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Gemini Expands Tokenized Stock Offerings with Nike, McDonald’s, Starbucks for EU Investors\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "McDonald",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "’s",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Gemini Expands Tokenized Stock Offerings with Nike, McDonald’s, Starbucks for EU Investors\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "McDonald",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Starbucks",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Gemini Expands Tokenized Stock Offerings with Nike, McDonald’s, Starbucks for EU Investors\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "’s",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Starbucks",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Gemini Expands Tokenized Stock Offerings with Nike, McDonald’s, Starbucks for EU Investors\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Nike",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "NIKE",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Nike has become one of the most-watched stocks on Zacks.com, indicating heightened investor interest and trading volume.\nNIKE, Inc. (NKE) is Attracting Investor Attention\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 22
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Nike",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": ",",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Nike has become one of the most-watched stocks on Zacks.com, indicating heightened investor interest and trading volume.\nNIKE, Inc. (NKE) is Attracting Investor Attention\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 23
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Nike",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Inc.",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Nike has become one of the most-watched stocks on Zacks.com, indicating heightened investor interest and trading volume.\nNIKE, Inc. (NKE) is Attracting Investor Attention\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 24
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Nike",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "NKE",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Nike has become one of the most-watched stocks on Zacks.com, indicating heightened investor interest and trading volume.\nNIKE, Inc. (NKE) is Attracting Investor Attention\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 26
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "NIKE",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": ",",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Nike has become one of the most-watched stocks on Zacks.com, indicating heightened investor interest and trading volume.\nNIKE, Inc. (NKE) is Attracting Investor Attention\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "NIKE",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Inc.",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Nike has become one of the most-watched stocks on Zacks.com, indicating heightened investor interest and trading volume.\nNIKE, Inc. (NKE) is Attracting Investor Attention\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "NIKE",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "NKE",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Nike has become one of the most-watched stocks on Zacks.com, indicating heightened investor interest and trading volume.\nNIKE, Inc. (NKE) is Attracting Investor Attention\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": ",",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Inc.",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Nike has become one of the most-watched stocks on Zacks.com, indicating heightened investor interest and trading volume.\nNIKE, Inc. (NKE) is Attracting Investor Attention\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": ",",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "NKE",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Nike has become one of the most-watched stocks on Zacks.com, indicating heightened investor interest and trading volume.\nNIKE, Inc. (NKE) is Attracting Investor Attention\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Inc.",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "NKE",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Nike has become one of the most-watched stocks on Zacks.com, indicating heightened investor interest and trading volume.\nNIKE, Inc. (NKE) is Attracting Investor Attention\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Nike",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Special",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Nike partners with Special Olympics for a global youth inclusion initiative, reinforcing brand goodwill and community engagement.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Nike",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Olympics",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Nike partners with Special Olympics for a global youth inclusion initiative, reinforcing brand goodwill and community engagement.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Special",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Olympics",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Nike partners with Special Olympics for a global youth inclusion initiative, reinforcing brand goodwill and community engagement.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "NIKE",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "NKE",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "NIKE (NKE) Teams With Special Olympics For Global Youth Sport Inclusion Initiative\nNeutral Sentiment:\nOakmark’s Q2 investor letter revisits Nike’s valuation amid mixed sector returns, sparking debate on whether this is the right entry point.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "NIKE",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Special",
      "entity2_type": "EVENT",
      "sentence": "NIKE (NKE) Teams With Special Olympics For Global Youth Sport Inclusion Initiative\nNeutral Sentiment:\nOakmark’s Q2 investor letter revisits Nike’s valuation amid mixed sector returns, sparking debate on whether this is the right entry point.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "NIKE",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Olympics",
      "entity2_type": "EVENT",
      "sentence": "NIKE (NKE) Teams With Special Olympics For Global Youth Sport Inclusion Initiative\nNeutral Sentiment:\nOakmark’s Q2 investor letter revisits Nike’s valuation amid mixed sector returns, sparking debate on whether this is the right entry point.",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "NIKE",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Oakmark",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "NIKE (NKE) Teams With Special Olympics For Global Youth Sport Inclusion Initiative\nNeutral Sentiment:\nOakmark’s Q2 investor letter revisits Nike’s valuation amid mixed sector returns, sparking debate on whether this is the right entry point.",
      "distance": 19
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "NIKE",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Q2",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "NIKE (NKE) Teams With Special Olympics For Global Youth Sport Inclusion Initiative\nNeutral Sentiment:\nOakmark’s Q2 investor letter revisits Nike’s valuation amid mixed sector returns, sparking debate on whether this is the right entry point.",
      "distance": 21
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "NIKE",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Nike",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "NIKE (NKE) Teams With Special Olympics For Global Youth Sport Inclusion Initiative\nNeutral Sentiment:\nOakmark’s Q2 investor letter revisits Nike’s valuation amid mixed sector returns, sparking debate on whether this is the right entry point.",
      "distance": 25
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "NKE",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Special",
      "entity2_type": "EVENT",
      "sentence": "NIKE (NKE) Teams With Special Olympics For Global Youth Sport Inclusion Initiative\nNeutral Sentiment:\nOakmark’s Q2 investor letter revisits Nike’s valuation amid mixed sector returns, sparking debate on whether this is the right entry point.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "NKE",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Olympics",
      "entity2_type": "EVENT",
      "sentence": "NIKE (NKE) Teams With Special Olympics For Global Youth Sport Inclusion Initiative\nNeutral Sentiment:\nOakmark’s Q2 investor letter revisits Nike’s valuation amid mixed sector returns, sparking debate on whether this is the right entry point.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "NKE",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Oakmark",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "NIKE (NKE) Teams With Special Olympics For Global Youth Sport Inclusion Initiative\nNeutral Sentiment:\nOakmark’s Q2 investor letter revisits Nike’s valuation amid mixed sector returns, sparking debate on whether this is the right entry point.",
      "distance": 17
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "NKE",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Q2",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "NIKE (NKE) Teams With Special Olympics For Global Youth Sport Inclusion Initiative\nNeutral Sentiment:\nOakmark’s Q2 investor letter revisits Nike’s valuation amid mixed sector returns, sparking debate on whether this is the right entry point.",
      "distance": 19
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "NKE",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Nike",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "NIKE (NKE) Teams With Special Olympics For Global Youth Sport Inclusion Initiative\nNeutral Sentiment:\nOakmark’s Q2 investor letter revisits Nike’s valuation amid mixed sector returns, sparking debate on whether this is the right entry point.",
      "distance": 23
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Special",
      "entity1_type": "EVENT",
      "entity2": "Olympics",
      "entity2_type": "EVENT",
      "sentence": "NIKE (NKE) Teams With Special Olympics For Global Youth Sport Inclusion Initiative\nNeutral Sentiment:\nOakmark’s Q2 investor letter revisits Nike’s valuation amid mixed sector returns, sparking debate on whether this is the right entry point.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Special",
      "entity1_type": "EVENT",
      "entity2": "Oakmark",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "NIKE (NKE) Teams With Special Olympics For Global Youth Sport Inclusion Initiative\nNeutral Sentiment:\nOakmark’s Q2 investor letter revisits Nike’s valuation amid mixed sector returns, sparking debate on whether this is the right entry point.",
      "distance": 13
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Special",
      "entity1_type": "EVENT",
      "entity2": "Q2",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "NIKE (NKE) Teams With Special Olympics For Global Youth Sport Inclusion Initiative\nNeutral Sentiment:\nOakmark’s Q2 investor letter revisits Nike’s valuation amid mixed sector returns, sparking debate on whether this is the right entry point.",
      "distance": 15
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Special",
      "entity1_type": "EVENT",
      "entity2": "Nike",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "NIKE (NKE) Teams With Special Olympics For Global Youth Sport Inclusion Initiative\nNeutral Sentiment:\nOakmark’s Q2 investor letter revisits Nike’s valuation amid mixed sector returns, sparking debate on whether this is the right entry point.",
      "distance": 19
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Olympics",
      "entity1_type": "EVENT",
      "entity2": "Oakmark",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "NIKE (NKE) Teams With Special Olympics For Global Youth Sport Inclusion Initiative\nNeutral Sentiment:\nOakmark’s Q2 investor letter revisits Nike’s valuation amid mixed sector returns, sparking debate on whether this is the right entry point.",
      "distance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Olympics",
      "entity1_type": "EVENT",
      "entity2": "Q2",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "NIKE (NKE) Teams With Special Olympics For Global Youth Sport Inclusion Initiative\nNeutral Sentiment:\nOakmark’s Q2 investor letter revisits Nike’s valuation amid mixed sector returns, sparking debate on whether this is the right entry point.",
      "distance": 14
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Olympics",
      "entity1_type": "EVENT",
      "entity2": "Nike",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "NIKE (NKE) Teams With Special Olympics For Global Youth Sport Inclusion Initiative\nNeutral Sentiment:\nOakmark’s Q2 investor letter revisits Nike’s valuation amid mixed sector returns, sparking debate on whether this is the right entry point.",
      "distance": 18
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Oakmark",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Q2",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "NIKE (NKE) Teams With Special Olympics For Global Youth Sport Inclusion Initiative\nNeutral Sentiment:\nOakmark’s Q2 investor letter revisits Nike’s valuation amid mixed sector returns, sparking debate on whether this is the right entry point.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Oakmark",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Nike",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "NIKE (NKE) Teams With Special Olympics For Global Youth Sport Inclusion Initiative\nNeutral Sentiment:\nOakmark’s Q2 investor letter revisits Nike’s valuation amid mixed sector returns, sparking debate on whether this is the right entry point.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Q2",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "Nike",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "NIKE (NKE) Teams With Special Olympics For Global Youth Sport Inclusion Initiative\nNeutral Sentiment:\nOakmark’s Q2 investor letter revisits Nike’s valuation amid mixed sector returns, sparking debate on whether this is the right entry point.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Nike",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "NKE",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Is this the Best Time to Invest in Nike (NKE)?",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Hypebeast",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Nike",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Hypebeast highlights Nike’s new Air Superfly release, showcasing ongoing product innovation that may support brand momentum.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Hypebeast",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Air",
      "entity2_type": "PRODUCT",
      "sentence": "Hypebeast highlights Nike’s new Air Superfly release, showcasing ongoing product innovation that may support brand momentum.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Hypebeast",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Superfly",
      "entity2_type": "PRODUCT",
      "sentence": "Hypebeast highlights Nike’s new Air Superfly release, showcasing ongoing product innovation that may support brand momentum.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Nike",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Air",
      "entity2_type": "PRODUCT",
      "sentence": "Hypebeast highlights Nike’s new Air Superfly release, showcasing ongoing product innovation that may support brand momentum.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Nike",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Superfly",
      "entity2_type": "PRODUCT",
      "sentence": "Hypebeast highlights Nike’s new Air Superfly release, showcasing ongoing product innovation that may support brand momentum.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Air",
      "entity1_type": "PRODUCT",
      "entity2": "Superfly",
      "entity2_type": "PRODUCT",
      "sentence": "Hypebeast highlights Nike’s new Air Superfly release, showcasing ongoing product innovation that may support brand momentum.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Nike",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "the",
      "entity2_type": "PRODUCT",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Nike",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Iconic",
      "entity2_type": "PRODUCT",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Nike",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Air",
      "entity2_type": "PRODUCT",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Nike",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Superfly",
      "entity2_type": "PRODUCT",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Nike",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Zacks",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 15
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Nike",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Research",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 16
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Nike",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Q1",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 19
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Nike",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "2026",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 20
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Nike",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Nike",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 24
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Nike",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "0.27",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 27
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Nike",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "0.35",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 30
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "the",
      "entity1_type": "PRODUCT",
      "entity2": "Iconic",
      "entity2_type": "PRODUCT",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "the",
      "entity1_type": "PRODUCT",
      "entity2": "Air",
      "entity2_type": "PRODUCT",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "the",
      "entity1_type": "PRODUCT",
      "entity2": "Superfly",
      "entity2_type": "PRODUCT",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "the",
      "entity1_type": "PRODUCT",
      "entity2": "Zacks",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 13
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "the",
      "entity1_type": "PRODUCT",
      "entity2": "Research",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 14
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "the",
      "entity1_type": "PRODUCT",
      "entity2": "Q1",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 17
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "the",
      "entity1_type": "PRODUCT",
      "entity2": "2026",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 18
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "the",
      "entity1_type": "PRODUCT",
      "entity2": "Nike",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 22
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "the",
      "entity1_type": "PRODUCT",
      "entity2": "0.27",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 25
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "the",
      "entity1_type": "PRODUCT",
      "entity2": "0.35",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 28
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Iconic",
      "entity1_type": "PRODUCT",
      "entity2": "Air",
      "entity2_type": "PRODUCT",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Iconic",
      "entity1_type": "PRODUCT",
      "entity2": "Superfly",
      "entity2_type": "PRODUCT",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Iconic",
      "entity1_type": "PRODUCT",
      "entity2": "Zacks",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Iconic",
      "entity1_type": "PRODUCT",
      "entity2": "Research",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 13
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Iconic",
      "entity1_type": "PRODUCT",
      "entity2": "Q1",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 16
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Iconic",
      "entity1_type": "PRODUCT",
      "entity2": "2026",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 17
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Iconic",
      "entity1_type": "PRODUCT",
      "entity2": "Nike",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 21
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Iconic",
      "entity1_type": "PRODUCT",
      "entity2": "0.27",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 24
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Iconic",
      "entity1_type": "PRODUCT",
      "entity2": "0.35",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 27
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Air",
      "entity1_type": "PRODUCT",
      "entity2": "Superfly",
      "entity2_type": "PRODUCT",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Air",
      "entity1_type": "PRODUCT",
      "entity2": "Zacks",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Air",
      "entity1_type": "PRODUCT",
      "entity2": "Research",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Air",
      "entity1_type": "PRODUCT",
      "entity2": "Q1",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 15
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Air",
      "entity1_type": "PRODUCT",
      "entity2": "2026",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 16
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Air",
      "entity1_type": "PRODUCT",
      "entity2": "Nike",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 20
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Air",
      "entity1_type": "PRODUCT",
      "entity2": "0.27",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 23
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Air",
      "entity1_type": "PRODUCT",
      "entity2": "0.35",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 26
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Superfly",
      "entity1_type": "PRODUCT",
      "entity2": "Zacks",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Superfly",
      "entity1_type": "PRODUCT",
      "entity2": "Research",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Superfly",
      "entity1_type": "PRODUCT",
      "entity2": "Q1",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 14
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Superfly",
      "entity1_type": "PRODUCT",
      "entity2": "2026",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 15
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Superfly",
      "entity1_type": "PRODUCT",
      "entity2": "Nike",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 19
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Superfly",
      "entity1_type": "PRODUCT",
      "entity2": "0.27",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 22
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Superfly",
      "entity1_type": "PRODUCT",
      "entity2": "0.35",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 25
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Zacks",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Research",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Zacks",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Q1",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Zacks",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "2026",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Zacks",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Nike",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Zacks",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "0.27",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Zacks",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "0.35",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 15
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Research",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Q1",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Research",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "2026",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Research",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Nike",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Research",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "0.27",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Research",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "0.35",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 14
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Q1",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "2026",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Q1",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "Nike",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Q1",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "0.27",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Q1",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "0.35",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "2026",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "Nike",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "2026",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "0.27",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "2026",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "0.35",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Nike",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "0.27",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Nike",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "0.35",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "0.27",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "0.35",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Nike Revives the Iconic Air Superfly with a Futuristic Exclusive\nNegative Sentiment:\nZacks Research cut its Q1 2026 EPS estimate for Nike to $0.27 from $0.35, signaling weaker near-term profit expectations.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Zacks",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Research",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Zacks Research Has Bearish Estimate for NIKE Q1 Earnings\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Zacks",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "NIKE",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Zacks Research Has Bearish Estimate for NIKE Q1 Earnings\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Zacks",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Q1",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Zacks Research Has Bearish Estimate for NIKE Q1 Earnings\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Research",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "NIKE",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Zacks Research Has Bearish Estimate for NIKE Q1 Earnings\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Research",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Q1",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Zacks Research Has Bearish Estimate for NIKE Q1 Earnings\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "NIKE",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Q1",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Zacks Research Has Bearish Estimate for NIKE Q1 Earnings\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "NKE",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "five",
      "entity2_type": "CARDINAL",
      "sentence": "An Investors.com article flags NKE among five S&P 500 stocks whose earnings are poised to plunge in the coming quarter.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "NKE",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "the",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "An Investors.com article flags NKE among five S&P 500 stocks whose earnings are poised to plunge in the coming quarter.",
      "distance": 13
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "NKE",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "coming",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "An Investors.com article flags NKE among five S&P 500 stocks whose earnings are poised to plunge in the coming quarter.",
      "distance": 14
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "NKE",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "quarter",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "An Investors.com article flags NKE among five S&P 500 stocks whose earnings are poised to plunge in the coming quarter.",
      "distance": 15
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "five",
      "entity1_type": "CARDINAL",
      "entity2": "the",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "An Investors.com article flags NKE among five S&P 500 stocks whose earnings are poised to plunge in the coming quarter.",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "five",
      "entity1_type": "CARDINAL",
      "entity2": "coming",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "An Investors.com article flags NKE among five S&P 500 stocks whose earnings are poised to plunge in the coming quarter.",
      "distance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "five",
      "entity1_type": "CARDINAL",
      "entity2": "quarter",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "An Investors.com article flags NKE among five S&P 500 stocks whose earnings are poised to plunge in the coming quarter.",
      "distance": 13
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "the",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "coming",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "An Investors.com article flags NKE among five S&P 500 stocks whose earnings are poised to plunge in the coming quarter.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "the",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "quarter",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "An Investors.com article flags NKE among five S&P 500 stocks whose earnings are poised to plunge in the coming quarter.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "coming",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "quarter",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "An Investors.com article flags NKE among five S&P 500 stocks whose earnings are poised to plunge in the coming quarter.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Five",
      "entity1_type": "CARDINAL",
      "entity2": "Any",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Five S&P 500 Stocks' Earnings Poised To Plunge Any Day Now\nPosted 2h ago\nAI Generated.",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Five",
      "entity1_type": "CARDINAL",
      "entity2": "Day",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Five S&P 500 Stocks' Earnings Poised To Plunge Any Day Now\nPosted 2h ago\nAI Generated.",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Five",
      "entity1_type": "CARDINAL",
      "entity2": "2h",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Five S&P 500 Stocks' Earnings Poised To Plunge Any Day Now\nPosted 2h ago\nAI Generated.",
      "distance": 14
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Five",
      "entity1_type": "CARDINAL",
      "entity2": "ago",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Five S&P 500 Stocks' Earnings Poised To Plunge Any Day Now\nPosted 2h ago\nAI Generated.",
      "distance": 15
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Any",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "Day",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Five S&P 500 Stocks' Earnings Poised To Plunge Any Day Now\nPosted 2h ago\nAI Generated.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Any",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "2h",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Five S&P 500 Stocks' Earnings Poised To Plunge Any Day Now\nPosted 2h ago\nAI Generated.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Any",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "ago",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Five S&P 500 Stocks' Earnings Poised To Plunge Any Day Now\nPosted 2h ago\nAI Generated.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Day",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "2h",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Five S&P 500 Stocks' Earnings Poised To Plunge Any Day Now\nPosted 2h ago\nAI Generated.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Day",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "ago",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Five S&P 500 Stocks' Earnings Poised To Plunge Any Day Now\nPosted 2h ago\nAI Generated.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "2h",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "ago",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Five S&P 500 Stocks' Earnings Poised To Plunge Any Day Now\nPosted 2h ago\nAI Generated.",
      "distance": 1
    }
  ],
  "key_phrases": [
    {
      "text": "profit forecasts",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "financial_metric"
    },
    {
      "text": "several bullish themes",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "Zacks Research",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "its Q1 2026 EPS estimate",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "a report",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "S&P 500 names",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "potentially plunging earnings",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "financial_metric"
    },
    {
      "text": "attractive valuation",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "expanded trading access",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "brand-strengthening initiatives",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "a rebound",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
      "text": "Positive Sentiment",
      "type": "noun_chunk",
      "category": "general"
    },
    {
