{
  "ticker": "SW",
  "entities": [
    {
      "text": "Smurfit Westrock PLC",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 0,
      "end": 20,
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock PLC (NYSE:SW) saw a mix of contract wins and analyst updates today, driving its share performance.",
      "context": "Smurfit Westrock PLC (NYSE:SW) saw a mix of contract wins and analyst",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "SW",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 27,
      "end": 29,
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock PLC (NYSE:SW) saw a mix of contract wins and analyst updates today, driving its share performance.",
      "context": "Smurfit Westrock PLC (NYSE:SW) saw a mix of contract wins and analyst updates t",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "today",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 78,
      "end": 83,
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock PLC (NYSE:SW) saw a mix of contract wins and analyst updates today, driving its share performance.",
      "context": "W) saw a mix of contract wins and analyst updates today, driving its share performance. Investors are rea",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Smurfit Westrock",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 227,
      "end": 243,
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nSmurfit Westrock won a multi-year contract in Ireland to supply tobacco product identification packaging, strengthening its regulated-products segment.",
      "context": "gets, and earnings forecasts:\nPositive Sentiment:\nSmurfit Westrock won a multi-year contract in Ireland to supply to",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "multi-year",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 250,
      "end": 260,
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nSmurfit Westrock won a multi-year contract in Ireland to supply tobacco product identification packaging, strengthening its regulated-products segment.",
      "context": "casts:\nPositive Sentiment:\nSmurfit Westrock won a multi-year contract in Ireland to supply tobacco product ide",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Ireland",
      "label": "GPE",
      "start": 273,
      "end": 280,
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nSmurfit Westrock won a multi-year contract in Ireland to supply tobacco product identification packaging, strengthening its regulated-products segment.",
      "context": "nt:\nSmurfit Westrock won a multi-year contract in Ireland to supply tobacco product identification packagin",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": true,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Smurfit Westrock",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 379,
      "end": 395,
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "context": "ng, strengthening its regulated-products segment.\nSmurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sent",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Irish",
      "label": "NORP",
      "start": 401,
      "end": 406,
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "context": "regulated-products segment.\nSmurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTrui",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Truist Financial",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 452,
      "end": 468,
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "context": "rish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "SW",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 496,
      "end": 498,
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "context": "ment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rati",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "50.00",
      "label": "MONEY",
      "start": 505,
      "end": 510,
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "context": "ist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": true
    },
    {
      "text": "54.00",
      "label": "MONEY",
      "start": 515,
      "end": 520,
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "context": "ial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 1",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": true
    },
    {
      "text": "roughly 14.4%",
      "label": "PERCENT",
      "start": 561,
      "end": 574,
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "context": "to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.\nSmurfit Westrock (NYSE:SW) Price Target R",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": true
    },
    {
      "text": "Smurfit Westrock",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 583,
      "end": 599,
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock (NYSE:SW) Price Target Raised to $54.00",
      "context": "ed a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.\nSmurfit Westrock (NYSE:SW) Price Target Raised to $54.00\nPositive",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "SW",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 606,
      "end": 608,
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock (NYSE:SW) Price Target Raised to $54.00",
      "context": "ying roughly 14.4% upside.\nSmurfit Westrock (NYSE:SW) Price Target Raised to $54.00\nPositive Sentiment",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "54.00",
      "label": "MONEY",
      "start": 634,
      "end": 639,
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock (NYSE:SW) Price Target Raised to $54.00",
      "context": "murfit Westrock (NYSE:SW) Price Target Raised to $54.00\nPositive Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley set a new $53.",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": true
    },
    {
      "text": "Morgan Stanley",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 660,
      "end": 674,
      "sentence": "Morgan Stanley set a new $53.00 price target on SW, signaling confidence in the company’s mid-cycle earnings power.",
      "context": "Price Target Raised to $54.00\nPositive Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley set a new $53.00 price target on SW, signaling co",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "53.00",
      "label": "MONEY",
      "start": 686,
      "end": 691,
      "sentence": "Morgan Stanley set a new $53.00 price target on SW, signaling confidence in the company’s mid-cycle earnings power.",
      "context": ".00\nPositive Sentiment:\nMorgan Stanley set a new $53.00 price target on SW, signaling confidence in the c",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": true
    },
    {
      "text": "SW",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 708,
      "end": 710,
      "sentence": "Morgan Stanley set a new $53.00 price target on SW, signaling confidence in the company’s mid-cycle earnings power.",
      "context": ":\nMorgan Stanley set a new $53.00 price target on SW, signaling confidence in the company’s mid-cycle",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "mid-cycle",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 750,
      "end": 759,
      "sentence": "Morgan Stanley set a new $53.00 price target on SW, signaling confidence in the company’s mid-cycle earnings power.",
      "context": "rget on SW, signaling confidence in the company’s mid-cycle earnings power.\nSmurfit Westrock (NYSE:SW) Given",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Smurfit Westrock",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 776,
      "end": 792,
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock (NYSE:SW) Given New $53.00 Price Target at Morgan Stanley\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "context": "idence in the company’s mid-cycle earnings power.\nSmurfit Westrock (NYSE:SW) Given New $53.00 Price Target at Morgan",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "SW",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 799,
      "end": 801,
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock (NYSE:SW) Given New $53.00 Price Target at Morgan Stanley\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "context": "mid-cycle earnings power.\nSmurfit Westrock (NYSE:SW) Given New $53.00 Price Target at Morgan Stanley",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "53.00",
      "label": "MONEY",
      "start": 814,
      "end": 819,
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock (NYSE:SW) Given New $53.00 Price Target at Morgan Stanley\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "context": "ings power.\nSmurfit Westrock (NYSE:SW) Given New $53.00 Price Target at Morgan Stanley\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": true
    },
    {
      "text": "Morgan Stanley",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 836,
      "end": 850,
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock (NYSE:SW) Given New $53.00 Price Target at Morgan Stanley\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "context": "strock (NYSE:SW) Given New $53.00 Price Target at Morgan Stanley\nNeutral Sentiment:\nSeaport Research Partners fore",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Seaport Research Partners",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 870,
      "end": 895,
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "context": "Price Target at Morgan Stanley\nNeutral Sentiment:\nSeaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS o",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Q2",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 905,
      "end": 907,
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "context": "ral Sentiment:\nSeaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "0.55",
      "label": "MONEY",
      "start": 916,
      "end": 920,
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "context": "nt:\nSeaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with furt",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": true
    },
    {
      "text": "full-year",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 925,
      "end": 934,
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "context": "rt Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "2025",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 935,
      "end": 939,
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "context": "h Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "3.25",
      "label": "MONEY",
      "start": 948,
      "end": 952,
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "context": "recast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": true
    },
    {
      "text": "SW",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 957,
      "end": 959,
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "context": "EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 fo",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "0.78",
      "label": "MONEY",
      "start": 988,
      "end": 992,
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "context": "5 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.\nQ2 Ea",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": true
    },
    {
      "text": "Q3",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 997,
      "end": 999,
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "context": "$3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.\nQ2 Earnings",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "0.72",
      "label": "MONEY",
      "start": 1002,
      "end": 1006,
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "context": "for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.\nQ2 Earnings Forecas",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": true
    },
    {
      "text": "Q4",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 1011,
      "end": 1013,
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "context": "with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.\nQ2 Earnings Forecast for S",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "3.59",
      "label": "MONEY",
      "start": 1020,
      "end": 1024,
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "context": "her estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.\nQ2 Earnings Forecast for SW Issued By",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": true
    },
    {
      "text": "FY2026",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 1029,
      "end": 1035,
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "context": "ates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.\nQ2 Earnings Forecast for SW Issued By Seaport Re",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Q2",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 1037,
      "end": 1039,
      "sentence": "Q2 Earnings Forecast for SW Issued By Seaport Res Ptn\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "context": "$0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.\nQ2 Earnings Forecast for SW Issued By Seaport Res Pt",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "SW",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1062,
      "end": 1064,
      "sentence": "Q2 Earnings Forecast for SW Issued By Seaport Res Ptn\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "context": "4, and $3.59 for FY2026.\nQ2 Earnings Forecast for SW Issued By Seaport Res Ptn\nNeutral Sentiment:\nWell",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Seaport Res Ptn",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1075,
      "end": 1090,
      "sentence": "Q2 Earnings Forecast for SW Issued By Seaport Res Ptn\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "context": "for FY2026.\nQ2 Earnings Forecast for SW Issued By Seaport Res Ptn\nNeutral Sentiment:\nWells Fargo increased its SW t",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Wells Fargo",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1110,
      "end": 1121,
      "sentence": "Wells Fargo increased its SW target from $43.00 to $45.00 but kept an “equal weight” rating, indicating limited near-term upside.",
      "context": "r SW Issued By Seaport Res Ptn\nNeutral Sentiment:\nWells Fargo increased its SW target from $43.00 to $45.00 but",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "SW",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1136,
      "end": 1138,
      "sentence": "Wells Fargo increased its SW target from $43.00 to $45.00 but kept an “equal weight” rating, indicating limited near-term upside.",
      "context": "Ptn\nNeutral Sentiment:\nWells Fargo increased its SW target from $43.00 to $45.00 but kept an “equal w",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "43.00",
      "label": "MONEY",
      "start": 1152,
      "end": 1157,
      "sentence": "Wells Fargo increased its SW target from $43.00 to $45.00 but kept an “equal weight” rating, indicating limited near-term upside.",
      "context": "timent:\nWells Fargo increased its SW target from $43.00 to $45.00 but kept an “equal weight” rating, indi",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": true
    },
    {
      "text": "45.00",
      "label": "MONEY",
      "start": 1162,
      "end": 1167,
      "sentence": "Wells Fargo increased its SW target from $43.00 to $45.00 but kept an “equal weight” rating, indicating limited near-term upside.",
      "context": "lls Fargo increased its SW target from $43.00 to $45.00 but kept an “equal weight” rating, indicating lim",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": true
    },
    {
      "text": "Wells Fargo & Company",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1240,
      "end": 1261,
      "sentence": "Wells Fargo & Company Issues Positive Forecast for Smurfit Westrock (NYSE:SW) Stock Price\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "context": "ght” rating, indicating limited near-term upside.\nWells Fargo & Company Issues Positive Forecast for Smurfit Westrock (NY",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Smurfit Westrock",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1291,
      "end": 1307,
      "sentence": "Wells Fargo & Company Issues Positive Forecast for Smurfit Westrock (NYSE:SW) Stock Price\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "context": "ells Fargo & Company Issues Positive Forecast for Smurfit Westrock (NYSE:SW) Stock Price\nNegative Sentiment:\nDespite",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "daily",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 1360,
      "end": 1365,
      "sentence": "Despite a daily gain, SW underperformed peers on Thursday, highlighting potential competitive or sentiment headwinds.",
      "context": "YSE:SW) Stock Price\nNegative Sentiment:\nDespite a daily gain, SW underperformed peers on Thursday, highli",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "SW",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1372,
      "end": 1374,
      "sentence": "Despite a daily gain, SW underperformed peers on Thursday, highlighting potential competitive or sentiment headwinds.",
      "context": "k Price\nNegative Sentiment:\nDespite a daily gain, SW underperformed peers on Thursday, highlighting po",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Thursday",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 1399,
      "end": 1407,
      "sentence": "Despite a daily gain, SW underperformed peers on Thursday, highlighting potential competitive or sentiment headwinds.",
      "context": "Despite a daily gain, SW underperformed peers on Thursday, highlighting potential competitive or sentiment",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Smurfit Westrock PLC",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1468,
      "end": 1488,
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock PLC stock underperforms Thursday when compared to competitors despite daily gains\nPosted 1+ days ago\nAI Generated. May Contain Errors.",
      "context": "ing potential competitive or sentiment headwinds.\nSmurfit Westrock PLC stock underperforms Thursday when compared to com",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Thursday",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 1509,
      "end": 1517,
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock PLC stock underperforms Thursday when compared to competitors despite daily gains\nPosted 1+ days ago\nAI Generated. May Contain Errors.",
      "context": "adwinds.\nSmurfit Westrock PLC stock underperforms Thursday when compared to competitors despite daily gains",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "daily",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 1555,
      "end": 1560,
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock PLC stock underperforms Thursday when compared to competitors despite daily gains\nPosted 1+ days ago\nAI Generated. May Contain Errors.",
      "context": "rms Thursday when compared to competitors despite daily gains\nPosted 1+ days ago\nAI Generated. May Contai",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "1+ days ago",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 1574,
      "end": 1585,
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock PLC stock underperforms Thursday when compared to competitors despite daily gains\nPosted 1+ days ago\nAI Generated. May Contain Errors.",
      "context": "ompared to competitors despite daily gains\nPosted 1+ days ago\nAI Generated. May Contain Errors.",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "AI Generated",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1586,
      "end": 1598,
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock PLC stock underperforms Thursday when compared to competitors despite daily gains\nPosted 1+ days ago\nAI Generated. May Contain Errors.",
      "context": "ompetitors despite daily gains\nPosted 1+ days ago\nAI Generated. May Contain Errors.",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    }
  ],
  "relationships": [
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "PLC",
      "verb": "saw",
      "object": "mix",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock PLC (NYSE:SW) saw a mix of contract wins and analyst updates today, driving its share performance.",
      "importance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Westrock",
      "verb": "won",
      "object": "contract",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nSmurfit Westrock won a multi-year contract in Ireland to supply tobacco product identification packaging, strengthening its regulated-products segment.",
      "importance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Westrock",
      "verb": "wins",
      "object": "contract",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "importance": 14
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Financial",
      "verb": "raised",
      "object": "target",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "importance": 14
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Stanley",
      "verb": "set",
      "object": "target",
      "sentence": "Morgan Stanley set a new $53.00 price target on SW, signaling confidence in the company’s mid-cycle earnings power.",
      "importance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Westrock",
      "verb": "Given",
      "object": "Target",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock (NYSE:SW) Given New $53.00 Price Target at Morgan Stanley\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "importance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Partners",
      "verb": "forecast",
      "object": "EPS",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "importance": 18
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Fargo",
      "verb": "increased",
      "object": "target",
      "sentence": "Wells Fargo increased its SW target from $43.00 to $45.00 but kept an “equal weight” rating, indicating limited near-term upside.",
      "importance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Fargo",
      "verb": "Issues",
      "object": "Forecast",
      "sentence": "Wells Fargo & Company Issues Positive Forecast for Smurfit Westrock (NYSE:SW) Stock Price\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "importance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "SW",
      "verb": "underperformed",
      "object": "peers",
      "sentence": "Despite a daily gain, SW underperformed peers on Thursday, highlighting potential competitive or sentiment headwinds.",
      "importance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Smurfit",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Westrock",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock PLC (NYSE:SW) saw a mix of contract wins and analyst updates today, driving its share performance.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Smurfit",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "PLC",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock PLC (NYSE:SW) saw a mix of contract wins and analyst updates today, driving its share performance.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Smurfit",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "SW",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock PLC (NYSE:SW) saw a mix of contract wins and analyst updates today, driving its share performance.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Smurfit",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "today",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock PLC (NYSE:SW) saw a mix of contract wins and analyst updates today, driving its share performance.",
      "distance": 17
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Westrock",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "PLC",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock PLC (NYSE:SW) saw a mix of contract wins and analyst updates today, driving its share performance.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Westrock",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "SW",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock PLC (NYSE:SW) saw a mix of contract wins and analyst updates today, driving its share performance.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Westrock",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "today",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock PLC (NYSE:SW) saw a mix of contract wins and analyst updates today, driving its share performance.",
      "distance": 16
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "PLC",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "SW",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock PLC (NYSE:SW) saw a mix of contract wins and analyst updates today, driving its share performance.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "PLC",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "today",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock PLC (NYSE:SW) saw a mix of contract wins and analyst updates today, driving its share performance.",
      "distance": 15
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "SW",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "today",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock PLC (NYSE:SW) saw a mix of contract wins and analyst updates today, driving its share performance.",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Smurfit",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Westrock",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nSmurfit Westrock won a multi-year contract in Ireland to supply tobacco product identification packaging, strengthening its regulated-products segment.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Smurfit",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "multi",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nSmurfit Westrock won a multi-year contract in Ireland to supply tobacco product identification packaging, strengthening its regulated-products segment.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Smurfit",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nSmurfit Westrock won a multi-year contract in Ireland to supply tobacco product identification packaging, strengthening its regulated-products segment.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Smurfit",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "year",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nSmurfit Westrock won a multi-year contract in Ireland to supply tobacco product identification packaging, strengthening its regulated-products segment.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Smurfit",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Ireland",
      "entity2_type": "GPE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nSmurfit Westrock won a multi-year contract in Ireland to supply tobacco product identification packaging, strengthening its regulated-products segment.",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Westrock",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "multi",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nSmurfit Westrock won a multi-year contract in Ireland to supply tobacco product identification packaging, strengthening its regulated-products segment.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Westrock",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nSmurfit Westrock won a multi-year contract in Ireland to supply tobacco product identification packaging, strengthening its regulated-products segment.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Westrock",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "year",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nSmurfit Westrock won a multi-year contract in Ireland to supply tobacco product identification packaging, strengthening its regulated-products segment.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Westrock",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Ireland",
      "entity2_type": "GPE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nSmurfit Westrock won a multi-year contract in Ireland to supply tobacco product identification packaging, strengthening its regulated-products segment.",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "multi",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nSmurfit Westrock won a multi-year contract in Ireland to supply tobacco product identification packaging, strengthening its regulated-products segment.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "multi",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "year",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nSmurfit Westrock won a multi-year contract in Ireland to supply tobacco product identification packaging, strengthening its regulated-products segment.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "multi",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "Ireland",
      "entity2_type": "GPE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nSmurfit Westrock won a multi-year contract in Ireland to supply tobacco product identification packaging, strengthening its regulated-products segment.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "year",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nSmurfit Westrock won a multi-year contract in Ireland to supply tobacco product identification packaging, strengthening its regulated-products segment.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "Ireland",
      "entity2_type": "GPE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nSmurfit Westrock won a multi-year contract in Ireland to supply tobacco product identification packaging, strengthening its regulated-products segment.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "year",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "Ireland",
      "entity2_type": "GPE",
      "sentence": "Positive Sentiment:\nSmurfit Westrock won a multi-year contract in Ireland to supply tobacco product identification packaging, strengthening its regulated-products segment.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Smurfit",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Westrock",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Smurfit",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Irish",
      "entity2_type": "NORP",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Smurfit",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Truist",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 13
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Smurfit",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Financial",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 14
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Smurfit",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "SW",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 20
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Smurfit",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "50.00",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 23
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Smurfit",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "54.00",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 26
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Smurfit",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "roughly",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 36
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Smurfit",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "14.4",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 37
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Smurfit",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "%",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 38
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Westrock",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Irish",
      "entity2_type": "NORP",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Westrock",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Truist",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Westrock",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Financial",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 13
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Westrock",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "SW",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 19
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Westrock",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "50.00",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 22
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Westrock",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "54.00",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 25
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Westrock",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "roughly",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 35
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Westrock",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "14.4",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 36
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Westrock",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "%",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 37
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Irish",
      "entity1_type": "NORP",
      "entity2": "Truist",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Irish",
      "entity1_type": "NORP",
      "entity2": "Financial",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Irish",
      "entity1_type": "NORP",
      "entity2": "SW",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 17
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Irish",
      "entity1_type": "NORP",
      "entity2": "50.00",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 20
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Irish",
      "entity1_type": "NORP",
      "entity2": "54.00",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 23
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Irish",
      "entity1_type": "NORP",
      "entity2": "roughly",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 33
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Irish",
      "entity1_type": "NORP",
      "entity2": "14.4",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 34
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Irish",
      "entity1_type": "NORP",
      "entity2": "%",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 35
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Truist",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Financial",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Truist",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "SW",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Truist",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "50.00",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Truist",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "54.00",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 13
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Truist",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "roughly",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 23
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Truist",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "14.4",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 24
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Truist",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "%",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 25
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Financial",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "SW",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Financial",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "50.00",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Financial",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "54.00",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Financial",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "roughly",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 22
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Financial",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "14.4",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 23
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Financial",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "%",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 24
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "SW",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "50.00",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "SW",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "54.00",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "SW",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "roughly",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 16
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "SW",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "14.4",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 17
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "SW",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "%",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 18
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "50.00",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "54.00",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "50.00",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "roughly",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 13
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "50.00",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "14.4",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 14
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "50.00",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "%",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 15
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "54.00",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "roughly",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "54.00",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "14.4",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "54.00",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "%",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "roughly",
      "entity1_type": "PERCENT",
      "entity2": "14.4",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "roughly",
      "entity1_type": "PERCENT",
      "entity2": "%",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "14.4",
      "entity1_type": "PERCENT",
      "entity2": "%",
      "entity2_type": "PERCENT",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock wins Irish contract for tobacco IDs\nPositive Sentiment:\nTruist Financial raised its price target on SW from $50.00 to $54.00 and maintained a “buy” rating, implying roughly 14.4% upside.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Smurfit",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Westrock",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock (NYSE:SW) Price Target Raised to $54.00",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Smurfit",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "SW",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock (NYSE:SW) Price Target Raised to $54.00",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Smurfit",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "54.00",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock (NYSE:SW) Price Target Raised to $54.00",
      "distance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Westrock",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "SW",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock (NYSE:SW) Price Target Raised to $54.00",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Westrock",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "54.00",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock (NYSE:SW) Price Target Raised to $54.00",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "SW",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "54.00",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock (NYSE:SW) Price Target Raised to $54.00",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Morgan",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Stanley",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Morgan Stanley set a new $53.00 price target on SW, signaling confidence in the company’s mid-cycle earnings power.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Morgan",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "53.00",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Morgan Stanley set a new $53.00 price target on SW, signaling confidence in the company’s mid-cycle earnings power.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Morgan",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "SW",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Morgan Stanley set a new $53.00 price target on SW, signaling confidence in the company’s mid-cycle earnings power.",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Morgan",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "mid",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Morgan Stanley set a new $53.00 price target on SW, signaling confidence in the company’s mid-cycle earnings power.",
      "distance": 18
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Morgan",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Morgan Stanley set a new $53.00 price target on SW, signaling confidence in the company’s mid-cycle earnings power.",
      "distance": 19
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Morgan",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "cycle",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Morgan Stanley set a new $53.00 price target on SW, signaling confidence in the company’s mid-cycle earnings power.",
      "distance": 20
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Stanley",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "53.00",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Morgan Stanley set a new $53.00 price target on SW, signaling confidence in the company’s mid-cycle earnings power.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Stanley",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "SW",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Morgan Stanley set a new $53.00 price target on SW, signaling confidence in the company’s mid-cycle earnings power.",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Stanley",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "mid",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Morgan Stanley set a new $53.00 price target on SW, signaling confidence in the company’s mid-cycle earnings power.",
      "distance": 17
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Stanley",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Morgan Stanley set a new $53.00 price target on SW, signaling confidence in the company’s mid-cycle earnings power.",
      "distance": 18
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Stanley",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "cycle",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Morgan Stanley set a new $53.00 price target on SW, signaling confidence in the company’s mid-cycle earnings power.",
      "distance": 19
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "53.00",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "SW",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Morgan Stanley set a new $53.00 price target on SW, signaling confidence in the company’s mid-cycle earnings power.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "53.00",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "mid",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Morgan Stanley set a new $53.00 price target on SW, signaling confidence in the company’s mid-cycle earnings power.",
      "distance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "53.00",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Morgan Stanley set a new $53.00 price target on SW, signaling confidence in the company’s mid-cycle earnings power.",
      "distance": 13
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "53.00",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "cycle",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Morgan Stanley set a new $53.00 price target on SW, signaling confidence in the company’s mid-cycle earnings power.",
      "distance": 14
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "SW",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "mid",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Morgan Stanley set a new $53.00 price target on SW, signaling confidence in the company’s mid-cycle earnings power.",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "SW",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Morgan Stanley set a new $53.00 price target on SW, signaling confidence in the company’s mid-cycle earnings power.",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "SW",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "cycle",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Morgan Stanley set a new $53.00 price target on SW, signaling confidence in the company’s mid-cycle earnings power.",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "mid",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Morgan Stanley set a new $53.00 price target on SW, signaling confidence in the company’s mid-cycle earnings power.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "mid",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "cycle",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Morgan Stanley set a new $53.00 price target on SW, signaling confidence in the company’s mid-cycle earnings power.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "cycle",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Morgan Stanley set a new $53.00 price target on SW, signaling confidence in the company’s mid-cycle earnings power.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Smurfit",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Westrock",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock (NYSE:SW) Given New $53.00 Price Target at Morgan Stanley\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Smurfit",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "SW",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock (NYSE:SW) Given New $53.00 Price Target at Morgan Stanley\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Smurfit",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "53.00",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock (NYSE:SW) Given New $53.00 Price Target at Morgan Stanley\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Smurfit",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Morgan",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock (NYSE:SW) Given New $53.00 Price Target at Morgan Stanley\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 14
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Smurfit",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Stanley",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock (NYSE:SW) Given New $53.00 Price Target at Morgan Stanley\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 15
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Westrock",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "SW",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock (NYSE:SW) Given New $53.00 Price Target at Morgan Stanley\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Westrock",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "53.00",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock (NYSE:SW) Given New $53.00 Price Target at Morgan Stanley\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Westrock",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Morgan",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock (NYSE:SW) Given New $53.00 Price Target at Morgan Stanley\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 13
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Westrock",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Stanley",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock (NYSE:SW) Given New $53.00 Price Target at Morgan Stanley\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 14
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "SW",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "53.00",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock (NYSE:SW) Given New $53.00 Price Target at Morgan Stanley\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "SW",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Morgan",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock (NYSE:SW) Given New $53.00 Price Target at Morgan Stanley\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "SW",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Stanley",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock (NYSE:SW) Given New $53.00 Price Target at Morgan Stanley\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "53.00",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "Morgan",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock (NYSE:SW) Given New $53.00 Price Target at Morgan Stanley\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "53.00",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "Stanley",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock (NYSE:SW) Given New $53.00 Price Target at Morgan Stanley\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Morgan",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Stanley",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Smurfit Westrock (NYSE:SW) Given New $53.00 Price Target at Morgan Stanley\nNeutral Sentiment:",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Seaport",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Research",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Seaport",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Partners",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Seaport",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Q2",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Seaport",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "0.55",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Seaport",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "full",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Seaport",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Seaport",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "year",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Seaport",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "2025",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 13
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Seaport",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "3.25",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 17
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Seaport",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "SW",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 19
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Seaport",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "0.78",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 26
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Seaport",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Q3",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 28
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Seaport",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "0.72",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 31
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Seaport",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Q4",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 33
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Seaport",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "3.59",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 37
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Seaport",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "FY2026",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 39
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Research",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Partners",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Research",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Q2",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Research",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "0.55",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Research",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "full",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Research",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Research",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "year",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Research",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "2025",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Research",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "3.25",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 16
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Research",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "SW",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 18
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Research",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "0.78",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 25
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Research",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Q3",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 27
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Research",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "0.72",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 30
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Research",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Q4",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 32
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Research",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "3.59",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 36
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Research",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "FY2026",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 38
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Partners",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Q2",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Partners",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "0.55",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Partners",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "full",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Partners",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Partners",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "year",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Partners",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "2025",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Partners",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "3.25",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 15
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Partners",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "SW",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 17
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Partners",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "0.78",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 24
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Partners",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Q3",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 26
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Partners",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "0.72",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 29
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Partners",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Q4",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 31
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Partners",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "3.59",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 35
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Partners",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "FY2026",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 37
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Q2",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "0.55",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Q2",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "full",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Q2",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Q2",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "year",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Q2",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "2025",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Q2",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "3.25",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 13
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Q2",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "SW",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 15
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Q2",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "0.78",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 22
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Q2",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "Q3",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 24
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Q2",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "0.72",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 27
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Q2",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "Q4",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 29
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Q2",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "3.59",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 33
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Q2",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "FY2026",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 35
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "0.55",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "full",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "0.55",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "0.55",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "year",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "0.55",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "2025",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "0.55",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "3.25",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "0.55",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "SW",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "0.55",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "0.78",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 18
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "0.55",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "Q3",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 20
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "0.55",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "0.72",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 23
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "0.55",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "Q4",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 25
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "0.55",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "3.59",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 29
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "0.55",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "FY2026",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 31
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "full",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "full",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "year",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "full",
      "entity1_type": "DATE",
      "entity2": "2025",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Seaport Research Partners forecast Q2 EPS of $0.55 and full-year 2025 EPS of $3.25 for SW, with further estimates of $0.78 for Q3, $0.72 for Q4, and $3.59 for FY2026.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "full",
