{
  "ticker": "TMUS",
  "entities": [
    {
      "text": "T-Mobile US, Inc.",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 0,
      "end": 17,
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US, Inc. (NASDAQ: TMUS) saw its stock react to a mix of regulatory developments, analyst actions and corporate news.",
      "context": "T-Mobile US, Inc. (NASDAQ: TMUS) saw its stock react to a mix of re",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "TMUS",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 27,
      "end": 31,
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US, Inc. (NASDAQ: TMUS) saw its stock react to a mix of regulatory developments, analyst actions and corporate news.",
      "context": "T-Mobile US, Inc. (NASDAQ: TMUS) saw its stock react to a mix of regulatory devel",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "UScellular",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 182,
      "end": 192,
      "sentence": "Recent positive catalysts include key approvals for its UScellular deal and an analyst upgrade, while negative pressures stem from downgrades, bearish technical signals and insider stock sales.",
      "context": "positive catalysts include key approvals for its UScellular deal and an analyst upgrade, while negative press",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "TMUS",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 361,
      "end": 365,
      "sentence": "Below is a summary of the drivers moving TMUS shares today:",
      "context": "k sales. Below is a summary of the drivers moving TMUS shares today:\nPositive Sentiment:\nU.S. antitrust",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "today",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 373,
      "end": 378,
      "sentence": "Below is a summary of the drivers moving TMUS shares today:",
      "context": "ow is a summary of the drivers moving TMUS shares today:\nPositive Sentiment:\nU.S. antitrust and communica",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "U.S.",
      "label": "GPE",
      "start": 400,
      "end": 404,
      "sentence": "U.S. antitrust and communications regulators cleared T-Mobile’s $4.4 billion acquisition of UScellular after the carrier agreed to end its DEI programs, removing a major hurdle to expansion.",
      "context": "ers moving TMUS shares today:\nPositive Sentiment:\nU.S. antitrust and communications regulators cleared T",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": true,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "T-Mobile’s",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 453,
      "end": 463,
      "sentence": "U.S. antitrust and communications regulators cleared T-Mobile’s $4.4 billion acquisition of UScellular after the carrier agreed to end its DEI programs, removing a major hurdle to expansion.",
      "context": ". antitrust and communications regulators cleared T-Mobile’s $4.4 billion acquisition of UScellular after the",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "$4.4 billion",
      "label": "MONEY",
      "start": 464,
      "end": 476,
      "sentence": "U.S. antitrust and communications regulators cleared T-Mobile’s $4.4 billion acquisition of UScellular after the carrier agreed to end its DEI programs, removing a major hurdle to expansion.",
      "context": "and communications regulators cleared T-Mobile’s $4.4 billion acquisition of UScellular after the carrier agree",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": true
    },
    {
      "text": "UScellular",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 492,
      "end": 502,
      "sentence": "U.S. antitrust and communications regulators cleared T-Mobile’s $4.4 billion acquisition of UScellular after the carrier agreed to end its DEI programs, removing a major hurdle to expansion.",
      "context": "rs cleared T-Mobile’s $4.4 billion acquisition of UScellular after the carrier agreed to end its DEI programs,",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Trump",
      "label": "PERSON",
      "start": 591,
      "end": 596,
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "context": "I programs, removing a major hurdle to expansion.\nTrump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mob",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": true,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "DOJ",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 599,
      "end": 602,
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "context": "ms, removing a major hurdle to expansion.\nTrump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "T-Mobile’s",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 641,
      "end": 651,
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "context": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals a",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "FCC",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 668,
      "end": 671,
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "context": "bout having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrie",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "two",
      "label": "CARDINAL",
      "start": 681,
      "end": 684,
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "context": "o approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI p",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "T-Mobile",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 685,
      "end": 693,
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "context": "prove T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nP",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Arete Research",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 762,
      "end": 776,
      "sentence": "Arete Research upgraded TMUS to a “strong-buy” rating, signaling growing analyst confidence.",
      "context": "ss carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:\nArete Research upgraded TMUS to a “strong-buy” rating, signaling",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "TMUS",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 786,
      "end": 790,
      "sentence": "Arete Research upgraded TMUS to a “strong-buy” rating, signaling growing analyst confidence.",
      "context": "grams\nPositive Sentiment:\nArete Research upgraded TMUS to a “strong-buy” rating, signaling growing analy",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "T-Mobile US",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 855,
      "end": 866,
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Upgraded by Arete Research to Strong-Buy Rating\nNeutral Sentiment:\nZacks highlights TMUS as a strong momentum stock, underpinned by favorable style scores but not necessarily fundamental changes.",
      "context": "uy” rating, signaling growing analyst confidence.\nT-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Upgraded by Arete Research to Stron",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "TMUS",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 875,
      "end": 879,
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Upgraded by Arete Research to Strong-Buy Rating\nNeutral Sentiment:\nZacks highlights TMUS as a strong momentum stock, underpinned by favorable style scores but not necessarily fundamental changes.",
      "context": "g growing analyst confidence.\nT-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Upgraded by Arete Research to Strong-Buy Rating",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Arete Research",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 893,
      "end": 907,
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Upgraded by Arete Research to Strong-Buy Rating\nNeutral Sentiment:\nZacks highlights TMUS as a strong momentum stock, underpinned by favorable style scores but not necessarily fundamental changes.",
      "context": "confidence.\nT-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Upgraded by Arete Research to Strong-Buy Rating\nNeutral Sentiment:\nZacks hig",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Zacks",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 948,
      "end": 953,
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Upgraded by Arete Research to Strong-Buy Rating\nNeutral Sentiment:\nZacks highlights TMUS as a strong momentum stock, underpinned by favorable style scores but not necessarily fundamental changes.",
      "context": "Research to Strong-Buy Rating\nNeutral Sentiment:\nZacks highlights TMUS as a strong momentum stock, under",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "TMUS",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 965,
      "end": 969,
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Upgraded by Arete Research to Strong-Buy Rating\nNeutral Sentiment:\nZacks highlights TMUS as a strong momentum stock, underpinned by favorable style scores but not necessarily fundamental changes.",
      "context": "ng-Buy Rating\nNeutral Sentiment:\nZacks highlights TMUS as a strong momentum stock, underpinned by favora",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "T-Mobile",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1088,
      "end": 1096,
      "sentence": "Here's Why T-Mobile (TMUS) is a Strong Momentum Stock\nNeutral Sentiment:\nT-Mobile is showcasing its 5G network at MLB All-Star Week with new automated fan experiences, which may boost brand engagement over the long term.",
      "context": "t not necessarily fundamental changes.\nHere's Why T-Mobile (TMUS) is a Strong Momentum Stock\nNeutral Sentime",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "TMUS",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1098,
      "end": 1102,
      "sentence": "Here's Why T-Mobile (TMUS) is a Strong Momentum Stock\nNeutral Sentiment:\nT-Mobile is showcasing its 5G network at MLB All-Star Week with new automated fan experiences, which may boost brand engagement over the long term.",
      "context": "ssarily fundamental changes.\nHere's Why T-Mobile (TMUS) is a Strong Momentum Stock\nNeutral Sentiment:\nT-",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "T-Mobile",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1150,
      "end": 1158,
      "sentence": "Here's Why T-Mobile (TMUS) is a Strong Momentum Stock\nNeutral Sentiment:\nT-Mobile is showcasing its 5G network at MLB All-Star Week with new automated fan experiences, which may boost brand engagement over the long term.",
      "context": "US) is a Strong Momentum Stock\nNeutral Sentiment:\nT-Mobile is showcasing its 5G network at MLB All-Star Week",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "MLB All-Star Week",
      "label": "EVENT",
      "start": 1191,
      "end": 1208,
      "sentence": "Here's Why T-Mobile (TMUS) is a Strong Momentum Stock\nNeutral Sentiment:\nT-Mobile is showcasing its 5G network at MLB All-Star Week with new automated fan experiences, which may boost brand engagement over the long term.",
      "context": "ntiment:\nT-Mobile is showcasing its 5G network at MLB All-Star Week with new automated fan experiences, which may boo",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "T-Mobile",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1298,
      "end": 1306,
      "sentence": "T-Mobile Brings 5G-Powered ABS, New Fan Experiences to MLB All-Star Week — Backed by America's Best Network\nNegative Sentiment:\nKeyCorp cut TMUS to a “strong sell” and lowered its Q2 EPS forecasts on concerns around slowing growth, weighing on sentiment.\nT-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Lowered to Strong Sell Rating by KeyCorp\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "context": "ch may boost brand engagement over the long term.\nT-Mobile Brings 5G-Powered ABS, New Fan Experiences to MLB",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "MLB All-Star Week",
      "label": "EVENT",
      "start": 1353,
      "end": 1370,
      "sentence": "T-Mobile Brings 5G-Powered ABS, New Fan Experiences to MLB All-Star Week — Backed by America's Best Network\nNegative Sentiment:\nKeyCorp cut TMUS to a “strong sell” and lowered its Q2 EPS forecasts on concerns around slowing growth, weighing on sentiment.\nT-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Lowered to Strong Sell Rating by KeyCorp\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "context": "ile Brings 5G-Powered ABS, New Fan Experiences to MLB All-Star Week — Backed by America's Best Network\nNegative Senti",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "America",
      "label": "GPE",
      "start": 1383,
      "end": 1390,
      "sentence": "T-Mobile Brings 5G-Powered ABS, New Fan Experiences to MLB All-Star Week — Backed by America's Best Network\nNegative Sentiment:\nKeyCorp cut TMUS to a “strong sell” and lowered its Q2 EPS forecasts on concerns around slowing growth, weighing on sentiment.\nT-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Lowered to Strong Sell Rating by KeyCorp\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "context": "Fan Experiences to MLB All-Star Week — Backed by America's Best Network\nNegative Sentiment:\nKeyCorp cut TM",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": true,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "KeyCorp",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1426,
      "end": 1433,
      "sentence": "T-Mobile Brings 5G-Powered ABS, New Fan Experiences to MLB All-Star Week — Backed by America's Best Network\nNegative Sentiment:\nKeyCorp cut TMUS to a “strong sell” and lowered its Q2 EPS forecasts on concerns around slowing growth, weighing on sentiment.\nT-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Lowered to Strong Sell Rating by KeyCorp\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "context": "ked by America's Best Network\nNegative Sentiment:\nKeyCorp cut TMUS to a “strong sell” and lowered its Q2 EP",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "TMUS",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1438,
      "end": 1442,
      "sentence": "T-Mobile Brings 5G-Powered ABS, New Fan Experiences to MLB All-Star Week — Backed by America's Best Network\nNegative Sentiment:\nKeyCorp cut TMUS to a “strong sell” and lowered its Q2 EPS forecasts on concerns around slowing growth, weighing on sentiment.\nT-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Lowered to Strong Sell Rating by KeyCorp\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "context": "ca's Best Network\nNegative Sentiment:\nKeyCorp cut TMUS to a “strong sell” and lowered its Q2 EPS forecas",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "Q2",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 1478,
      "end": 1480,
      "sentence": "T-Mobile Brings 5G-Powered ABS, New Fan Experiences to MLB All-Star Week — Backed by America's Best Network\nNegative Sentiment:\nKeyCorp cut TMUS to a “strong sell” and lowered its Q2 EPS forecasts on concerns around slowing growth, weighing on sentiment.\nT-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Lowered to Strong Sell Rating by KeyCorp\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "context": "yCorp cut TMUS to a “strong sell” and lowered its Q2 EPS forecasts on concerns around slowing growth,",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "T-Mobile US",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1553,
      "end": 1564,
      "sentence": "T-Mobile Brings 5G-Powered ABS, New Fan Experiences to MLB All-Star Week — Backed by America's Best Network\nNegative Sentiment:\nKeyCorp cut TMUS to a “strong sell” and lowered its Q2 EPS forecasts on concerns around slowing growth, weighing on sentiment.\nT-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Lowered to Strong Sell Rating by KeyCorp\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "context": "rns around slowing growth, weighing on sentiment.\nT-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Lowered to Strong Sell Rating by Ke",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "TMUS",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1573,
      "end": 1577,
      "sentence": "T-Mobile Brings 5G-Powered ABS, New Fan Experiences to MLB All-Star Week — Backed by America's Best Network\nNegative Sentiment:\nKeyCorp cut TMUS to a “strong sell” and lowered its Q2 EPS forecasts on concerns around slowing growth, weighing on sentiment.\nT-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Lowered to Strong Sell Rating by KeyCorp\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "context": "rowth, weighing on sentiment.\nT-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Lowered to Strong Sell Rating by KeyCorp\nNegativ",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "KeyCorp",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1612,
      "end": 1619,
      "sentence": "T-Mobile Brings 5G-Powered ABS, New Fan Experiences to MLB All-Star Week — Backed by America's Best Network\nNegative Sentiment:\nKeyCorp cut TMUS to a “strong sell” and lowered its Q2 EPS forecasts on concerns around slowing growth, weighing on sentiment.\nT-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Lowered to Strong Sell Rating by KeyCorp\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "context": "US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Lowered to Strong Sell Rating by KeyCorp\nNegative Sentiment:\nTechnical analysts highlight",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "T-Mobile Q2",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1781,
      "end": 1792,
      "sentence": "Technical analysts highlight bearish patterns—lower highs, falling RSI and high implied volatility—prompting calls for option-selling plays.\nT-Mobile Q2:",
      "context": "atility—prompting calls for option-selling plays.\nT-Mobile Q2: High Volatility Points To An Option Play (Techni",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "$16.6 million",
      "label": "MONEY",
      "start": 1895,
      "end": 1908,
      "sentence": "An insider sale of $16.6 million in TMUS shares by a company director could be viewed as profit-taking.",
      "context": "Analysis)\nNegative Sentiment:\nAn insider sale of $16.6 million in TMUS shares by a company director could be vie",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": true
    },
    {
      "text": "TMUS",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1912,
      "end": 1916,
      "sentence": "An insider sale of $16.6 million in TMUS shares by a company director could be viewed as profit-taking.",
      "context": "ve Sentiment:\nAn insider sale of $16.6 million in TMUS shares by a company director could be viewed as p",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "T-Mobile US, Inc.",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1980,
      "end": 1997,
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US, Inc. (NASDAQ:TMUS) Director Sells $16,627,507.20 in Stock\nPosted 1+ days ago\nAI Generated.",
      "context": "ompany director could be viewed as profit-taking.\nT-Mobile US, Inc. (NASDAQ:TMUS) Director Sells $16,627,507.20 in St",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "NASDAQ",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 1999,
      "end": 2005,
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US, Inc. (NASDAQ:TMUS) Director Sells $16,627,507.20 in Stock\nPosted 1+ days ago\nAI Generated.",
      "context": "ld be viewed as profit-taking.\nT-Mobile US, Inc. (NASDAQ:TMUS) Director Sells $16,627,507.20 in Stock\nPost",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "TMUS",
      "label": "ORG",
      "start": 2006,
      "end": 2010,
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US, Inc. (NASDAQ:TMUS) Director Sells $16,627,507.20 in Stock\nPosted 1+ days ago\nAI Generated.",
      "context": "iewed as profit-taking.\nT-Mobile US, Inc. (NASDAQ:TMUS) Director Sells $16,627,507.20 in Stock\nPosted 1+",
      "is_company": true,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    },
    {
      "text": "$16,627,507.20",
      "label": "MONEY",
      "start": 2027,
      "end": 2041,
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US, Inc. (NASDAQ:TMUS) Director Sells $16,627,507.20 in Stock\nPosted 1+ days ago\nAI Generated.",
      "context": "g.\nT-Mobile US, Inc. (NASDAQ:TMUS) Director Sells $16,627,507.20 in Stock\nPosted 1+ days ago\nAI Generated. May Con",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": true
    },
    {
      "text": "1+ days ago",
      "label": "DATE",
      "start": 2058,
      "end": 2069,
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US, Inc. (NASDAQ:TMUS) Director Sells $16,627,507.20 in Stock\nPosted 1+ days ago\nAI Generated.",
      "context": "US) Director Sells $16,627,507.20 in Stock\nPosted 1+ days ago\nAI Generated. May Contain Errors.",
      "is_company": false,
      "is_person": false,
      "is_location": false,
      "is_financial": false
    }
  ],
  "relationships": [
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "catalysts",
      "verb": "include",
      "object": "approvals",
      "sentence": "Recent positive catalysts include key approvals for its UScellular deal and an analyst upgrade, while negative pressures stem from downgrades, bearish technical signals and insider stock sales.",
      "importance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "regulators",
      "verb": "cleared",
      "object": "acquisition",
      "sentence": "U.S. antitrust and communications regulators cleared T-Mobile’s $4.4 billion acquisition of UScellular after the carrier agreed to end its DEI programs, removing a major hurdle to expansion.",
      "importance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "FCC",
      "verb": "approves",
      "object": "deals",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "importance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "carrier",
      "verb": "drops",
      "object": "programs",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "importance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Research",
      "verb": "upgraded",
      "object": "TMUS",
      "sentence": "Arete Research upgraded TMUS to a “strong-buy” rating, signaling growing analyst confidence.",
      "importance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "US",
      "verb": "highlights",
      "object": "TMUS",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Upgraded by Arete Research to Strong-Buy Rating\nNeutral Sentiment:\nZacks highlights TMUS as a strong momentum stock, underpinned by favorable style scores but not necessarily fundamental changes.",
      "importance": 13
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Zacks",
      "verb": "highlights",
      "object": "TMUS",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Upgraded by Arete Research to Strong-Buy Rating\nNeutral Sentiment:\nZacks highlights TMUS as a strong momentum stock, underpinned by favorable style scores but not necessarily fundamental changes.",
      "importance": 13
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Mobile",
      "verb": "showcasing",
      "object": "network",
      "sentence": "Here's Why T-Mobile (TMUS) is a Strong Momentum Stock\nNeutral Sentiment:\nT-Mobile is showcasing its 5G network at MLB All-Star Week with new automated fan experiences, which may boost brand engagement over the long term.",
      "importance": 15
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "which",
      "verb": "boost",
      "object": "engagement",
      "sentence": "Here's Why T-Mobile (TMUS) is a Strong Momentum Stock\nNeutral Sentiment:\nT-Mobile is showcasing its 5G network at MLB All-Star Week with new automated fan experiences, which may boost brand engagement over the long term.",
      "importance": 15
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Mobile",
      "verb": "Brings",
      "object": "ABS",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile Brings 5G-Powered ABS, New Fan Experiences to MLB All-Star Week — Backed by America's Best Network\nNegative Sentiment:\nKeyCorp cut TMUS to a “strong sell” and lowered its Q2 EPS forecasts on concerns around slowing growth, weighing on sentiment.\nT-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Lowered to Strong Sell Rating by KeyCorp\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "importance": 22
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "KeyCorp",
      "verb": "cut",
      "object": "TMUS",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile Brings 5G-Powered ABS, New Fan Experiences to MLB All-Star Week — Backed by America's Best Network\nNegative Sentiment:\nKeyCorp cut TMUS to a “strong sell” and lowered its Q2 EPS forecasts on concerns around slowing growth, weighing on sentiment.\nT-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Lowered to Strong Sell Rating by KeyCorp\nNegative Sentiment:",
      "importance": 22
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "analysts",
      "verb": "highlight",
      "object": "patterns",
      "sentence": "Technical analysts highlight bearish patterns—lower highs, falling RSI and high implied volatility—prompting calls for option-selling plays.\nT-Mobile Q2:",
      "importance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "SVO",
      "subject": "Inc.",
      "verb": "Sells",
      "object": "16,627,507.20",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US, Inc. (NASDAQ:TMUS) Director Sells $16,627,507.20 in Stock\nPosted 1+ days ago\nAI Generated.",
      "importance": 16
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "T",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US, Inc. (NASDAQ: TMUS) saw its stock react to a mix of regulatory developments, analyst actions and corporate news.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "T",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Mobile",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US, Inc. (NASDAQ: TMUS) saw its stock react to a mix of regulatory developments, analyst actions and corporate news.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "T",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "US",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US, Inc. (NASDAQ: TMUS) saw its stock react to a mix of regulatory developments, analyst actions and corporate news.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "T",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": ",",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US, Inc. (NASDAQ: TMUS) saw its stock react to a mix of regulatory developments, analyst actions and corporate news.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "T",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Inc.",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US, Inc. (NASDAQ: TMUS) saw its stock react to a mix of regulatory developments, analyst actions and corporate news.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "T",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "TMUS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US, Inc. (NASDAQ: TMUS) saw its stock react to a mix of regulatory developments, analyst actions and corporate news.",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Mobile",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US, Inc. (NASDAQ: TMUS) saw its stock react to a mix of regulatory developments, analyst actions and corporate news.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "US",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US, Inc. (NASDAQ: TMUS) saw its stock react to a mix of regulatory developments, analyst actions and corporate news.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": ",",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US, Inc. (NASDAQ: TMUS) saw its stock react to a mix of regulatory developments, analyst actions and corporate news.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Inc.",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US, Inc. (NASDAQ: TMUS) saw its stock react to a mix of regulatory developments, analyst actions and corporate news.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "TMUS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US, Inc. (NASDAQ: TMUS) saw its stock react to a mix of regulatory developments, analyst actions and corporate news.",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Mobile",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "US",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US, Inc. (NASDAQ: TMUS) saw its stock react to a mix of regulatory developments, analyst actions and corporate news.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Mobile",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": ",",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US, Inc. (NASDAQ: TMUS) saw its stock react to a mix of regulatory developments, analyst actions and corporate news.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Mobile",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Inc.",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US, Inc. (NASDAQ: TMUS) saw its stock react to a mix of regulatory developments, analyst actions and corporate news.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Mobile",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "TMUS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US, Inc. (NASDAQ: TMUS) saw its stock react to a mix of regulatory developments, analyst actions and corporate news.",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "US",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": ",",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US, Inc. (NASDAQ: TMUS) saw its stock react to a mix of regulatory developments, analyst actions and corporate news.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "US",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Inc.",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US, Inc. (NASDAQ: TMUS) saw its stock react to a mix of regulatory developments, analyst actions and corporate news.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "US",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "TMUS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US, Inc. (NASDAQ: TMUS) saw its stock react to a mix of regulatory developments, analyst actions and corporate news.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": ",",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Inc.",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US, Inc. (NASDAQ: TMUS) saw its stock react to a mix of regulatory developments, analyst actions and corporate news.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": ",",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "TMUS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US, Inc. (NASDAQ: TMUS) saw its stock react to a mix of regulatory developments, analyst actions and corporate news.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Inc.",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "TMUS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US, Inc. (NASDAQ: TMUS) saw its stock react to a mix of regulatory developments, analyst actions and corporate news.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "TMUS",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "today",
      "entity2_type": "DATE",
      "sentence": "Below is a summary of the drivers moving TMUS shares today:",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "U.S.",
      "entity1_type": "GPE",
      "entity2": "T",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "U.S. antitrust and communications regulators cleared T-Mobile’s $4.4 billion acquisition of UScellular after the carrier agreed to end its DEI programs, removing a major hurdle to expansion.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "U.S.",
      "entity1_type": "GPE",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "U.S. antitrust and communications regulators cleared T-Mobile’s $4.4 billion acquisition of UScellular after the carrier agreed to end its DEI programs, removing a major hurdle to expansion.",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "U.S.",
      "entity1_type": "GPE",
      "entity2": "Mobile",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "U.S. antitrust and communications regulators cleared T-Mobile’s $4.4 billion acquisition of UScellular after the carrier agreed to end its DEI programs, removing a major hurdle to expansion.",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "U.S.",
      "entity1_type": "GPE",
      "entity2": "’s",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "U.S. antitrust and communications regulators cleared T-Mobile’s $4.4 billion acquisition of UScellular after the carrier agreed to end its DEI programs, removing a major hurdle to expansion.",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "U.S.",
      "entity1_type": "GPE",
      "entity2": "$",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "U.S. antitrust and communications regulators cleared T-Mobile’s $4.4 billion acquisition of UScellular after the carrier agreed to end its DEI programs, removing a major hurdle to expansion.",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "U.S.",
      "entity1_type": "GPE",
      "entity2": "4.4",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "U.S. antitrust and communications regulators cleared T-Mobile’s $4.4 billion acquisition of UScellular after the carrier agreed to end its DEI programs, removing a major hurdle to expansion.",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "U.S.",
      "entity1_type": "GPE",
      "entity2": "billion",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "U.S. antitrust and communications regulators cleared T-Mobile’s $4.4 billion acquisition of UScellular after the carrier agreed to end its DEI programs, removing a major hurdle to expansion.",
      "distance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "U.S.",
      "entity1_type": "GPE",
      "entity2": "UScellular",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "U.S. antitrust and communications regulators cleared T-Mobile’s $4.4 billion acquisition of UScellular after the carrier agreed to end its DEI programs, removing a major hurdle to expansion.",
      "distance": 15
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "T",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "U.S. antitrust and communications regulators cleared T-Mobile’s $4.4 billion acquisition of UScellular after the carrier agreed to end its DEI programs, removing a major hurdle to expansion.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "T",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Mobile",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "U.S. antitrust and communications regulators cleared T-Mobile’s $4.4 billion acquisition of UScellular after the carrier agreed to end its DEI programs, removing a major hurdle to expansion.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "T",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "’s",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "U.S. antitrust and communications regulators cleared T-Mobile’s $4.4 billion acquisition of UScellular after the carrier agreed to end its DEI programs, removing a major hurdle to expansion.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "T",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "$",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "U.S. antitrust and communications regulators cleared T-Mobile’s $4.4 billion acquisition of UScellular after the carrier agreed to end its DEI programs, removing a major hurdle to expansion.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "T",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "4.4",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "U.S. antitrust and communications regulators cleared T-Mobile’s $4.4 billion acquisition of UScellular after the carrier agreed to end its DEI programs, removing a major hurdle to expansion.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "T",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "billion",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "U.S. antitrust and communications regulators cleared T-Mobile’s $4.4 billion acquisition of UScellular after the carrier agreed to end its DEI programs, removing a major hurdle to expansion.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "T",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "UScellular",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "U.S. antitrust and communications regulators cleared T-Mobile’s $4.4 billion acquisition of UScellular after the carrier agreed to end its DEI programs, removing a major hurdle to expansion.",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Mobile",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "U.S. antitrust and communications regulators cleared T-Mobile’s $4.4 billion acquisition of UScellular after the carrier agreed to end its DEI programs, removing a major hurdle to expansion.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "’s",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "U.S. antitrust and communications regulators cleared T-Mobile’s $4.4 billion acquisition of UScellular after the carrier agreed to end its DEI programs, removing a major hurdle to expansion.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "$",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "U.S. antitrust and communications regulators cleared T-Mobile’s $4.4 billion acquisition of UScellular after the carrier agreed to end its DEI programs, removing a major hurdle to expansion.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "4.4",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "U.S. antitrust and communications regulators cleared T-Mobile’s $4.4 billion acquisition of UScellular after the carrier agreed to end its DEI programs, removing a major hurdle to expansion.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "billion",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "U.S. antitrust and communications regulators cleared T-Mobile’s $4.4 billion acquisition of UScellular after the carrier agreed to end its DEI programs, removing a major hurdle to expansion.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "UScellular",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "U.S. antitrust and communications regulators cleared T-Mobile’s $4.4 billion acquisition of UScellular after the carrier agreed to end its DEI programs, removing a major hurdle to expansion.",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Mobile",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "’s",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "U.S. antitrust and communications regulators cleared T-Mobile’s $4.4 billion acquisition of UScellular after the carrier agreed to end its DEI programs, removing a major hurdle to expansion.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Mobile",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "$",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "U.S. antitrust and communications regulators cleared T-Mobile’s $4.4 billion acquisition of UScellular after the carrier agreed to end its DEI programs, removing a major hurdle to expansion.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Mobile",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "4.4",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "U.S. antitrust and communications regulators cleared T-Mobile’s $4.4 billion acquisition of UScellular after the carrier agreed to end its DEI programs, removing a major hurdle to expansion.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Mobile",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "billion",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "U.S. antitrust and communications regulators cleared T-Mobile’s $4.4 billion acquisition of UScellular after the carrier agreed to end its DEI programs, removing a major hurdle to expansion.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Mobile",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "UScellular",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "U.S. antitrust and communications regulators cleared T-Mobile’s $4.4 billion acquisition of UScellular after the carrier agreed to end its DEI programs, removing a major hurdle to expansion.",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "’s",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "$",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "U.S. antitrust and communications regulators cleared T-Mobile’s $4.4 billion acquisition of UScellular after the carrier agreed to end its DEI programs, removing a major hurdle to expansion.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "’s",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "4.4",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "U.S. antitrust and communications regulators cleared T-Mobile’s $4.4 billion acquisition of UScellular after the carrier agreed to end its DEI programs, removing a major hurdle to expansion.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "’s",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "billion",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "U.S. antitrust and communications regulators cleared T-Mobile’s $4.4 billion acquisition of UScellular after the carrier agreed to end its DEI programs, removing a major hurdle to expansion.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "’s",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "UScellular",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "U.S. antitrust and communications regulators cleared T-Mobile’s $4.4 billion acquisition of UScellular after the carrier agreed to end its DEI programs, removing a major hurdle to expansion.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "$",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "4.4",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "U.S. antitrust and communications regulators cleared T-Mobile’s $4.4 billion acquisition of UScellular after the carrier agreed to end its DEI programs, removing a major hurdle to expansion.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "$",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "billion",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "U.S. antitrust and communications regulators cleared T-Mobile’s $4.4 billion acquisition of UScellular after the carrier agreed to end its DEI programs, removing a major hurdle to expansion.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "$",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "UScellular",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "U.S. antitrust and communications regulators cleared T-Mobile’s $4.4 billion acquisition of UScellular after the carrier agreed to end its DEI programs, removing a major hurdle to expansion.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "4.4",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "billion",
      "entity2_type": "MONEY",
      "sentence": "U.S. antitrust and communications regulators cleared T-Mobile’s $4.4 billion acquisition of UScellular after the carrier agreed to end its DEI programs, removing a major hurdle to expansion.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "4.4",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "UScellular",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "U.S. antitrust and communications regulators cleared T-Mobile’s $4.4 billion acquisition of UScellular after the carrier agreed to end its DEI programs, removing a major hurdle to expansion.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "billion",
      "entity1_type": "MONEY",
      "entity2": "UScellular",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "U.S. antitrust and communications regulators cleared T-Mobile’s $4.4 billion acquisition of UScellular after the carrier agreed to end its DEI programs, removing a major hurdle to expansion.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Trump",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "DOJ",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Trump",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "T",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Trump",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Trump",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "Mobile",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Trump",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "’s",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Trump",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "FCC",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 18
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Trump",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "two",
      "entity2_type": "CARDINAL",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 20
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Trump",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "T",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 21
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Trump",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 22
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Trump",
      "entity1_type": "PERSON",
      "entity2": "Mobile",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 23
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "DOJ",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "T",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "DOJ",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "DOJ",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Mobile",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "DOJ",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "’s",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "DOJ",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "FCC",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 16
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "DOJ",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "two",
      "entity2_type": "CARDINAL",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 18
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "DOJ",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "T",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 19
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "DOJ",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 20
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "DOJ",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Mobile",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 21
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "T",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "T",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Mobile",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "T",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "’s",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "T",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "FCC",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "T",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "two",
      "entity2_type": "CARDINAL",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "T",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "T",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "T",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 13
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "T",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Mobile",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 14
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Mobile",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "’s",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "FCC",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "two",
      "entity2_type": "CARDINAL",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "T",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Mobile",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 13
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Mobile",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "’s",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Mobile",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "FCC",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Mobile",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "two",
      "entity2_type": "CARDINAL",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Mobile",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "T",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Mobile",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Mobile",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Mobile",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "’s",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "FCC",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "’s",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "two",
      "entity2_type": "CARDINAL",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "’s",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "T",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "’s",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "’s",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Mobile",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "FCC",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "two",
      "entity2_type": "CARDINAL",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "FCC",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "T",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "FCC",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "FCC",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Mobile",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "two",
      "entity1_type": "CARDINAL",
      "entity2": "T",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "two",
      "entity1_type": "CARDINAL",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "two",
      "entity1_type": "CARDINAL",
      "entity2": "Mobile",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "T",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "T",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Mobile",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Mobile",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Trump’s DOJ seems annoyed about having to approve T-Mobile’s latest merger\n,\nFCC approves two T-Mobile deals after wireless carrier drops DEI programs\nPositive Sentiment:",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Arete",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Research",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Arete Research upgraded TMUS to a “strong-buy” rating, signaling growing analyst confidence.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Arete",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "TMUS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Arete Research upgraded TMUS to a “strong-buy” rating, signaling growing analyst confidence.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Research",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "TMUS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Arete Research upgraded TMUS to a “strong-buy” rating, signaling growing analyst confidence.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "T",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Upgraded by Arete Research to Strong-Buy Rating\nNeutral Sentiment:\nZacks highlights TMUS as a strong momentum stock, underpinned by favorable style scores but not necessarily fundamental changes.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "T",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Mobile",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Upgraded by Arete Research to Strong-Buy Rating\nNeutral Sentiment:\nZacks highlights TMUS as a strong momentum stock, underpinned by favorable style scores but not necessarily fundamental changes.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "T",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "US",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Upgraded by Arete Research to Strong-Buy Rating\nNeutral Sentiment:\nZacks highlights TMUS as a strong momentum stock, underpinned by favorable style scores but not necessarily fundamental changes.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "T",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "TMUS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Upgraded by Arete Research to Strong-Buy Rating\nNeutral Sentiment:\nZacks highlights TMUS as a strong momentum stock, underpinned by favorable style scores but not necessarily fundamental changes.",
      "distance": 7
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "T",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Arete",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Upgraded by Arete Research to Strong-Buy Rating\nNeutral Sentiment:\nZacks highlights TMUS as a strong momentum stock, underpinned by favorable style scores but not necessarily fundamental changes.",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "T",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Research",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Upgraded by Arete Research to Strong-Buy Rating\nNeutral Sentiment:\nZacks highlights TMUS as a strong momentum stock, underpinned by favorable style scores but not necessarily fundamental changes.",
      "distance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "T",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Zacks",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Upgraded by Arete Research to Strong-Buy Rating\nNeutral Sentiment:\nZacks highlights TMUS as a strong momentum stock, underpinned by favorable style scores but not necessarily fundamental changes.",
      "distance": 23
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "T",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "TMUS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Upgraded by Arete Research to Strong-Buy Rating\nNeutral Sentiment:\nZacks highlights TMUS as a strong momentum stock, underpinned by favorable style scores but not necessarily fundamental changes.",
      "distance": 25
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Mobile",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Upgraded by Arete Research to Strong-Buy Rating\nNeutral Sentiment:\nZacks highlights TMUS as a strong momentum stock, underpinned by favorable style scores but not necessarily fundamental changes.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "US",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Upgraded by Arete Research to Strong-Buy Rating\nNeutral Sentiment:\nZacks highlights TMUS as a strong momentum stock, underpinned by favorable style scores but not necessarily fundamental changes.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "TMUS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Upgraded by Arete Research to Strong-Buy Rating\nNeutral Sentiment:\nZacks highlights TMUS as a strong momentum stock, underpinned by favorable style scores but not necessarily fundamental changes.",
      "distance": 6
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Arete",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Upgraded by Arete Research to Strong-Buy Rating\nNeutral Sentiment:\nZacks highlights TMUS as a strong momentum stock, underpinned by favorable style scores but not necessarily fundamental changes.",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Research",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Upgraded by Arete Research to Strong-Buy Rating\nNeutral Sentiment:\nZacks highlights TMUS as a strong momentum stock, underpinned by favorable style scores but not necessarily fundamental changes.",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Zacks",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Upgraded by Arete Research to Strong-Buy Rating\nNeutral Sentiment:\nZacks highlights TMUS as a strong momentum stock, underpinned by favorable style scores but not necessarily fundamental changes.",
      "distance": 22
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "TMUS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Upgraded by Arete Research to Strong-Buy Rating\nNeutral Sentiment:\nZacks highlights TMUS as a strong momentum stock, underpinned by favorable style scores but not necessarily fundamental changes.",
      "distance": 24
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Mobile",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "US",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Upgraded by Arete Research to Strong-Buy Rating\nNeutral Sentiment:\nZacks highlights TMUS as a strong momentum stock, underpinned by favorable style scores but not necessarily fundamental changes.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Mobile",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "TMUS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Upgraded by Arete Research to Strong-Buy Rating\nNeutral Sentiment:\nZacks highlights TMUS as a strong momentum stock, underpinned by favorable style scores but not necessarily fundamental changes.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Mobile",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Arete",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Upgraded by Arete Research to Strong-Buy Rating\nNeutral Sentiment:\nZacks highlights TMUS as a strong momentum stock, underpinned by favorable style scores but not necessarily fundamental changes.",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Mobile",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Research",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Upgraded by Arete Research to Strong-Buy Rating\nNeutral Sentiment:\nZacks highlights TMUS as a strong momentum stock, underpinned by favorable style scores but not necessarily fundamental changes.",
      "distance": 10
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Mobile",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Zacks",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Upgraded by Arete Research to Strong-Buy Rating\nNeutral Sentiment:\nZacks highlights TMUS as a strong momentum stock, underpinned by favorable style scores but not necessarily fundamental changes.",
      "distance": 21
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Mobile",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "TMUS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Upgraded by Arete Research to Strong-Buy Rating\nNeutral Sentiment:\nZacks highlights TMUS as a strong momentum stock, underpinned by favorable style scores but not necessarily fundamental changes.",
      "distance": 23
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "US",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "TMUS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Upgraded by Arete Research to Strong-Buy Rating\nNeutral Sentiment:\nZacks highlights TMUS as a strong momentum stock, underpinned by favorable style scores but not necessarily fundamental changes.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "US",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Arete",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Upgraded by Arete Research to Strong-Buy Rating\nNeutral Sentiment:\nZacks highlights TMUS as a strong momentum stock, underpinned by favorable style scores but not necessarily fundamental changes.",
      "distance": 8
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "US",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Research",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Upgraded by Arete Research to Strong-Buy Rating\nNeutral Sentiment:\nZacks highlights TMUS as a strong momentum stock, underpinned by favorable style scores but not necessarily fundamental changes.",
      "distance": 9
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "US",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Zacks",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Upgraded by Arete Research to Strong-Buy Rating\nNeutral Sentiment:\nZacks highlights TMUS as a strong momentum stock, underpinned by favorable style scores but not necessarily fundamental changes.",
      "distance": 20
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "US",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "TMUS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Upgraded by Arete Research to Strong-Buy Rating\nNeutral Sentiment:\nZacks highlights TMUS as a strong momentum stock, underpinned by favorable style scores but not necessarily fundamental changes.",
      "distance": 22
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "TMUS",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Arete",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Upgraded by Arete Research to Strong-Buy Rating\nNeutral Sentiment:\nZacks highlights TMUS as a strong momentum stock, underpinned by favorable style scores but not necessarily fundamental changes.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "TMUS",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Research",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Upgraded by Arete Research to Strong-Buy Rating\nNeutral Sentiment:\nZacks highlights TMUS as a strong momentum stock, underpinned by favorable style scores but not necessarily fundamental changes.",
      "distance": 5
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "TMUS",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Zacks",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Upgraded by Arete Research to Strong-Buy Rating\nNeutral Sentiment:\nZacks highlights TMUS as a strong momentum stock, underpinned by favorable style scores but not necessarily fundamental changes.",
      "distance": 16
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "TMUS",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "TMUS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Upgraded by Arete Research to Strong-Buy Rating\nNeutral Sentiment:\nZacks highlights TMUS as a strong momentum stock, underpinned by favorable style scores but not necessarily fundamental changes.",
      "distance": 18
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Arete",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Research",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Upgraded by Arete Research to Strong-Buy Rating\nNeutral Sentiment:\nZacks highlights TMUS as a strong momentum stock, underpinned by favorable style scores but not necessarily fundamental changes.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Arete",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Zacks",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Upgraded by Arete Research to Strong-Buy Rating\nNeutral Sentiment:\nZacks highlights TMUS as a strong momentum stock, underpinned by favorable style scores but not necessarily fundamental changes.",
      "distance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Arete",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "TMUS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Upgraded by Arete Research to Strong-Buy Rating\nNeutral Sentiment:\nZacks highlights TMUS as a strong momentum stock, underpinned by favorable style scores but not necessarily fundamental changes.",
      "distance": 14
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Research",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Zacks",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Upgraded by Arete Research to Strong-Buy Rating\nNeutral Sentiment:\nZacks highlights TMUS as a strong momentum stock, underpinned by favorable style scores but not necessarily fundamental changes.",
      "distance": 11
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Research",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "TMUS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Upgraded by Arete Research to Strong-Buy Rating\nNeutral Sentiment:\nZacks highlights TMUS as a strong momentum stock, underpinned by favorable style scores but not necessarily fundamental changes.",
      "distance": 13
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Zacks",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "TMUS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "T-Mobile US (NASDAQ:TMUS) Upgraded by Arete Research to Strong-Buy Rating\nNeutral Sentiment:\nZacks highlights TMUS as a strong momentum stock, underpinned by favorable style scores but not necessarily fundamental changes.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "T",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Here's Why T-Mobile (TMUS) is a Strong Momentum Stock\nNeutral Sentiment:\nT-Mobile is showcasing its 5G network at MLB All-Star Week with new automated fan experiences, which may boost brand engagement over the long term.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "T",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Mobile",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Here's Why T-Mobile (TMUS) is a Strong Momentum Stock\nNeutral Sentiment:\nT-Mobile is showcasing its 5G network at MLB All-Star Week with new automated fan experiences, which may boost brand engagement over the long term.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "T",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "TMUS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Here's Why T-Mobile (TMUS) is a Strong Momentum Stock\nNeutral Sentiment:\nT-Mobile is showcasing its 5G network at MLB All-Star Week with new automated fan experiences, which may boost brand engagement over the long term.",
      "distance": 4
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "T",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "T",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Here's Why T-Mobile (TMUS) is a Strong Momentum Stock\nNeutral Sentiment:\nT-Mobile is showcasing its 5G network at MLB All-Star Week with new automated fan experiences, which may boost brand engagement over the long term.",
      "distance": 16
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "T",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Here's Why T-Mobile (TMUS) is a Strong Momentum Stock\nNeutral Sentiment:\nT-Mobile is showcasing its 5G network at MLB All-Star Week with new automated fan experiences, which may boost brand engagement over the long term.",
      "distance": 17
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "T",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Mobile",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Here's Why T-Mobile (TMUS) is a Strong Momentum Stock\nNeutral Sentiment:\nT-Mobile is showcasing its 5G network at MLB All-Star Week with new automated fan experiences, which may boost brand engagement over the long term.",
      "distance": 18
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "T",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "MLB",
      "entity2_type": "EVENT",
      "sentence": "Here's Why T-Mobile (TMUS) is a Strong Momentum Stock\nNeutral Sentiment:\nT-Mobile is showcasing its 5G network at MLB All-Star Week with new automated fan experiences, which may boost brand engagement over the long term.",
      "distance": 26
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "T",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "All",
      "entity2_type": "EVENT",
      "sentence": "Here's Why T-Mobile (TMUS) is a Strong Momentum Stock\nNeutral Sentiment:\nT-Mobile is showcasing its 5G network at MLB All-Star Week with new automated fan experiences, which may boost brand engagement over the long term.",
      "distance": 27
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "T",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "EVENT",
      "sentence": "Here's Why T-Mobile (TMUS) is a Strong Momentum Stock\nNeutral Sentiment:\nT-Mobile is showcasing its 5G network at MLB All-Star Week with new automated fan experiences, which may boost brand engagement over the long term.",
      "distance": 28
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "T",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Star",
      "entity2_type": "EVENT",
      "sentence": "Here's Why T-Mobile (TMUS) is a Strong Momentum Stock\nNeutral Sentiment:\nT-Mobile is showcasing its 5G network at MLB All-Star Week with new automated fan experiences, which may boost brand engagement over the long term.",
      "distance": 29
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "T",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Week",
      "entity2_type": "EVENT",
      "sentence": "Here's Why T-Mobile (TMUS) is a Strong Momentum Stock\nNeutral Sentiment:\nT-Mobile is showcasing its 5G network at MLB All-Star Week with new automated fan experiences, which may boost brand engagement over the long term.",
      "distance": 30
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Mobile",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Here's Why T-Mobile (TMUS) is a Strong Momentum Stock\nNeutral Sentiment:\nT-Mobile is showcasing its 5G network at MLB All-Star Week with new automated fan experiences, which may boost brand engagement over the long term.",
      "distance": 1
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "TMUS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Here's Why T-Mobile (TMUS) is a Strong Momentum Stock\nNeutral Sentiment:\nT-Mobile is showcasing its 5G network at MLB All-Star Week with new automated fan experiences, which may boost brand engagement over the long term.",
      "distance": 3
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "T",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Here's Why T-Mobile (TMUS) is a Strong Momentum Stock\nNeutral Sentiment:\nT-Mobile is showcasing its 5G network at MLB All-Star Week with new automated fan experiences, which may boost brand engagement over the long term.",
      "distance": 15
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Here's Why T-Mobile (TMUS) is a Strong Momentum Stock\nNeutral Sentiment:\nT-Mobile is showcasing its 5G network at MLB All-Star Week with new automated fan experiences, which may boost brand engagement over the long term.",
      "distance": 16
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Mobile",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Here's Why T-Mobile (TMUS) is a Strong Momentum Stock\nNeutral Sentiment:\nT-Mobile is showcasing its 5G network at MLB All-Star Week with new automated fan experiences, which may boost brand engagement over the long term.",
      "distance": 17
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "MLB",
      "entity2_type": "EVENT",
      "sentence": "Here's Why T-Mobile (TMUS) is a Strong Momentum Stock\nNeutral Sentiment:\nT-Mobile is showcasing its 5G network at MLB All-Star Week with new automated fan experiences, which may boost brand engagement over the long term.",
      "distance": 25
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "All",
      "entity2_type": "EVENT",
      "sentence": "Here's Why T-Mobile (TMUS) is a Strong Momentum Stock\nNeutral Sentiment:\nT-Mobile is showcasing its 5G network at MLB All-Star Week with new automated fan experiences, which may boost brand engagement over the long term.",
      "distance": 26
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "EVENT",
      "sentence": "Here's Why T-Mobile (TMUS) is a Strong Momentum Stock\nNeutral Sentiment:\nT-Mobile is showcasing its 5G network at MLB All-Star Week with new automated fan experiences, which may boost brand engagement over the long term.",
      "distance": 27
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Star",
      "entity2_type": "EVENT",
      "sentence": "Here's Why T-Mobile (TMUS) is a Strong Momentum Stock\nNeutral Sentiment:\nT-Mobile is showcasing its 5G network at MLB All-Star Week with new automated fan experiences, which may boost brand engagement over the long term.",
      "distance": 28
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "-",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Week",
      "entity2_type": "EVENT",
      "sentence": "Here's Why T-Mobile (TMUS) is a Strong Momentum Stock\nNeutral Sentiment:\nT-Mobile is showcasing its 5G network at MLB All-Star Week with new automated fan experiences, which may boost brand engagement over the long term.",
      "distance": 29
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Mobile",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "TMUS",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Here's Why T-Mobile (TMUS) is a Strong Momentum Stock\nNeutral Sentiment:\nT-Mobile is showcasing its 5G network at MLB All-Star Week with new automated fan experiences, which may boost brand engagement over the long term.",
      "distance": 2
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Mobile",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "T",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Here's Why T-Mobile (TMUS) is a Strong Momentum Stock\nNeutral Sentiment:\nT-Mobile is showcasing its 5G network at MLB All-Star Week with new automated fan experiences, which may boost brand engagement over the long term.",
      "distance": 14
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Mobile",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Here's Why T-Mobile (TMUS) is a Strong Momentum Stock\nNeutral Sentiment:\nT-Mobile is showcasing its 5G network at MLB All-Star Week with new automated fan experiences, which may boost brand engagement over the long term.",
      "distance": 15
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Mobile",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Mobile",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Here's Why T-Mobile (TMUS) is a Strong Momentum Stock\nNeutral Sentiment:\nT-Mobile is showcasing its 5G network at MLB All-Star Week with new automated fan experiences, which may boost brand engagement over the long term.",
      "distance": 16
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Mobile",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "MLB",
      "entity2_type": "EVENT",
      "sentence": "Here's Why T-Mobile (TMUS) is a Strong Momentum Stock\nNeutral Sentiment:\nT-Mobile is showcasing its 5G network at MLB All-Star Week with new automated fan experiences, which may boost brand engagement over the long term.",
      "distance": 24
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Mobile",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "All",
      "entity2_type": "EVENT",
      "sentence": "Here's Why T-Mobile (TMUS) is a Strong Momentum Stock\nNeutral Sentiment:\nT-Mobile is showcasing its 5G network at MLB All-Star Week with new automated fan experiences, which may boost brand engagement over the long term.",
      "distance": 25
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Mobile",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "EVENT",
      "sentence": "Here's Why T-Mobile (TMUS) is a Strong Momentum Stock\nNeutral Sentiment:\nT-Mobile is showcasing its 5G network at MLB All-Star Week with new automated fan experiences, which may boost brand engagement over the long term.",
      "distance": 26
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Mobile",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Star",
      "entity2_type": "EVENT",
      "sentence": "Here's Why T-Mobile (TMUS) is a Strong Momentum Stock\nNeutral Sentiment:\nT-Mobile is showcasing its 5G network at MLB All-Star Week with new automated fan experiences, which may boost brand engagement over the long term.",
      "distance": 27
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "Mobile",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Week",
      "entity2_type": "EVENT",
      "sentence": "Here's Why T-Mobile (TMUS) is a Strong Momentum Stock\nNeutral Sentiment:\nT-Mobile is showcasing its 5G network at MLB All-Star Week with new automated fan experiences, which may boost brand engagement over the long term.",
      "distance": 28
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "TMUS",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "T",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Here's Why T-Mobile (TMUS) is a Strong Momentum Stock\nNeutral Sentiment:\nT-Mobile is showcasing its 5G network at MLB All-Star Week with new automated fan experiences, which may boost brand engagement over the long term.",
      "distance": 12
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "TMUS",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "-",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Here's Why T-Mobile (TMUS) is a Strong Momentum Stock\nNeutral Sentiment:\nT-Mobile is showcasing its 5G network at MLB All-Star Week with new automated fan experiences, which may boost brand engagement over the long term.",
      "distance": 13
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "TMUS",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "Mobile",
      "entity2_type": "ORG",
      "sentence": "Here's Why T-Mobile (TMUS) is a Strong Momentum Stock\nNeutral Sentiment:\nT-Mobile is showcasing its 5G network at MLB All-Star Week with new automated fan experiences, which may boost brand engagement over the long term.",
      "distance": 14
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "TMUS",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "MLB",
      "entity2_type": "EVENT",
      "sentence": "Here's Why T-Mobile (TMUS) is a Strong Momentum Stock\nNeutral Sentiment:\nT-Mobile is showcasing its 5G network at MLB All-Star Week with new automated fan experiences, which may boost brand engagement over the long term.",
      "distance": 22
    },
    {
      "type": "co-occurrence",
      "entity1": "TMUS",
      "entity1_type": "ORG",
      "entity2": "All",
      "entity2_type": "EVENT",
